<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Product Hunt 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Product Hunt 热门App，网站和产品]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 17:57:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[GetMails - 让每个人都能简单地进行冷接触]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们讨厌冷门的外展，因为大多数工具要么太复杂，要么需要很多其他工具并行才能使外展发挥作用。因此，我们决定为营销人员简化冷推广过程。欢迎加入GetMails大家庭❤️]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/getmails</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/getmails</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 17:30:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We hated cold outreach because most of the tools are either too complicated or they need a lot of other tools parallel to make the outreach work. So, we decided to simplify the cold outreach process for marketers. Welcome to GetMails Family ❤️</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Santa Hat Profile Pic Maker - 在你的个人照片上免费添加一顶圣诞节圣诞老人的帽子]]></title><description><![CDATA[通过在Twitter、Instagram、LinkedIn和Tiktok的社交媒体资料图片上添加圣诞老人的帽子来庆祝2021年圣诞节。我们会自动删除你的背景，并添加很酷的背景图片和效果!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/santa-hat-profile-pic-maker</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/santa-hat-profile-pic-maker</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 14:46:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Celebrate 2021 Christmas by adding a Santa hat to your social media profile picture on Twitter, Instagram, LinkedIn, and Tiktok. We remove your background &amp; add cool background images &amp; effects automatically!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Paperback - 更简单、更整洁的维基页面的替代品]]></title><description><![CDATA[平装书是一种比维基页面更简单、更整洁的选择。与其把东西埋在深层次的结构中，它让你用你的链接、文件和注释创建简明的列表。然后，人们可以真正找到他们需要的东西，而不是一直在问。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/paperback-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/paperback-3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 13:48:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Paperback is a simpler and tidier alternative to wiki pages. Instead of burying stuff in deep hierarchies, it lets you create concise lists with your links, files, and notes. Then, people can actually find what they need, instead of asking around all the time.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Incoggo - 免费的付费广告屏蔽器--阅读《纽约时报》、《华尔街日报》、《华盛顿邮报》等]]></title><description><![CDATA[- ⛔️Incoggo是一个免费的广告屏蔽器，用于付费墙。适用于Mac，即将推出Windows版本! - 📚 自动免费解锁新闻和文章，更方便地获取新闻和信息! - 🗞️ 15+顶级酒馆已解锁。完整列表见go.incoggo.com/pubs]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/incoggo</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/incoggo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 09:16:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>- ⛔️ Incoggo is a free adblocker for paywalls. Available for Mac, coming soon for Windows! - 📚 Automatically unlock news and articles for free and get easier access to news and information! - 🗞️ 15+ top pubs unlocked. Full list at go.incoggo.com/pubs</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hypervault - 安全地管理并与你的团队分享敏感数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[告别用平面文字 "安全笔记 "来存储非密码的东西。Hypervault为企业提供解决方案，以安全地存储、共享和组织多种类型的敏感数据，而不仅仅是密码。对IT部门、开发人员、机构和初创企业来说是非常好的选择!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hypervault</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hypervault</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:01:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Say goodbye to flat text “secure notes” to store anything that’s not a password. Hypervault offers the solution for businesses to securely store, share and organize many types of sensitive data, not just passwords. Great for IT, Devs, Agencies, and Startups!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[QRToon - 把你无聊的二维码变成吸引人的艺术品]]></title><description><![CDATA[把你无聊的二维码变成吸引人的艺术作品。不用担心，它们的工作方式仍与您的原始代码相同。只要提供一个二维码和一张自拍，就可以准备好与大家分享它的卡通版本了!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/qrtoon-toonified-qr-maker</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/qrtoon-toonified-qr-maker</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 21:01:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Turn your boring QR codes into catchy artworks. No worries, they will still work the same way as your original codes. Just provide a QR code and a selfie and get ready to share its Toon version with everybody!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Havoc Shield - 一体化的网络安全平台。12个工具在一个仪表板上]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个为小型企业打造的经济实惠的一体化网络安全平台。通过一个仪表板中的十几种工具，提供漏洞扫描、全球密码管理器、防病毒/防恶意软件威胁保护、策略管理等，让人放心。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/havoc-shield</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/havoc-shield</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 18:49:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>An affordable, all-in-one cybersecurity platform built for small business. Get peace of mind through a dozen tools in one dashboard offering vulnerability scans, global password manager, antivirus/anti-malware threat protection, policy management and more.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SaaS Advent Calendar 2021 - 在降临的每一天，解锁独家SaaS交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[每一天，都可以解锁一些法国最好的SaaS公司的独家优惠。有些你知道，有些你不知道；但大多数你会喜欢。快来加入圣诞老人的队伍，享受一些乐趣吧！😀]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/saas-advent-calendar-2021-1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/saas-advent-calendar-2021-1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 15:01:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>For each day of advent, unlock exclusive deals on some of the best French SaaS companies. Some you&apos;ll know, some you won&apos;t; but most of them you&apos;ll love. Come join Santa&apos;s slede and have some fun 😀</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Greety - 免费创建独特的、基于视频的圣诞卡。]]></title><description><![CDATA[正在寻找一份特别的圣诞礼物吗？只需填写一个表格，附上一个Youtube视频，就能得到一个基于视频的贺卡链接，给你的朋友和家人一个惊喜。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/greety</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/greety</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 14:24:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Looking for a special gift for Christmas? Simply fill out a form, attach a Youtube video and get a link to a video-based greeting card to surprise your friends and family.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[250+ Trends for 2022 - 来自埃森哲、Gartner、Instagram、麦肯锡的70多个报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[2022年的250多个趋势，来自70多个最近发布的趋势报告。 ft: 埃森哲、本尼迪克特-埃文斯、德勤、电通、福雷斯特、福布斯、Fjord、Gartner、Instagram、麦肯锡、Next Atlas、奥美、普华永道、Pinterest、Springwise、Sparks & Honey、Trendhunter、Unity，等等。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/250-trends-for-2022</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/250-trends-for-2022</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 13:46:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>250+ trends for 2022 from 70+ recently released trend reports. ft: Accenture, Benedict Evans, Deloitte, Dentsu, Forrester, Forbes, Fjord, Gartner, Instagram, McKinsey, Next Atlas, Ogilvy, PWC, Pinterest, Springwise, Sparks &amp; Honey, Trendhunter, Unity, &amp; more.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Project Shasta from Adobe - AI驱动的网络音频录制和编辑]]></title><description><![CDATA[Project Shasta将人工智能驱动的音频录制和编辑带入网络，无需下载。现在，任何人都可以创建听起来很专业的音频，而不需要成为专业人士。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/project-shasta-from-adobe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/project-shasta-from-adobe</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 11:47:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Project Shasta brings AI-powered audio recording and editing to the web, no download required. Now anyone can create audio that sounds professional, without needing to be a professional.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[eesel Extensions - 你所有的工作都在一个地方 - 现在也在火狐上了]]></title><description><![CDATA[eesel是对你的浏览器历史的一个过滤器，只显示与工作有关的网页。它几乎适用于任何工具。它在本地运行，所以你的工作永远不会离开你的电脑。在我们在Chrome浏览器上推出几个月后，我们现在也在Firefox上了!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/eesel-extensions</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/eesel-extensions</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 11:20:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>eesel is a filter on your browser history to just show pages relevant for work. It works with pretty much any tool. It runs locally, so your work never leaves your computer. A few months after our launch on Chrome, we’re now on Firefox too!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Podcast Cover Template - 用于播客的播客封面模板]]></title><description><![CDATA[购买后你将拥有这些东西😊 ▶ 101个播客封面 ▶ 101个Instagram帖子 ▶ 101件Youtube缩略图 完全可编辑的播客封面设计 Figma - Adobe XD - Photoshop (Comig Soon)]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/podcast-cover-template</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/podcast-cover-template</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 10:16:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>You&apos;ll Have These When You Buy 😊 ▶ 101 Podcast Covers ▶ 101 Instagram Posts ▶ 101 Pieces Youtube Thumbnails Fully Editable Podcast Cover Designs Figma • Adobe XD • Photoshop (Comig Soon)</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Odyssey - 我们是一个学习型DAO，创造高质量的免费web3教育。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Odyssey是一个学习型DAO，其使命是让下一个100万人加入web3。 我们已经为web3的入门、DeFi、DAO、NFT等编写了高质量的ELI5指南。现在就开始学习👇]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/odyssey-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/odyssey-2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 10:01:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Odyssey is a learning DAO on a mission to onboard the next 1 million people to web3. We&apos;ve written quality ELI5 guides for intro to web3, DeFi, DAOs, NFTs, and more. Start learning now 👇</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Songtastic - 一个有趣的测试，测试你的音乐知识]]></title><description><![CDATA[Spotify Wrapped无处不在，展示了我们对歌曲的热爱。但是，你对你最常听的歌曲到底有多了解？带上Songtastic转一转，了解一下你的分数吧!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/songtastic</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/songtastic</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 09:17:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Spotify Wrapped is everywhere showcasing our love for songs. But how well do you really know your most listened songs? Take Songtastic for a spin and get to know your score!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amon Wallet - 用Amon保护、管理和使用你的加密货币]]></title><description><![CDATA[Amon是由千禧一代创立的，他们致力于建立一个加密货币和法币并存的世界。我们通过我们的Amon钱包、Amon Earn和即将推出的Amon卡，使加密货币服务变得简单。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/amon-wallet</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/amon-wallet</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 09:01:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Amon was founded by millennials who strive for a world where crypto &amp; fiat co-exist. We make crypto services simple with our Amon Wallet, Amon Earn and the forthcoming Amon Card.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[HackerRank Interview - 点击，采访，就完成了]]></title><description><![CDATA[一体化的远程技术采访解决方案。同时编辑代码，在虚拟白板上进行协作，并在你的浏览器中访问一套面试问题的样本。不需要下载。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hackerrank-interview</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hackerrank-interview</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 07:26:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>An all-in-one solution for remote technical interviewing. Simultaneously edit code, collaborate on virtual whiteboards, and access a sample set of interview questions all within your browser. No downloads required.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[heylogin - 无密码登录你的所有网络账户]]></title><description><![CDATA[注重用户体验的登录管理使heylogin变得简单而方便。只要在你的智能手机上轻轻一扫，你就可以一键登录到你的任何网络账户。不再需要密码了。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/heylogin</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/heylogin</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 20:28:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Login management with a focus on user experience makes heylogin simple and convenient. Just swipe on your Smartphone and you can log into any of your web accounts with just one click. No more passwords needed.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Web3 Army - 在加密货币、Web3和区块链领域找工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[到2027年，全球GDP的10%（约9.7万亿美元）将在区块链上。有一个全新的世界要建立，我们需要一支雄心勃勃的专业人员的军队来实现它。Web3Army帮助你找到跳入这个行业的最佳机会。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/web3-army</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/web3-army</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 18:52:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The 10% of global GDP (~$9.7 Trillion) will be on the blockchain by 2027. There&apos;s a whole new world to build and we need an army of ambitious professionals to make it. Web3Army helps you find the best opportunities to jump into the industry.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ngage - 为您的混合会议提供现场演示、问答和投票。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在全年的会议和活动中，通过现场演示、现场投票、测验、问答和文字云，吸引听众。用易于使用的在线编辑器建立互动幻灯片。在你的演讲中加入实时流媒体，并将互动游戏化。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ngage-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ngage-2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 18:40:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Engage audiences for meetings &amp; events throughout the year with live presentations, live polls, quizzes, Q &amp; A, and word cloud. Build interactive slides with the easy-to-use online editor. Add live streaming to your presentations and gamify interaction.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[360+ OKR Examples Directory - 精心策划的科技界每个角色的目标实例清单]]></title><description><![CDATA[对于领导者和IC来说，目标是一些最难想出的东西。这就是为什么我们扩大了我们的图书馆，包括360多个目标和OKR的例子，包括来自G2、GitLab和Privy的贡献。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/360-okr-examples-directory</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/360-okr-examples-directory</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 15:33:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Goals are some of the hardest things for leaders and ICs to come up with. That’s why we’ve expanded our library to include over 360 goal and OKR examples, including contributions from G2, GitLab, and Privy.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Potential - 今天就开启你的最佳生活]]></title><description><![CDATA[潜力帮助你重新获得你的注意力和习惯--让你控制你所做的事情，你的感觉，以及你成为谁。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/potential</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/potential</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 14:01:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Potential helps you reclaim your attention and habits — giving you control over what you do, how you feel, and who you become.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fanalyze Voice - SIRI用于NFL橄榄球幻想和体育投注数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[你所有的NFL幻想或体育投注问题的SIRI。通过语音或文字输入询问有关NFL统计数据、球员和球队信息、大/小球预测、赔率等问题。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fanalyze-voice</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fanalyze-voice</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 13:06:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The SIRI for all your NFL Fantasy or sports betting questions. Ask questions about NFL statistics, player and team info, over/under predictions, odds, and more through your voice or text input.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[nuka - 你将购买的最后一台笔记本]]></title><description><![CDATA[嗨，这是nuka.me! BBC专题报道和3次reddot奖的永恒文具 可重复使用的笔记本和永无止境的铅笔 它配备了一个应用程序，将手写变成数字 10月开始发货 目前已售罄 6500/6500 https://nuka.me/buy/，价格为-30%，2月获得一个]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nuka</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nuka</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 12:10:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Hi, it&apos;s nuka.me! BBC featured &amp; 3 times reddot awarded eternal stationery Reusable notebook &amp; never-ending pencil It comes with an app that turns handwriting into digital Shipping started Oct. Currently sold out 6500/6500 https://nuka.me/buy/ with -30%, get one in Feb</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Typewise Text Prediction API (Beta) - 在你的软件中添加谷歌风格的智能撰写]]></title><description><![CDATA[使用Typewise API（Beta）在几分钟内将先进的文本预测和自动更正AI添加到您的软件或平台： 🤖 下一个单词和句子预测 🔤 自动更正（-75%的错字） 🌎 语言检测 😵 表情符号搜索 🔒 100%隐私，在🇨🇭制造]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/typewise-text-prediction-api-beta</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/typewise-text-prediction-api-beta</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 10:47:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Add advanced text prediction and autocorrect AI to your software or platform in minutes with Typewise API (Beta): 🤖 Next-word and sentence prediction 🔤 Autocorrection (-75% typos) 🌎 Language Detection 😵‍ Emoji Search 🔒 100% Privacy, made in 🇨🇭</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pioneer 3.0 - 创始人的家在第0天]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们将在先锋计划中增加一个新的选项。除了成为先锋的所有现有好处外，你的公司有2%的投资。我们还将增加一个为期一个月的硅谷之旅，与其他创始人一起。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pioneer-3-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pioneer-3-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 10:17:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We’re adding a new option to the Pioneer offer: 2% of your company for a $20k investment, in addition to all the existing benefits of becoming a Pioneer. We&apos;re also adding a monthlong trip to Silicon Valley with fellow founders.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Virtual Event Chat Kit - 用于建立应用内虚拟活动聊天的UI工具包和示例应用程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[100多个精心设计的屏幕凝聚成映射出的流程，因此您和您的团队可以跳入Figma，比以往任何时候都更快地创建您自己的定制活动聊天。示例应用程序显示了Stream的聊天API，该API也可免费用于个人使用和小型项目，为后端提供支持。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/virtual-event-chat-kit</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/virtual-event-chat-kit</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 10:00:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>100+ polished screens coalesce into mapped-out flows so you and your team can jump into Figma and create your own custom event chat faster than ever. The sample app shows Stream&apos;s chat API, also free for personal use and small projects, powering the backend.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021 Looped - 关于2021年，你的日历怎么说？]]></title><description><![CDATA[好奇地想知道你是如何在工作中花费时间的？2021年的Looped对你的日历年进行了汇总，并产生了独特的见解，如在会议中花费的时间，会见的人数以及其他一些很酷的统计。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/2021-looped</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/2021-looped</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:48:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Curious to know how you spend your time at work? 2021 Looped rounds up your calendar year and generates unique insights like time spent in meetings, the number of people met along with some other cool stats.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Detail 2 - 简单的电影式视频]]></title><description><![CDATA[用你的Mac录制和流传高质量的视频。通过场景、多镜头和自动取景，将你的 Mac 变成一个制作室。细节可与你的 iPhone、iPad、内置网络摄像头或任何其他摄像头一起使用。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/detail-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/detail-2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:48:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Record and stream high-quality video with your Mac. Turn your Mac into a production studio with Scenes, multi-cam, and auto framing. Detail works with your iPhone, iPad, built-in webcam, or any other camera.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Multiversial - 科技和商业新闻变得更聪明的西班牙语日报]]></title><description><![CDATA[MultiVersial是一份每日通讯，以西班牙语提供最新的科技商业信息。语言仍然是获取知识的一个障碍。一份有趣而简单的通讯，让你在5分钟内掌握最新信息，了解科技战略，实现专业成长。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/multiversial</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/multiversial</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:16:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>MultiVersial is a daily newsletter with the latest in tech business in Spanish. Languages are still a barrier to accessing knowledge. A fun and simple newsletter that allows you to stay up to date, understand tech strategy, and grow professionally in 5 mins</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Opal C1 - 第一个帮助你看起来更好的专业网络摄像机。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们正在为那些与他们的工作--他们的团队、员工、客户--的主要联系是通过视频通话的人建立Opal。我们希望通过一个即插即用的系统，让每个人都能轻松拥有专业的设置。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/opal-c1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/opal-c1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:16:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We’re building Opal for anyone who’s primary connection to their job – their team, their employees, their customers – is through video calls. We want to make it easy for everyone to have a professional setup, with a single plug and play system.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Face Swapper - 免费交换面孔，前所未有]]></title><description><![CDATA[忘记那些来自图片库的过度使用的面孔。忘掉有不适当许可证的照片。改变面孔或身体，在广告、电子商务、社交媒体、教育、光鲜的杂志等方面使用它们。卓越的质量。无与伦比的分辨率。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/face-swapper</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/face-swapper</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:01:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Forget about overused faces from stock photos. Forget about photos with an inappropriate license. Change faces or bodies and use them in ads, e-commerce, social media, education, glossy magazines, etc. Exceptional quality. Unrivaled resolution.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ripple - 掌控你的情绪，赢得一天，每一天]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ripple是一款情绪跟踪应用程序，通过摆脱焦虑、抑郁和毒性，帮助人们改善心理健康。只要在1到10的范围内选择你的满意度和能量水平。Ripple将翻译你的情绪，并将其转化为文字!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ripple-13</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ripple-13</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:01:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Ripple is a mood tracking app that helps people improve their mental health by getting rid of anxiety, depression, and toxicity. Just choose your satisfaction and energy level on a scale of 1 to 10. Ripple will translate your emotions and put them into words!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AutoCloud - 自动化的三维云基础设施图和洞察力]]></title><description><![CDATA[对于在AWS、Azure和GCP上运行工作负载的人来说，AutoCloud可以自动绘制架构图，进行合规性检查和漂移检测。使用3D环境或通过查询GraphQL端点来探索洞察力。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/autocloud</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/autocloud</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 08:48:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>For anyone running workloads on AWS, Azure, and GCP, AutoCloud automates architecture diagrams, compliance checks, and drift detection. Explore insights using a 3D environment or by querying a GraphQL endpoint.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Magic Sidebar by BlackMagic.so - 为Twitter提供强大的增强体验]]></title><description><![CDATA[Magic Sidebar是Twitter的最佳浏览器扩展。今天就使用它，解开你从不知道的见解，与你的受众更好地沟通，并建立强大的1：1关系。也可使用iOS和Android的移动应用程序!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/magic-sidebar-by-blackmagic-so</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/magic-sidebar-by-blackmagic-so</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 08:36:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Magic Sidebar is the best browser extension for Twitter. Use it today and unlock insights you never knew about, communicate better with your audience, and build strong 1:1 relationships. Mobile apps for iOS and Android are also available!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Creativity Booster by Alpe Audio - 为你的教学和内容寻找故事和例子]]></title><description><![CDATA[不再有写作障碍。不要一直纠结于如何打开你的课程、文章或视频。自动生成伟大的开场钩子、故事和相关的例子，涉及你想教的或想写的任何东西!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/creativity-booster-by-alpe-audio</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/creativity-booster-by-alpe-audio</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 23:28:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>No more writers block. Don&apos;t stay stuck wondering how to open your lesson, article or video. Automatically generate great opening hooks, stories and relevant examples about anything you want to teach or write about!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Christmas Design Assets by Iconfinder - 免费的节日图标、插图和动画]]></title><description><![CDATA[用这些节日的好东西洒在你的季节性内容上。小精灵们来了，他们带来了充满设计资产的圣诞赠品，非常适合你的节日通讯、简报和社交媒体帖子。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/christmas-design-assets-by-iconfinder</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/christmas-design-assets-by-iconfinder</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 16:02:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Sprinkle up your seasonal content with these festive goodies. Here come the elves with a Christmas freebie full of design assets that are perfect for your holiday newsletters, presentations &amp; social media posts.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[HiHo - 具有无限线程的异步视频讨论区]]></title><description><![CDATA[HiHo是一个面对面的社交应用程序，用于认识有趣的人并进行精彩的视频对话。通过异步回复和无限线程，每个人都可以在任何时间参与。该应用程序既提供公共论坛，也提供私人DMs。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hiho</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hiho</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 16:02:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>HiHo is a face-forward social app for meeting interesting people and having great video conversations. With asynchronous replies and infinite threading, everyone can participate at any time. The app offers both public forums as well as private DMs.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CommerceBooster - 一个用于电子商务的开源B2B UI模板]]></title><description><![CDATA[CommerceBooster是第一个开源的B2B电子商务的UI模板。它可以在Figma社区免费使用，并针对commercetools和Vue Storefront进行了优化。它实际上为任何开始B2B电子商务项目的人节省了几个月的工作。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/commercebooster</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/commercebooster</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 15:52:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>CommerceBooster is the first open-source, UI template for B2B eCommerce. It’s available for free on the Figma Community and optimized for commercetools and Vue Storefront. It literally saves months of work for anyone starting B2B eCommerce projects.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Carrot - 你的所有购物，像魔术一样组织起来]]></title><description><![CDATA[无法跟踪你想买的东西？认识一下Carrot，这个扩展可以在你购物时自动收集你的购物车。你可以通过点击回到产品上，创建可分享和可赠送的收藏，获得降价提醒，而且完全免费！这就是Carrot。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/carrot-4400273f-0d5e-4a81-a978-0f2477a39ad6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/carrot-4400273f-0d5e-4a81-a978-0f2477a39ad6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 13:14:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Can’t keep track of the stuff you want to buy? Meet Carrot, the extension that automatically collects your carts as you shop. You can get back to products with a click, create shareable and gift-able collections, get price drop alerts, and it&apos;s totally free!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pilot - 远程团队的薪资、福利和合规性]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pilot为拥有远程团队的美国公司提供薪资、福利和合规性。轻松地在160多个国家的员工和240多个国家的承包商入职和付款。为Product Hunt用户提供特殊价格： pilot.co/producthunt]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pilot-8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pilot-8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 12:55:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Pilot provides payroll, benefits, and compliance for US-based companies with remote teams. Easily onboard and pay employees in 160+ countries and contractors in 240+ countries. Offering special pricing for Product Hunt users: pilot.co/producthunt</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Battle of Mars - 一个玩家与玩家之间的NFT游戏]]></title><description><![CDATA[火星之战是一个PVP的NFT游戏，你可以挑战对方，把对手的火星人带走。1. 铸造一个火星人（有10,000个独特的火星人） 2. 加入一个加密派别 3. 挑战朋友并夺走他们的火星人]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-battle-of-mars</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-battle-of-mars</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 10:16:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The Battle of Mars is a PVP NFT game where you can challenge each other and take your opponent&apos;s Martian away. 1. Mint a Martian (10,000 unique martians available) 2. Join a crypto faction 3. Challenge a friend and take their Martian away</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pretty Progress - 在你的iPhone主屏幕上有漂亮的倒计时小工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[漂亮的进度允许你在你的iPhone主屏幕上添加漂亮的个性化的倒计时和进度条部件。在你每天使用的设备上跟踪并提醒自己重要的事情。清晰而方便。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pretty-progress</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pretty-progress</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 10:16:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Pretty Progress allows you to add beautiful &amp; personalized Countdown &amp; Progress Bar widgets on your iPhone&apos;s Home Screen. Track and remind yourself about the important things on the device you use every day. Clear and convenient.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Adobe Creative Cloud Express - 快速、轻松地制作社交图形和更多]]></title><description><![CDATA[Creative Cloud Express（以前的Adobe Spark）使您可以轻松地开始使用数以千计的精美模板，以及用于社交媒体内容、标志和更多的资产。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/adobe-creative-cloud-express</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/adobe-creative-cloud-express</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 10:01:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Creative Cloud Express (formerly Adobe Spark) makes it easy to get started with thousands of beautiful templates, plus assets for social media content, logos, and more.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Albert - 在Slack上为你的团队提高网络安全意识]]></title><description><![CDATA[艾伯特通过Slack向你的团队传授网络安全基础知识。这些课程很短，为每个员工动态定制，具有互动性，并且全年发送。这就是为什么你的团队会喜欢它。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/albert-5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/albert-5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 09:48:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Albert teaches cybersecurity basics to your team over Slack. The courses are short, dynamically customized for each employee, interactive, and sent all year long. That&apos;s why your team will love it.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tella for Chrome - 在Chrome浏览器的任何地方都能录制精彩的视频]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tella for Chrome，屏幕和相机记录器，让你的工作看起来很棒。在Chrome浏览器的任何地方录制完全可定制的、可立即分享的视频。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tella-for-chrome</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tella-for-chrome</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 09:31:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Tella for Chrome, the screen and camera recorder that makes your work look great. Record fully customisable, instantly shareable videos from anywhere in Chrome.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Around 3.0 - 为你的下一个快乐时光提供带有音乐和游戏的视频通话]]></title><description><![CDATA[Around独特的视频通话旨在帮助混合远程团队一起创造、协作和庆祝。现在还配有音乐和游戏，以促进团队的团结和联系。在你的下一个快乐时光或联合办公会议上试试吧。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/around-3-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/around-3-0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:47:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Around&apos;s radically unique video calls are designed to help hybrid-remote teams create, collaborate and celebrate together. Now comes with music and games for team bonding and connection. Try it for your next happy hour or co-working session.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Smart VC Search by Unicorn Nest - 为你的创业公司提供免费的独特的相关风险投资商名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们建立了一个算法，分析38000个风险投资基金的历史数据，为初创企业推荐相关的投资者（种子期、A轮、B轮和C轮）。填写调查问卷 ➡️获得一份VC名单（包括决策者） ➡️立即开始投资者推广 🚀]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/smart-vc-search-by-unicorn-nest</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/smart-vc-search-by-unicorn-nest</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:47:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We&apos;ve built an algorithm that analyses historical data of 38,000 VC funds and suggests relevant investors for startups (seed, round A, B and C). Fill in the questionnaire ➡️ Get a list of VCs (incl. decision makers) ➡️ Start investor outreach immediately 🚀</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ZeroBlur - 模糊敏感信息，自信地分享屏幕]]></title><description><![CDATA[ZeroBlur是一个100%免费的Chrome扩展，可以快速模糊敏感信息。在提供产品演示或销售电话时，不再担心敏感数据的泄露。只需点击几下，你就能模糊任何网络应用或网站的任何元素或页面区域。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zeroblur</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zeroblur</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:47:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>ZeroBlur is a 100% free Chrome extension to quickly blur sensitive information. Stop worrying about leaking sensitive data when delivering a product demo or a sales call. In few clicks you&apos;ll be able to blur any element or page area of any web app or website.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trivia Game Center - 在你的浏览器中通过团队游戏为你的工作增添乐趣]]></title><description><![CDATA[你难道不讨厌你的周一忧郁症在周五晚上结束吗？别担心! 在实时小组电话中与你的团队一起玩猜谜和猜字游戏，并与你的团队进行虚拟的联系。不需要安装! 打开你的浏览器，准备好享受一些乐趣吧 🎉。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/trivia-game-center-1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/trivia-game-center-1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Don’t you hate it when your Monday blues end on Friday nights? Fret not! Play Quizzes and Pictionary with your team in real-time group calls and bond with your team virtually. No installation required! Fire up your browsers and get ready to have some fun 🎉</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>