<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Product Hunt 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Product Hunt 热门App，网站和产品]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 19:23:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[InLoop - 为你的社区发起一个会员制的NFT]]></title><description><![CDATA[InLoop帮助创作者为他们的社区推出会员制NFT，只需0代码和艺术。生成独特的NFT会员卡，设计一个定制的店面，并为代币所有权背后的独家内容把关。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/inloop-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/inloop-2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 19:02:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>InLoop helps creators launch a membership NFT for their community with 0 code and art. Generate unique NFT membership cards, design a custom storefront, and gate exclusive content behind token ownership.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Snoozz - 缓冲标签和窗口，以便以后使用]]></title><description><![CDATA["Snoozz "标签和窗口现在就会自动重新打开 - 暂停个别标签、选定的标签或整个窗口 - 暂停一次或重复间隔（每周或每月） - 极其轻量级和开放源代码 阅读更多信息，请访问https://snoozz.me]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/snoozz</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/snoozz</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 17:19:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&quot;Snoozz&quot; tabs and windows now and they will reopen automatically later - Snooze individual tabs, selected tabs, or full windows - Snooze once or at repeated intervals (weekly or monthly) - Extremely lightweight and open source Read more on the https://snoozz.me</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gwaber - 联系到1,000,000多名远程工作者，申请远程工作。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gwaber是一个简单的平台，在一个地方连接远程求职者和远程公司。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/gwaber</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/gwaber</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 16:59:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Gwaber is an easy platform that connect between remote job seekers and remote companies in one place.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[UKO - 免费的Figma仪表盘和设计系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[Uko是一个免费的Figma仪表盘和设计系统捆绑包，包含大量的组件和页面。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/uko</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/uko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 14:01:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Uko is a Free Figma Dashboards &amp; Design System Bundle with lots of Components and pages</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NeuralCam 5 - 4800万像素的iPhone照片，夜间模式，HDR和微距模式]]></title><description><![CDATA[NeuralCam 5是iPhone上最先进的计算摄影相机应用程序，可用于拍摄夜间和白天的照片。通过人工智能驱动的4800万像素超级分辨率、微距模式和NeuralHDR捕捉更好的照片。更多详情请见：https://neural.cam/news/ https://neural.cam/news/nightmode5/]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/neuralcam-5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/neuralcam-5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 13:29:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>NeuralCam 5 is the most advanced Computational Photography Camera App for the iPhone for both Night and Day photos. Capture better photos with AI powered 48MP Super-resolution, Macro-Mode and NeuralHDR. More details here: https://neural.cam/news/ https://neural.cam/news/nightmode5/</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sleek - 愉快地完成任务]]></title><description><![CDATA[发现一种新的令人愉快的方式来创建和管理你的待办事项。为任务和提醒引入了一个新的彩色等级系统。Sleek是完全可定制的! 你可以改变主题和字体。设置到期日和提醒，添加注释、链接和更多]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sleek-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sleek-3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 13:29:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Discover a new delightful way to create and manage your to-do&apos;s. Introducing a new colorful Rank system for tasks and reminders. Sleek is completely customizable! You can change themes and fonts. Set due dates and reminders, add notes, links and more!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YouNote - 无缝记下YouTube视频]]></title><description><![CDATA[YouNote是一个极其简单的网络应用程序，允许用户观看YouTube视频并在旁边以RichText格式做笔记。目前处于测试阶段。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/younote</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/younote</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 13:29:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>YouNote is an extremely simple web application that allows users to watch a YouTube video and take notes next to it in RichText format. Currently in Beta.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Quire Nested Kanban Board - 让无限嵌套的任务列表遇到看板]]></title><description><![CDATA[Quire是一个现代协作应用程序，旨在帮助有远见的团队实现大的想法。以嵌套任务列表视图而闻名，现在引入了嵌套看板视图。在Inc和Huffington Post上被评为最佳项目管理软件之一。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/quire-nested-kanban-board</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/quire-nested-kanban-board</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 11:46:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Quire is a modern collaborative app made to help visionary teams with big ideas. Well-known for Nested Task List View, now introducing Nested Kanban Board View. Featured as one of the best project management software on Inc and Huffington Post.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Outdone - 人工智能驱动的礼物推荐]]></title><description><![CDATA[特殊场合是有压力的。Outdone的Ai-powered礼品推荐器让你少了一件事的烦恼。目前，Outdone的引擎推荐服装品牌，但我们计划扩大到其他礼品类别，并很快将用户引向特定的产品!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/outdone</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/outdone</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 11:24:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Special occasions are stressful. Outdone&apos;s Ai-powered gift recommender gives you one less thing to worry about. For now, Outdone&apos;s engine recommends apparel brands, but we plan to expand into other gift categories and drive users to specific products soon!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Runbooks by Airplane - 将脚本、SQL等转化为内部工作流程]]></title><description><![CDATA[Airplane Runbooks可以轻松地将少量的代码变成复杂的内部工作流程。模拟入职流程、管理操作、类似于cron的时间表等等，并与你的团队分享。它就像Zapier，但适用于触及prod数据的第一方操作。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/runbooks-by-airplane</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/runbooks-by-airplane</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 09:01:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Airplane Runbooks make it easy to turn small amounts of code into complex internal workflows. Model onboarding flows, admin operations, cron-like schedules and more and share with your team. It&apos;s like Zapier but for first-party operations that touch prod data.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SuperDMs - 只需2次点击，就能向所有的Twitter回复发送批量DMs]]></title><description><![CDATA[SuperDMs通过向你的推特回应者批量发送DM，帮助你增加你的关注。你可以使用SuperDMs来发送你的。- 赠品 - 通讯 - 独特的优惠 - 特别策划的内容 SuperDMs是所有活跃的Twitter用户的理想选择。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/superdms</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/superdms</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 08:37:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>SuperDMs helps you grow your following by sending bulk DMs to your tweet responders. You can use SuperDMs to send your: - Giveaways - Newsletters - Offers that are unique - Specially-curated content SuperDMs is ideal for all active Twitter users.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BiFi X - 轻松的闪电贷款。获得杠杆收益的耕作和交易。]]></title><description><![CDATA[BiFi X是一项DeFi服务，使你能够在一次交易中使用闪电式贷款的收益耕作和保证金交易头寸获得最大的杠杆。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bifi-x</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bifi-x</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 08:18:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>BiFi X is a DeFi service that enables you to get maximum leverage in a single transaction using flash loans on yield farming and margin trading positions.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Okel - 与合适的陌生人分享膳食并不奇怪]]></title><description><![CDATA[Okel是一个社交平台，通过分享当地餐馆的饭菜将用户联系起来。与约会软件的功能类似，Okel根据共同的兴趣、最喜欢的美食和可用的时间来匹配用户。等待名单 👉 https://www.joinokel.com/]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/okel</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/okel</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 08:18:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Okel is a social platform that connects users over sharing meals at local restaurants. Similar to how dating apps function, Okel matches users based on shared interests, favorite cuisines, and times of availability. Waitlist 👉 https://www.joinokel.com/</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reward Hunt - 每周通过对喜欢的产品进行评论获得100美元的奖金]]></title><description><![CDATA[在Capterra、G2、Trustpilot等网站上有75.000美元的活跃评论奖励计划。通过对你最喜欢的产品进行评论或发现新的产品来获得报酬! 奖励计划的产品搜索]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/reward-hunt</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/reward-hunt</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 22:00:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>$75.000 active review reward programs on Capterra, G2, Trustpilot etc. Get paid by making review about your favorite products or discovering new ones! Product Hunt for Reward Programs</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fantasy Startup - 财务复杂性是新的投资标准]]></title><description><![CDATA[通过这种真实的模拟，你将--在几周内体验10年的投资；--掌握股权的非流动性；--建立耐心、纪律和毅力；--发现如何保护你的净资产；以及--成为财务上的老手。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fantasy-startup</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fantasy-startup</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 15:19:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With this real-to-life simulation, you will - Experience 10 yrs of investing in a few weeks; - Grasp the illiquid nature of equity; - Build patience, discipline &amp; perseverance; - Discover how to protect your net worth; and - Become Financially Sophisticated</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wicked Launchers - 13个带有HTML、Tailwind CSS的启动器和即将推出的模板]]></title><description><![CDATA[Wicked Launchers是一个用Tailwind CSS制作的13个英雄的集合，准备好获得注册，将它连接到你的数据库，使用你的副本，你就可以开始了]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/wicked-launchers</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/wicked-launchers</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 14:17:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Wicked Launchers is a collection of 13 heros made with Tailwind CSS ready to get Sign Ups, connect it to your data base, use your copy and you are ready to go!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Biport Wallet - 你的去中心化的多币种钱包]]></title><description><![CDATA[用Biport多链钱包开始你的区块链之旅，适用于比特币、以太坊、BSC以及其他。Biport允许你在一个地方管理散落在不同区块链上的加密货币，而不需要切换区块链网络。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/biport-wallet</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/biport-wallet</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 13:32:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Start your blockchain journey with Biport Multichain Wallet for Bitcoin, Ethereum, BSC, and beyond. Biport allows you to manage cryptocurrencies scattered across different blockchains all in one place without switching blockchain networks.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ZUQ.AI for Facebook Messenger - 创建你自己的人工智能客户支持代理，不需要代码]]></title><description><![CDATA[Zuq学习您的常见问题，并立即为您的客户提供重复性问题的相关答案。Zuq就像一个完美的客户支持人工智能代理，它将昼夜不停地工作，总是很有礼貌，只会变得更聪明，而且永远不会退出。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zuq-ai-for-facebook-messenger</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zuq-ai-for-facebook-messenger</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 12:44:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Zuq learns your FAQ and instantly provides your customers with relevant answers to repetitive questions. Zuq is like a perfect customer support AI agent that will work around the clock, always be polite, only get smarter, and will never quit.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Emojination - 使用表情符号创建有趣的引人入胜的图形 😎]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个结合了表情符号和现代美学的简单设计工具。在几秒钟内创建有趣的引人入胜的视觉效果。壮大你的社交媒体，表达你的公司文化，脱颖而出，最重要的是要有乐趣!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/emojination-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/emojination-3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 11:26:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A simple design tool combining emojis and modern aesthetics. Create fun engaging visuals in seconds. Grow your social media, express your company culture, standout and most importantly have fun!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Podcast Audiogram Creator by Milk Video - 带有社会剪辑的标题和标志的视频字幕生成器]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个将播客快速转化为社会听觉的工具。它不需要注册，而且是免费的! 它是如何工作的。* 上传一个播客 *添加标题和设置颜色 *剪辑一个关键时刻 *下载和分享 如果你有一个播客，我们希望得到你的反馈!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/podcast-audiogram-creator-by-milk-video</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/podcast-audiogram-creator-by-milk-video</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 11:26:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>This is a tool to quickly turn podcasts into social audiograms. There is no sign up and it&apos;s free! How it works: * Upload a podcast * Add titles and set colors * Clip a key moment * Download and share If you have a podcast, we would love your feedback!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Co.Lab Learning - 与他人一起，在小组中现场学习]]></title><description><![CDATA[一种新的多人在线学习方法。通过Co.Lab的混合直播、无讲师的课程，观看视频、开展活动、分享观点并交朋友。通过在亲密的小团体中相互学习和交流，更深入地学习。#LearnTogether]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/co-lab-learning</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/co-lab-learning</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 11:01:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A new multiplayer-method of learning online. Watch videos, do activities, share perspectives and make friends via Co.Lab’s hybrid-live, instructor-less courses. Go deeper by learning with and from one another in small intimate groups. #LearnTogether</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MRR Meter Generator - 为你的Twitter和Instagram简历提供ASCII进度条]]></title><description><![CDATA[生成很酷的进度条，展示你的MRR朝着你的梦想目标的进展。🤑非常适合独立黑客和创业者在公开场合建立他们的开放式创业公司。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mrr-meter-generator</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mrr-meter-generator</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 10:40:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Generate cool progress bars to showcase your MRR progress toward your dream goals. 🤑 Perfect for indie hackers &amp; entrepreneurs who build in public their open startups.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Ultimate Google Sheet Toolkit - 99个资源来提高你的电子表格游戏]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们把一个精心策划的模板、视频和教程列表放在一起，可以帮助你建立你的分析专业知识。浏览这个目录，为你的任务找到合适的工具。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-ultimate-google-sheet-toolkit</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-ultimate-google-sheet-toolkit</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 10:40:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We put together a curated list of templates, videos, and tutorials that can help you build your analytics expertise. Browse through this directory to find the right tools for your task.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fundraising Market Map - 所有可用于筹款的工具的视觉概述]]></title><description><![CDATA[为你的初创企业获得资金是很难的，但有数百家公司在帮助你进行筹款工作。这张地图是对筹款生态系统中每一个参与者的直观概述。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fundraising-market-map</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fundraising-market-map</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 10:24:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Getting funding for your startup is hard, but there are hundreds of companies helping you with your fundraising efforts. This map is a visual overview of every player in the fundraising ecosystem.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Headroom 2.0 - 通过实时AI视频会议进行免提会议]]></title><description><![CDATA[净空实现了自然的视频通话。我们的人工智能可以识别手势，提供实时记录和摘要，并允许你在重播、记录和笔记中进行搜索。专注于人，让Headroom将工作自动化。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/headroom-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/headroom-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 10:24:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Headroom enables natural video calls. Our AI recognizes gestures, provides real-time transcripts and summaries, and allows you to search across replays, transcripts and notes. ​​Focus on people and let Headroom automate away the work.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AcquireFlow - 英国和欧洲的SaaS、电子商务初创企业收购市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[AcquireFlow是英国和欧洲的免费私人收购市场，供数字初创企业的买家和卖家使用。我们专注于SaaS、电子商务和亚马逊FBA等关键领域。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/acquireflow</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/acquireflow</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 10:03:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>AcquireFlow is the UK &amp; Europe&apos;s free private acquisition marketplace for buyers and sellers of digital startups. We focus on the key areas of SaaS, e-commerce and Amazon FBA.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Status Page by Spike.sh - 为你的网站、应用程序或商店提供漂亮的状态页面]]></title><description><![CDATA[为您的网站、应用程序和商店创建漂亮的品牌状态页。🚀 快速设置 - 在2分钟内创建您的品牌状态页。分享有关事故和计划维修的实时更新。🎁 12月免费提供无限的状态页!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/status-page-by-spike-sh</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/status-page-by-spike-sh</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 09:46:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Create beautiful and branded Status Pages for your website, app and store. 🚀 Fast setup - create your branded status page in 2 minutes. Share real time updates about incidents and planned maintenances. 🎁 Unlimited Status Pages for free in December!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chatwoot 2.0 - 开源的自我托管的客户参与套件]]></title><description><![CDATA[Chatwoot是一个开源的、自我托管的客户参与套件。通过Chatwoot，你可以查看和管理你的客户数据，与他们沟通，无论他们使用哪种媒介，并根据他们的资料重新与他们接触。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/chatwoot-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/chatwoot-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 09:33:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Chatwoot is an open-source, self-hosted customer engagement suite. With Chatwoot, you can view and manage your customer data, communicate with them irrespective of which medium they use, and re-engage them based on their profile.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ycode - 无代码网络应用程序生成器，设计与功能完美结合]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ycode是一个可视化的开发平台，使创作者能够在无需雇佣开发人员的情况下建立自定义的网络项目。Ycode的使命是使视觉开发与手工编码一样强大，只是更快、更容易获得。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ycode-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ycode-3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 09:33:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Ycode is a visual development platform that enables creators to build custom web projects without having to hire developers. Ycode&apos;s mission is to make visual development as powerful as coding by hand—just faster and more accessible.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nanonets Table Extractor - 从任何文件中提取超强的表格]]></title><description><![CDATA[使用Nanonets的无代码表格提取器，可以节省从各种文档中提取表格数据的时间、精力和资源。自动捕捉任何 "类似表格 "的结构，提取整个表格或只提取特定单元格/行/列的数据。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nanonets-table-extractor</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nanonets-table-extractor</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 09:01:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Save time, effort &amp; resources&amp;nbsp;spent on extracting tabular data from all kinds of documents with Nanonets’ no-code table extractor. Automatically capture any “table-like” structure, extract entire tables or just pull data from specific cells/rows/columns.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Quarkly 2.0 - 在React上创建网站和网络应用的无代码平台]]></title><description><![CDATA[你是否一直在寻找一个无需代码的快速上市的React构建器，并在需要时进行深入控制？你是否对快速创建一个在图形用户界面和代码输入之间保持良好平衡的用户界面感兴趣？告诉你一个好消息--现在你可以使用Quarkly了。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/quarkly-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/quarkly-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 09:01:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Have you been searching for a no-code fast-to-market builder in React with in-depth controls when needed? Are you interested in quickly creating a UI with a good balance between GUI and code input? Good news for you — now you can use Quarkly.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WeWeb 2.0 - 唯一一个与后端无关的无代码前端构建器]]></title><description><![CDATA[WeWeb是建立生产就绪的网络应用程序的最快方式： - 连接多个数据源（如Airtable、REST APIs、XANO、PostgreSQL） - 可视化设计你的前端或添加自定义组件（vue.js / react） - 建立无代码工作流或添加自定义JS]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/weweb-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/weweb-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 09:01:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>WeWeb is the fastest way to build production-ready web apps: - connect multiple data sources (e.g. Airtable, REST APIs, XANO, PostgreSQL) - visually design your frontend or add custom components (vue.js / react) - build no-code workflows or add custom JS</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stytch - 现代应用的用户基础设施]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stytch是一个全堆栈认证和授权平台，其API使其能够简单地无缝地加入、认证和吸引用户。通过无密码，提高安全性和用户体验。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/stytch</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/stytch</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 08:49:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Stytch is a full stack authentication and authorization platform, whose APIs make it simple to seamlessly onboard, authenticate and engage users. Improve security and user experience by going passwordless.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bookstash - 在3分钟内获得顶级书籍的精髓]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bookstash是一个免费的图书馆，收录了顶级非小说类书籍的精选摘要。我们为你挑选一本书，并给你所有的关键想法，你可以保存你的最爱，以便以后跟踪你的阅读进度。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bookstash</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bookstash</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 08:18:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Bookstash is a free library of curated summaries from top nonfiction books. We pick a book for you and give you all the key ideas and you get to save your favorites for later &amp; track your reading progress.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Universal UI Kit (Web) v1.0 - 用于在Figma中创建网站的强大的Web UI组件]]></title><description><![CDATA[强大的 Web UI 套件，用于在 Figma 中创建登陆页面、网站和仪表板。使用我们的 UI 套件可节省数百个小时。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/universal-ui-kit-web-v1-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/universal-ui-kit-web-v1-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 08:18:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Powerful Web UI kit for creating landing pages, websites and dashboards in Figma. Save hundreds of hours with our UI Kit.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wannadocs - 知识库管理系统]]></title><description><![CDATA[为你的客户创建公共产品文档，或为你的团队创建内部知识库，所有这些都在同一个令人敬畏的用户界面中🖖。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/wannadocs</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/wannadocs</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 08:18:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Create public product docs for your customers or internal knowledge base for your team, all within the same awesome UI 🖖</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Founders' Book 2.0 - 世界上最大的创始人工具和资源库]]></title><description><![CDATA[创始人和创始团队在建立和扩大他们的想法方面的知识差距是真实的、昂贵的和耗时的。这种差距伤害了我们的想法、信心和雄心壮志! 因此，《创始人之书》支持他们的风险建设过程。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/founders-book-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/founders-book-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 07:48:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The knowledge gap in founders and founding teams to build on and scale their ideas is real, expensive and time-consuming. This gap hurt our ideas, confidence and ambition! Hence Founders’ Book to support their venture building process.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[OKR for Jira - 用OKRs使你的日常工作与公司战略保持一致]]></title><description><![CDATA[在Jira中管理你的OKRs的最佳方式。通过OKRs使你的日常工作与公司战略保持一致。通过在Jira中跟踪你的OKRs，关注真正重要的事情。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/okr-for-jira-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/okr-for-jira-2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 03:01:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Best way to manage your OKRs in Jira. Align your daily work to the company strategy with OKRs. Focus on what really matters by tracking your OKRs in Jira.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Clubs Poker - 让你的下一次公司活动成为在线扑克之夜]]></title><description><![CDATA[抛弃虚拟的欢乐时光，用Clubs Poker的新产品-->"For Companies "来举办一个扑克之夜 💚 只需将链接发送给你的同事，就可以开始游戏 💚 在桌子和牌上添加你公司的标志 💚 专门的活动主持（可选）]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/clubs-poker-for-companies</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/clubs-poker-for-companies</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 16:33:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Ditch the virtual happy hours and host a poker night instead with Clubs Poker&apos;s new product --&gt; &quot;For Companies&quot; 💚 Just send a link to your colleagues and start playing 💚 Add your company logo to the table and card decks 💚 Dedicated event host (optional)</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AltCoffee - 给人们提供一种用加密货币表示感谢的方式]]></title><description><![CDATA[这基本上是一个加密版本的请我喝咖啡。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/altcoffee</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/altcoffee</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 15:16:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>It&apos;s basically a crypto version of buy me a coffee.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Cold Start Problem - 一本关于如何启动和扩大网络效应的书]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据对Twitch、Tinder、Uber、Airbnb、Pinterest等公司创始团队的100次采访，陈志刚探讨了科技界最成功的公司是如何利用网络效应解决可怕的 "冷启动问题 "来启动和扩展的。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-cold-start-problem</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-cold-start-problem</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 14:33:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Based on 100s of interviews with founding teams at Twitch, Tinder, Uber, Airbnb, Pinterest, and many more, Andrew Chen explores how tech’s most successful companies solved the dreaded &quot;cold start problem” using network effects to launch and scale.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Link in Bio - 带视频的生物体内链接工具，内置无代码]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个页面上有你所有的视频链接。要求一个独特的URL并在你的简历中分享。添加你的链接，选择你的主题，你就可以开始了。所有这些都是在没有代码的情况下建立的。Webflow + Bubble在4周内完成。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/link-in-bio-1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/link-in-bio-1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 14:06:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>One page for all your links with a video. Claim a unique URL and share in your bio. Add your links, pick your theme and you&apos;re good to go. All built in no-code: Webflow + Bubble in 4 weeks.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Matrix Playground - 矩阵内部的一瞥]]></title><description><![CDATA[在Spline，我们喜欢Matrix，所以我们建立了一个有趣的辅助项目，供大家玩耍。你可以上传你的3D模型，使用网络摄像头看到自己在Matrix代码中的样子，并改变粒子的参数。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/matrix-playground</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/matrix-playground</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 13:35:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>At Spline, we love the Matrix so we built a fun side project for everyone to play around! You can upload your 3d models, see yourself inside Matrix code using the webcam, and change the parameters of the particles.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Patchstack - 给你的WordPress堆栈打补丁]]></title><description><![CDATA[监控您所有的WordPress网站，以防止我们的道德黑客社区发现安全漏洞。免费添加多达99个网站!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/patchstack</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/patchstack</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 12:54:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Monitor all your WordPress sites for security vulnerabilities found by our community of ethical hackers. Add up to 99 websites for free!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gentler - 通过了解你的活动水平来支持长期的健康状况]]></title><description><![CDATA[了解你的活动水平并让它们指导你的活动生活，可以降低疲劳、倦怠、受伤的几率。Gentler监测你的健身进展，并提示你放慢、加强或休息。它是个性化的，适合所有健身水平。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/gentler</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/gentler</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 11:48:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Knowing your activity levels and having them guide your active life lowers the chances of fatigue, burnout, injury. Gentler monitors your fitness progress and nudges you to slow down, step up, or rest. It is personalized, appropriate for all fitness levels.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The State of Customer Onboarding 2022 - 有史以来第一次关于客户入职空间的调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[100多位客户入职专业人士分享了他们预见的2022年的挑战、目标和趋势。点击 "获取"，下载您的《客户入职状况》报告副本。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-state-of-customer-onboarding-2022</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-state-of-customer-onboarding-2022</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 11:03:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>100+ customer onboarding professionals share the challenges, goals, and trends they foresee in 2022. Click ‘Get it’ to download your copy of The State of Customer Onboarding report.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CloudTalk for Mobile - 用于扩大销售和支持团队规模的呼叫软件]]></title><description><![CDATA[CloudTalk Go允许销售、支持和运营团队在办公室外使用WiFi或移动网络保持联系并专业地处理客户来电。可在iOS应用商店和Android Play商店购买。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/cloudtalk-for-mobile</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/cloudtalk-for-mobile</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 10:46:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>CloudTalk Go allows Sales, Support &amp; Operation teams to stay connected and professionally handle customer calls outside of the office using WiFi or mobile networks. Available on the iOS App Store and the Android Play Store.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenScout by Landscape - 为多家风险投资公司物色人才，推荐人可获得高达5万美元的奖金]]></title><description><![CDATA[通过OpenScout，投资者可以从精心挑选的星探那里获得各种交易信息。风险投资侦察员可以与整个投资者市场分享交易，并获得成功的费用（5千至5万美金！）。申请加入我们的邀请测试版，成为星探或投资者。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/openscout-by-landscape</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/openscout-by-landscape</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 10:46:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With OpenScout, investors can access diverse dealflow from handpicked scouts. Venture scouts can share deals with an entire marketplace of investors, and get paid a success fee ($5k-50k!). Apply to join as a scout or as an investor for our invite-only beta!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fathom - 再也不用在Zoom电话中做笔记了]]></title><description><![CDATA[Fathom在你的Zoom通话中只需点击一个按钮就能记录、转录和取代笔记，因此你可以简单地专注于手头的对话。通过电子邮件、Slack或发送到CRM的自动生成的摘要，轻松地与你的团队分享通话要点。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fathom-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fathom-2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 10:32:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Fathom records, transcribes, and replaces note taking with a click of a button on your Zoom calls, so you can simply focus on the conversation at hand. Easily share call highlights with your team via email, Slack, or auto-generated summaries sent to your CRM.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tailwind CSS Cheat Sheet - 在一个页面上来自Tailwind CSS的每一个类名]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一个页面上访问和搜索Tailwind CSS的每一个实用类，并加速你的开发过程。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tailwind-css-cheat-sheet</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tailwind-css-cheat-sheet</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 10:32:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Get access and search for every utility class from Tailwind CSS on a single page and accelerate your development process.</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>