<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Product Hunt 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Product Hunt 热门App，网站和产品]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 19:21:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Betts Connect - 招聘的未来是连接]]></title><description><![CDATA[通过利用十多年的招聘经验，我们创建了一个平台，缩短了招聘时间，节省了招聘费用。只需选择你要招聘的角色，通过配额和交易规模等关键绩效指标过滤候选人，并安排面试。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/betts-connect-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/betts-connect-2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 18:48:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>By leveraging over a decade of recruiting experience, we created a platform that reduces time to hire and saves money on recruiting fees. Simply choose the roles you’re hiring for, filter candidates by KPIs like quota and deal size, and schedule interviews.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[TryDraw - 通过即时反馈学习数字艺术]]></title><description><![CDATA[用我们的工具提高你的线条艺术和观察能力，突出你的错误。等待老师来纠正你的错误的日子已经一去不复返了。在简单的 "一步一步 "教程的指导下，你将按照自己的节奏学习。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/trydraw</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/trydraw</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 14:21:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Improve your line art and observational skills with our tool that highlights your mistakes. Gone are the days of waiting for a teacher to correct your mistakes. Get guided by simple STEP BY STEP tutorials that will teach you at your own pace.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PassThru - 一个基于电子邮件的票据存储应用程序 🎟]]></title><description><![CDATA[PassThru允许你在一个地方安全地存储和管理你的所有门票、优惠券和预订。不管是哪家票务供应商，它都能与每个系统配合使用。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/passthru</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/passthru</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 13:13:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>PassThru allows you to store and manage all your tickets, vouchers and reservations safely in one place. Regardless of the ticket provider; it works with every system.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PM vs PM Challenge - 你是一个项目经理还是一个产品经理？]]></title><description><![CDATA[那个怀疑你的内心声音--"我是PM吗？不，我是一名PM！" 这正是一个结束。但是如果你不愿意面对残酷的现实检查，请马上离开。不要告诉我们我们没有警告你。Jk会很有趣。或者会吗？]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pm-vs-pm-challenge</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pm-vs-pm-challenge</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 10:31:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>That inner voice doubting you - “Am I a PM? No, I am a PM!” This is an end to exactly that. But if you aren’t okay facing harsh reality checks, leave rn. Don’t tell us we didn’t warn you. Jk will be fun. Or will it? :P</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rebox - 你不知道你需要的回报服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[易于使用的设计，能够安排你的回报。我们重新设计了产品的退货方式，所以你不必这样做!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/rebox</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/rebox</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 10:31:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Easy to use design, Ability to schedule your returns. We reimagined how products should be returned, So you don&apos;t have to!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[100 Free Userpics - 为设计项目创建的免费头像]]></title><description><![CDATA[收集了一百个免费的用户图片，特别是为你的设计项目。每个头像都有圆形和方形两种格式。按您的意愿编辑图片，使其符合您的设计观点。完全矢量，与Figma兼容。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/100-free-userpics</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/100-free-userpics</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 10:09:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Collection of a hundred free userpics especially for your design projects. Each avatar is available in circle and square formats. Edit images as you wish to make them fit your view of design. Fully vector, compatible with Figma.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[HUENIT - 面向创客的AI相机和模块化机械臂]]></title><description><![CDATA[该机械臂，它具有人工智能视觉、语音识别、3D打印、激光雕刻、吸盘抓取器和笔工具。它也可以通过块状编码、python、Arduino C++或G代码进行编程。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/huenit</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/huenit</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 10:09:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The robotic arm which has AI vision, voice recognition, 3D printing, laser engraving, a suction grabber, and a pen tool. It can aslo be programmed via block coding, python, Arduino C++, or G-code.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Valuer - 向你自己的AI发现引擎问好]]></title><description><![CDATA[梳理数十万个全球数据点来寻找最具创新性的技术和公司听起来是否很性感？我们并不这么认为。这就是为什么我们开发了一个人工智能驱动的平台来为你做繁重的工作。基本上，我们使创新采购变得简单和个性化。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/valuer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/valuer</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 10:09:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Does combing through hundreds of thousands of global data points to find the most innovative technologies and companies sound sexy? We didn&apos;t think so. Which is why we have developed an AI-driven platform to do the heavy lifting for you. Basically, we make innovation sourcing easy and personal.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weekend Club 2.0 - 开拓者联合办公俱乐部打造盈利产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[由65位创业者组成的社区，共同启动和发展盈利的互联网企业。在我们的远程和IRL联合办公活动中与创始人会面，与大师们一起保持责任感，从内部导师那里学习，并通过100多个伟大的折扣节省开支。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/weekend-club-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/weekend-club-2-0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 10:09:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The community of 65+ bootstrapped founders launching &amp; growing profitable internet businesses together. Meet founders at our remote &amp; IRL co-working events, stay accountable with masterminds, learn from in-house mentors and save with 100+ great discounts.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GrowthPost - 从100多个活跃的新闻通讯中获得高增长的隐性工作机会]]></title><description><![CDATA[GrowthPost帮助你从顶级企业家、投资者撰写的利基通讯中发现100多个工作，这些人来自Sahil Bloom、Julian Shapiro、Greg Isenberg、Lenny等人。GrowthPost做所有繁琐的工作，并每周向你发送新工作的更新。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/growthpost</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/growthpost</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 09:13:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>GrowthPost helps you discover 100+ jobs from niche newsletters written by top Entrepreneurs, Investors from the likes of Sahil Bloom, Julian Shapiro, Greg Isenberg, Lenny, and many more. GrowthPost does all tedious work &amp; sends you weekly updates of new jobs.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Moonship Personalized AI Discounts - 个性化的人工智能折扣，为Shopify商店带来最大收益]]></title><description><![CDATA[Moonship使Shopify商户能够为对价格敏感的客户提供个性化的人工智能折扣，这些客户需要一个小小的推动力来购买。我们使用机器学习模型，使电子商户的销售额平均增加20%，最高可达80%。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/moonship-personalized-ai-discounts</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/moonship-personalized-ai-discounts</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 09:13:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Moonship enables Shopify merchants to offer personalized AI discounts to price sensitive customers who need a little nudge to buy. We use machine learning models to enable ecomm merchants to increase their sales by an average of 20% and as much as 80%.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nifty Generator - 生成你的NFT集合，无需代码]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nifty Generator让你生成具有不同特征的NFT集合，并为Solana或Ethereum提供完整的元数据--不需要编码。只需将你的图像层连接到我们的工具，我们就能处理好生成的问题。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nifty-generator</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nifty-generator</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 09:13:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Nifty Generator lets you generate NFT collections with different traits, complete with metadata for Solana or Ethereum—no coding needed. Just connect your image layers to our tool, and we’ll handle the generation!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Teamble - 在Slack & Teams上提供简单、持续和可操作的反馈]]></title><description><![CDATA[通过https://teamble.com，给予并获得👍简单、🔁连续和🎯可操作的反馈。在https://slack.com/apps/AS8DW2X44-teamble 和 https://teams.microsoft.com/l/app/ee7907e3-f0b3-4e18-b882-baa83e87812f 上无缝连接。利用强大的工具、模板和提示，在你的团队中建立一个持续的反馈文化。开始免费使用teamble。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/teamble</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/teamble</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 08:40:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Give and get 👍 simple, 🔁 continuous, and 🎯 actionable feedback with https://teamble.com. Seamlessly on https://slack.com/apps/AS8DW2X44-teamble and https://teams.microsoft.com/l/app/ee7907e3-f0b3-4e18-b882-baa83e87812f. Leverage powerful tools, templates, and nudges to build a continuous feedback culture in your team. Start using teamble for FREE.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lalo - 一个值得纪念的地方]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lalo是一个缅怀的平台。我们给你提供工具来讲述你所爱的人的故事。在一个安全、无广告的地方保存你的记忆。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/lalo</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/lalo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 05:16:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Lalo is a platform for remembrance. We give you the tools to tell the story of those you love. Preserve your memories in a safe, ad-free place.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Convert Menu - 将纸质菜单转换为在线QR菜单]]></title><description><![CDATA[自动将纸质菜单转换为数字QR菜单。只要上传你的（pdf）纸质菜单，剩下的就由我们来做。一份数字菜单应在32小时内准备好。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/convert-menu</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/convert-menu</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 22:47:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Automatically convert paper menus into a digital QR menu. Just upload your (pdf) paper menu and we do the rest. A digital menu should be ready within 32 hours.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PASSCARD - 简单、免费、离线的卡片密码保存器]]></title><description><![CDATA[PASSCARD是一个帮助你记住卡片密码的应用程序。该应用程序将密码离线安全地保存在你的设备上。该应用程序将永远不会保存或收集任何信息。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/passcard-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/passcard-2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 22:47:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>PASSCARD is an app that helps you to remember card passwords. The app saves passwords on your device offline and securely. The app will never save or collect any information.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Showping - 与朋友展示和购物，购物建议社交网络]]></title><description><![CDATA[Showping是你口袋里的口碑力量。Showping是一个独特的应用程序，你可以与朋友分享你的愿望和购买列表。在这个地方，人们可以阅读他们信任的人的评论，并通过屏幕共享一起进行购物。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/showping</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/showping</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 21:03:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Showping is the power of word of mouth in your pocket. Showping is a unique app where you can share your Wish and Bought list with friends. It&apos;s a place where people can read reviews from someone they trust and do shopping together through screen sharing.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Able: 28-Day Affirmation Plan - 个性化的每日积极肯定语]]></title><description><![CDATA[每日肯定有助于将你的心态转变为积极思考。获得一个为期28天的个性化计划，通过口头肯定你的梦想和抱负，将帮助你变得感激、有灵感、有内容，只是更快乐而已]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/able-28-day-affirmation-plan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/able-28-day-affirmation-plan</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 17:11:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Daily affirmations help shift your mindset to positive thinking. Get a personalized plan for 28 days that will help you become grateful, inspired, content, and just happier by verbally affirming your dreams and ambitions!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Snout - 电子邮件嗅探器和人与公司的社交网络。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Snout从嗅探互联网上的公共数据，努力寻找人们和公司的电子邮件和社交网络。找到客户、影响者、投资者、员工和更多。200+国家 ★ 57M+公司 ★ 800M+人 ★ 150M+电子邮件地址]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/snout</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/snout</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 14:31:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Snout works hard from sniffing public data on the internet to find emails and social networks of people and companies. Find customers, influencers, investors, employees and more. ★ 200+ Countries ★ 57M+ Companies ★ 800M+ people ★ 150M+ emails address</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Favelent - 创建一个你最喜欢的内容的画廊]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们想把你最喜欢的内容水晶化，并让你向世界展示它！这就是我们的目标。在你的听众要求推荐时，与他们分享你的简介。收集电子邮件并添加您的社会链接 发现他人的最佳发现。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/favelent</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/favelent</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 14:23:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We want to crystalize your most-favourite content and let you represent it to the world! Share your Profile with your audience whenever they ask for recommendations. Collect E-Mails and add your social links Discover the best findings of others.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[InSite - 在你的Shopify商店中添加一个收集反馈的小工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[Insite是一个强大而简单的工具，帮助您了解客户对您的要求。在5分钟内将一个定制的、优雅的反馈调查嵌入到您的网站。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/insite-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/insite-2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 13:31:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Insite is a powerful yet simple tool that helps you learn what your customers want from you. Embed a custom, elegant feedback survey into your website in under 5 minutes.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aguapro - 我们从顶级社区为初创企业寻找人才!]]></title><description><![CDATA[在 "产品 "和 "增长 "领域，从独家、独特和顶级的社区雇用积极的人才。利用复杂的技术，将工作要求与社区价值相一致，并与合适的申请人相匹配。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/aguapro</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/aguapro</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 12:52:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Hire motivated talent from the exclusive, distinct &amp; top communities in ‘product’ and ‘growth’ domain. Using sophisticated techniques, job requirements are aligned to community values and match with the right applicant.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Health Hub OS (Notion Template) - 一个用来管理所有与健康有关的事物的操作系统!]]></title><description><![CDATA[❤️一个带有+15个独特模板和+10个跟踪器的操作系统模板，帮助你在一个连接的枢纽中跟踪与健康有关的一切。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/health-hub-os-notion-template</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/health-hub-os-notion-template</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 11:23:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>❤️ An Operating System Template with +15 unique templates &amp; +10 trackers to help you track everything health-related in one connected Hub.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Authorizer - 开源认证和授权解决方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[Authorizer是一个开源的认证和授权解决方案，适用于你的应用程序。带上你的数据库，对用户信息有完全的控制。你可以自行托管授权器实例并连接到任何SQL数据库。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/authorizer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/authorizer</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 10:40:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Authorizer is an open-source authentication and authorization solution for your applications. Bring your database and have complete control over the user information. You can self-host authorizer instances and connect to any SQL database.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[lllook - 可定制的表情符号线图标集合]]></title><description><![CDATA[一组可定制的SVG表情符号线图标。在浏览器中直接调整颜色、大小和笔画宽度，然后使用SVG图标为你的设计添加一些有趣的小表情符号。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/lllook</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/lllook</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:16:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A collection of customizable SVG emoji line icons. Adjust the color, size and stroke width right in the browser, and then use the SVG icons to add some fun little expressive characters to your designs.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Porndora - 个性化的、由人工智能驱动的色情]]></title><description><![CDATA[Porndora是个性化的情色小说。我们使用人工智能来学习你喜欢的东西，并为每个用户建立一个个性化的快乐档案。我们正在建立一个成人网站，为每个人服务，无论其性别、性取向或癖好如何。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/porndora</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/porndora</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 20:36:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Porndora is personalized erotica. We use AI to learn what you like over time and build a personalized pleasure profile for every user. We’re building an adult site that works for everyone, regardless of gender, sexual orientation, or kink.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dash 6.0 - 即时离线访问200多个API文档集]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dash可以立即搜索200多个API的离线文档集，100多个小抄等。Dash也是一个代码片段管理器，支持使用缩写的片段扩展。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/dash-6-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/dash-6-0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:19:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Dash instantly searches offline documentation sets for 200+ APIs, 100+ cheat sheets and more. Dash is also a code snippet manager and supports snippet expansion using abbreviations.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fisio - 最佳在线简历生成器]]></title><description><![CDATA[Fisio简历生成器允许你用一个直观的工具快速、轻松地创建一个原创的简历。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fisio</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fisio</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:19:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Fisio resume builder allows you to create an original resule quickly and easily with an intuitive tool.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GTD Dashboard - 一体化的仪表板来完成事情]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个全面的Notion仪表盘，帮助你节省时间，完成更多工作。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/gtd-dashboard</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/gtd-dashboard</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:19:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A comprehensive Notion dashboard that helps you save time, and get more done.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[InstaaSnap - 保存Instagram的公共帖子和卷轴，开源节流]]></title><description><![CDATA[InstaaSnap是一个开源的Instagram帖子保存器API、WebApp、iOS和Andoid应用。我创建它是为了保存Instagram上的一些重要信息。它是隐私友好的，没有数据库，没有分析，没有日志，没有cookies，加上开源的。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/instaasnap</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/instaasnap</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:19:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>InstaaSnap is a open-source Instagram post saver API, WebApp, iOS and Andoid app. I created it to save some important feeds from Instagram. It&apos;s Privacy-friendly, no database, no analytics, no logs, no cookies, plus open-source.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Passky - Passky是一个简单、现代和开源的密码管理器]]></title><description><![CDATA[Passky是一个简单、现代、轻便、开源和安全的密码管理器。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/passky-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/passky-2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:19:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Passky is a simple, modern, lightweight, open-source and secure password manager.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[W3Schools Spaces - 用W3Schools Spaces建立您自己的网站]]></title><description><![CDATA[W3Schools允许你创建自己的网站并与他人分享。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/w3schools-spaces</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/w3schools-spaces</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:19:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>W3Schools allows you to create your own website and share it with others.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Office Club Illustration pack - 观念式的艺术指导和插图]]></title><description><![CDATA[无论你是创建一个网站或移动应用程序，展示一个投资组合，发布一个博客，还是一个电子商务商店 - Office Club的100幅插图和设计的艺术指导帮助你创造最好的产品。现场：https://overflow.design/]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/office-club-illustration-pack</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/office-club-illustration-pack</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 10:45:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Whether you’re creating a website or mobile app, showcasing a portfolio, publishing a blog, or an e-commerce store — Office Club’s 100 illustrations and designed art directions help you create the best possible products. Live: https://overflow.design/</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ultimate Free Trial Card - 帮助你获得免费试用的虚拟卡]]></title><description><![CDATA[使用Zerobalance虚拟卡进行所有的免费试用注册，永远不用担心被收费或取消。探索我们的100多个不同类别的免费试用库，无忧无虑地享受所有的好处。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ultimate-free-trial-card</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ultimate-free-trial-card</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 10:35:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Use Zerobalance virtual cards for all your Free-Trial Signups and never worry about getting charged or cancellations. Explore our library of 100+ free trials across different categories and enjoy all the benefits without a worry.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jobstack - 寻找工作。变得简单。]]></title><description><![CDATA[构建你的求职过程。📈 带有15个以上模板的个人简历生成器 😃 带有3000个以上入围资料的简易网络指南 ✍🏻 准备使用超过16个角色的个人CRM]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/jobstack</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/jobstack</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 09:32:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Structure your job search process: 📈 Personal Resume Builder with 15+ templates 😃 Easy Networking Guides with 3000+ shortlisted profiles ✍🏻 Ready to use Personal CRM for over 16 roles</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ExplodingCommunities - 发现增长最快的在线社区]]></title><description><![CDATA[ExplodingCommunites是一个拥有Reddit上增长最快的在线社区的数据库，可以支撑你的下一个业务。它帮助你尽早发现趋势性社区，发现隐藏的商业机会，并建立基于社区的产品。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/explodingcommunities</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/explodingcommunities</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 22:47:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>ExplodingCommunites is a database with the fastest-growing online communities on Reddit that can sustain your next business. It helps you discover trending communities early, uncover hidden business opportunities, and build community-based products.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenIn 3 - 自定义MacOS中的链接和文件打开方式]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenIn帮助你管理Mac上的链接和文件的打开方式。对于每个链接，你可以从多个浏览器、邮件客户端或应用程序中选择文件，或根据文件或链接的打开位置，或根据位置或域进行配置。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/openin-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/openin-3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 22:47:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>OpenIn helps you manage how links and files open on your Mac. For every link, you can select from multiple browsers, mail clients or apps for files, or configure based on where the file or link is opened, or based on location or domain.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Notion Travel Template - 清楚地旅行。]]></title><description><![CDATA[🙅🏽♀️忘记电子表格、电子邮件、订票网站和一打杂乱的硬盘或有限的云存储的文件。💻使用这个Notion旅行模板，把所有东西都放在一个地方，旅行时从杂乱无章到清晰明了。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/notion-travel-template</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/notion-travel-template</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 19:01:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>🙅🏽‍♀️ Forget spreadsheets, e-mails, booking sites and a dozen documents cluttering your hard drives or limited cloud storage. 💻 Use this Notion travel template to everything in one place and move from clutter to clarity when travelling.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[defly.ai - 以太坊费用优化器]]></title><description><![CDATA[你可能听说过，甚至经历过因为交易失败而损失以太坊交易费的痛苦。defly.ai使用实时区块链数据和Spice.ai机器学习，进行最安全的AI驱动的估计，在使用Uniswap时挽救损失的费用。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/defly-ai</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/defly-ai</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 17:10:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>You may have heard of or even experienced the pain of losing your Ethereum transaction fee because your trade failed. defly.ai uses real-time blockchain data &amp; Spice.ai machine learning for the safest AI-powered estimates to save lost fees when using Uniswap.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Job Search Journey - 带有帮助求职者的工具的数字市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[找工作不一定很困难。在世界第一个职业市场上找到由获奖的简历作家和职业专家设计的模板和脚本。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/job-search-journey</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/job-search-journey</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 14:31:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Job searching doesn&apos;t have to be hard. Find templates and scripts designed by award-winning resume writers and career experts on the world&apos;s first career marketplace.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[High Signal - 每周与成功的创始人通话]]></title><description><![CDATA[High Signal是一个为创始人创造收入的小型社区。我们每周都会在Zoom通话，以分享我们的进展，讨论我们的目标，并在我们遇到困难时获得帮助。我们也有一个Telegram群组来分享建议。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/high-signal</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/high-signal</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 13:33:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>High Signal is a small community for founders making revenue. We meet for Zoom calls every week in order to share our progress, talk through our goals and get help when we get stuck. We also have a Telegram group for sharing advice.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[glyde - 最时尚、最酷、最快速的报税方式]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们在手机上做任何事情，为什么不在税务上做呢？有了Glyde，你可以预先将收入、扣除额、税收抵免、银行账户等信息填入你的ITR，从你的经纪人和投资平台导入交易以及更多。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/glyde-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/glyde-3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 13:33:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>we do everything on our phones, so why not taxes too? with glyde, you can pre-fill your ITR with incomes, deductions, tax credits, bank accounts. import trades from your broker and investment platform &amp; much more. save, pay, file &amp; track taxes with a few taps.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lofly - 用LOFI节拍和大自然的声音提高生产力]]></title><description><![CDATA[欣赏带有自然声音的Lofi节拍。从17种以上的自然声音和17种以上的Lo-fi曲目中选择。用Pomodoro提高你的工作效率并保持有序。享受与成员聊天的乐趣。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/lofly</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/lofly</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 12:27:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Enjoy lofi beats with nature sounds. Choose from 17+ nature sounds and 17+ lo-fi tracks. Increase your productivity and stay organized with Pomodoro. Enjoy chatting with members and have fun.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kizie for Twitter - 一个更干净、更好的方式来浏览Twitter]]></title><description><![CDATA[介绍一下Kizie，一个浏览Twitter的新方式 ✨ 更干净，更好，无广告的主页和简介时间线 ⚡️ 专业功能，可以用twitter做更多事情（阅读第一条评论的清单👇） 㱮在网页和PWA上工作 👉试试吧：https://kizie.co]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/kizie-for-twitter</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/kizie-for-twitter</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 11:49:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Introducing Kizie, a new way to browse Twitter 🐤 ✨ cleaner, better, ad-free home and profile timelines ⚡️ pro features to do more with twitter(read first comment for the list 👇) 📱 works on web and as PWA 👉 try it: https://kizie.co</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PlainAdmin - 开源的多用途仪表板模板]]></title><description><![CDATA[PlainAdmin是一个开源免费的基于Bootstrap 5的vanilla JS多用途管理模板，它包含了所有基本的仪表盘组件、页面、UI元素、图表、图形、库和所有你可能需要的数据丰富的后台。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/plainadmin</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/plainadmin</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 11:22:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>PlainAdmin is an Open-source freemium Bootstrap 5 based vanilla JS multipurpose admin template comes with - all essential dashboard components, pages, UI elements, charts, graphs, libraries and everything you may need for a data-rich backends.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sandpack by CodeSandbox - 用于在浏览器中构建实时编码体验的工具包]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sandpack是一个工具包，用于构建完全在浏览器中运行的实时编码体验。全功能的编辑器体验 ✨ 闪电般快速的浏览器捆绑器 ✨ 直接与CodeSandbox集成]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sandpack-by-codesandbox</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sandpack-by-codesandbox</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 11:07:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Sandpack is a toolkit for building live coding experiences that run fully in the browser. ✨ Full-featured editor experience ✨ Lightning-fast browser bundler ✨ Direct CodeSandbox integration</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[LeadStory - 有地理标记的新闻，在发生的地方和时间观看故事]]></title><description><![CDATA[在新闻雷达地图上关注突发新闻报道。观看你感兴趣的或你关心的地方的新闻。完全控制你从哪里得到你的新闻。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/leadstory</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/leadstory</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 10:35:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Follow breaking news stories on News Radar map. Watch news that you&apos;re interested in or in places you care about. Take complete control over where you get your news from.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reachfluencer - 用于LinkedIn、Twitter、Medium和Quora的参与舱]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://reachfluencer.com/，帮助企业家和创客建立一个参与和活跃的社区。👋 邀请你网络中认识的人 ✍️ 在LinkedIn、Twitter、Medium或Quora上发布内容 📋 在你的网络中粘贴内容URL 🔥 自动获得几十个赞!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/reachfluencer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/reachfluencer</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 10:16:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>https://reachfluencer.com/ helps entrepreneurs and makers to build an engaged and active community. 👋 Invite people you know in your network ✍️ Post content on LinkedIn, Twitter, Medium or Quora 📋 Paste content URL in your network 🔥 Get dozens of likes automatically!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thundra Foresight V2 - 用Foresight监控和调试你的CI管道和测试]]></title><description><![CDATA[用Foresight监控和调试你的CI管道和测试。同时监控你所有的CI工作流程和测试！通过访问关键的CI指标，深入了解你所有的CI工作流程和测试。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/thundra-foresight-v2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/thundra-foresight-v2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 09:32:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Monitor and Debug your CI Pipelines &amp; Tests with Foresight.Monitor all of your CI Workflows &amp; Tests at the same time!Gain Insight into your all CI Workflows and tests by accessing key CI metrics.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[100 UI/UX Tips - 让你的界面更完美的技巧集锦]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个让你的用户界面变得更好的 "应做 "和 "不做 "的集合。100页=100条提示。几乎每个提示都有一个插图，其中一些还有指向外部资源的附加链接。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/100-ui-ux-tips</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/100-ui-ux-tips</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 09:16:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>This is a collection of Dos and Dont&apos;s for making your UI better. 100 pages = 100 tips. Almost every tip has an illustration, some of them have additional links to external resources.</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>