<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Product Hunt 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Product Hunt 热门App，网站和产品]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 13:29:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Fanalyze Voice - SIRI用于NFL橄榄球幻想和体育投注数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[你所有的NFL幻想或体育投注问题的SIRI。通过语音或文字输入询问有关NFL统计数据、球员和球队信息、大/小球预测、赔率等问题。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fanalyze-voice</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fanalyze-voice</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 13:06:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The SIRI for all your NFL Fantasy or sports betting questions. Ask questions about NFL statistics, player and team info, over/under predictions, odds, and more through your voice or text input.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[nuka - 你将购买的最后一台笔记本]]></title><description><![CDATA[嗨，这是nuka.me! BBC专题报道和3次reddot奖的永恒文具 可重复使用的笔记本和永无止境的铅笔 它配备了一个应用程序，将手写变成数字 10月开始发货 目前已售罄 6500/6500 https://nuka.me/buy/，价格为-30%，2月获得一个]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nuka</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nuka</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 12:10:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Hi, it&apos;s nuka.me! BBC featured &amp; 3 times reddot awarded eternal stationery Reusable notebook &amp; never-ending pencil It comes with an app that turns handwriting into digital Shipping started Oct. Currently sold out 6500/6500 https://nuka.me/buy/ with -30%, get one in Feb</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Typewise Text Prediction API (Beta) - 在你的软件中添加谷歌风格的智能撰写]]></title><description><![CDATA[使用Typewise API（Beta）在几分钟内将先进的文本预测和自动更正AI添加到您的软件或平台： 🤖 下一个单词和句子预测 🔤 自动更正（-75%的错字） 🌎 语言检测 😵 表情符号搜索 🔒 100%隐私，在🇨🇭制造]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/typewise-text-prediction-api-beta</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/typewise-text-prediction-api-beta</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 10:47:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Add advanced text prediction and autocorrect AI to your software or platform in minutes with Typewise API (Beta): 🤖 Next-word and sentence prediction 🔤 Autocorrection (-75% typos) 🌎 Language Detection 😵‍ Emoji Search 🔒 100% Privacy, made in 🇨🇭</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pioneer 3.0 - 创始人的家在第0天]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们将在先锋计划中增加一个新的选项。除了成为先锋的所有现有好处外，你的公司有2%的投资。我们还将增加一个为期一个月的硅谷之旅，与其他创始人一起。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pioneer-3-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pioneer-3-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 10:17:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We’re adding a new option to the Pioneer offer: 2% of your company for a $20k investment, in addition to all the existing benefits of becoming a Pioneer. We&apos;re also adding a monthlong trip to Silicon Valley with fellow founders.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Virtual Event Chat Kit - 用于建立应用内虚拟活动聊天的UI工具包和示例应用程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[100多个精心设计的屏幕凝聚成映射出的流程，因此您和您的团队可以跳入Figma，比以往任何时候都更快地创建您自己的定制活动聊天。示例应用程序显示了Stream的聊天API，该API也可免费用于个人使用和小型项目，为后端提供支持。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/virtual-event-chat-kit</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/virtual-event-chat-kit</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 10:00:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>100+ polished screens coalesce into mapped-out flows so you and your team can jump into Figma and create your own custom event chat faster than ever. The sample app shows Stream&apos;s chat API, also free for personal use and small projects, powering the backend.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021 Looped - 关于2021年，你的日历怎么说？]]></title><description><![CDATA[好奇地想知道你是如何在工作中花费时间的？2021年的Looped对你的日历年进行了汇总，并产生了独特的见解，如在会议中花费的时间，会见的人数以及其他一些很酷的统计。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/2021-looped</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/2021-looped</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:48:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Curious to know how you spend your time at work? 2021 Looped rounds up your calendar year and generates unique insights like time spent in meetings, the number of people met along with some other cool stats.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Detail 2 - 简单的电影式视频]]></title><description><![CDATA[用你的Mac录制和流传高质量的视频。通过场景、多镜头和自动取景，将你的 Mac 变成一个制作室。细节可与你的 iPhone、iPad、内置网络摄像头或任何其他摄像头一起使用。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/detail-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/detail-2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:48:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Record and stream high-quality video with your Mac. Turn your Mac into a production studio with Scenes, multi-cam, and auto framing. Detail works with your iPhone, iPad, built-in webcam, or any other camera.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Multiversial - 科技和商业新闻变得更聪明的西班牙语日报]]></title><description><![CDATA[MultiVersial是一份每日通讯，以西班牙语提供最新的科技商业信息。语言仍然是获取知识的一个障碍。一份有趣而简单的通讯，让你在5分钟内掌握最新信息，了解科技战略，实现专业成长。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/multiversial</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/multiversial</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:16:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>MultiVersial is a daily newsletter with the latest in tech business in Spanish. Languages are still a barrier to accessing knowledge. A fun and simple newsletter that allows you to stay up to date, understand tech strategy, and grow professionally in 5 mins</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Opal C1 - 第一个帮助你看起来更好的专业网络摄像机。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们正在为那些与他们的工作--他们的团队、员工、客户--的主要联系是通过视频通话的人建立Opal。我们希望通过一个即插即用的系统，让每个人都能轻松拥有专业的设置。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/opal-c1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/opal-c1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:16:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We’re building Opal for anyone who’s primary connection to their job – their team, their employees, their customers – is through video calls. We want to make it easy for everyone to have a professional setup, with a single plug and play system.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Face Swapper - 免费交换面孔，前所未有]]></title><description><![CDATA[忘记那些来自图片库的过度使用的面孔。忘掉有不适当许可证的照片。改变面孔或身体，在广告、电子商务、社交媒体、教育、光鲜的杂志等方面使用它们。卓越的质量。无与伦比的分辨率。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/face-swapper</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/face-swapper</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:01:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Forget about overused faces from stock photos. Forget about photos with an inappropriate license. Change faces or bodies and use them in ads, e-commerce, social media, education, glossy magazines, etc. Exceptional quality. Unrivaled resolution.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ripple - 掌控你的情绪，赢得一天，每一天]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ripple是一款情绪跟踪应用程序，通过摆脱焦虑、抑郁和毒性，帮助人们改善心理健康。只要在1到10的范围内选择你的满意度和能量水平。Ripple将翻译你的情绪，并将其转化为文字!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ripple-13</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ripple-13</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:01:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Ripple is a mood tracking app that helps people improve their mental health by getting rid of anxiety, depression, and toxicity. Just choose your satisfaction and energy level on a scale of 1 to 10. Ripple will translate your emotions and put them into words!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AutoCloud - 自动化的三维云基础设施图和洞察力]]></title><description><![CDATA[对于在AWS、Azure和GCP上运行工作负载的人来说，AutoCloud可以自动绘制架构图，进行合规性检查和漂移检测。使用3D环境或通过查询GraphQL端点来探索洞察力。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/autocloud</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/autocloud</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 08:48:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>For anyone running workloads on AWS, Azure, and GCP, AutoCloud automates architecture diagrams, compliance checks, and drift detection. Explore insights using a 3D environment or by querying a GraphQL endpoint.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Magic Sidebar by BlackMagic.so - 为Twitter提供强大的增强体验]]></title><description><![CDATA[Magic Sidebar是Twitter的最佳浏览器扩展。今天就使用它，解开你从不知道的见解，与你的受众更好地沟通，并建立强大的1：1关系。也可使用iOS和Android的移动应用程序!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/magic-sidebar-by-blackmagic-so</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/magic-sidebar-by-blackmagic-so</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 08:36:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Magic Sidebar is the best browser extension for Twitter. Use it today and unlock insights you never knew about, communicate better with your audience, and build strong 1:1 relationships. Mobile apps for iOS and Android are also available!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Creativity Booster by Alpe Audio - 为你的教学和内容寻找故事和例子]]></title><description><![CDATA[不再有写作障碍。不要一直纠结于如何打开你的课程、文章或视频。自动生成伟大的开场钩子、故事和相关的例子，涉及你想教的或想写的任何东西!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/creativity-booster-by-alpe-audio</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/creativity-booster-by-alpe-audio</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 23:28:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>No more writers block. Don&apos;t stay stuck wondering how to open your lesson, article or video. Automatically generate great opening hooks, stories and relevant examples about anything you want to teach or write about!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Christmas Design Assets by Iconfinder - 免费的节日图标、插图和动画]]></title><description><![CDATA[用这些节日的好东西洒在你的季节性内容上。小精灵们来了，他们带来了充满设计资产的圣诞赠品，非常适合你的节日通讯、简报和社交媒体帖子。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/christmas-design-assets-by-iconfinder</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/christmas-design-assets-by-iconfinder</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 16:02:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Sprinkle up your seasonal content with these festive goodies. Here come the elves with a Christmas freebie full of design assets that are perfect for your holiday newsletters, presentations &amp; social media posts.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[HiHo - 具有无限线程的异步视频讨论区]]></title><description><![CDATA[HiHo是一个面对面的社交应用程序，用于认识有趣的人并进行精彩的视频对话。通过异步回复和无限线程，每个人都可以在任何时间参与。该应用程序既提供公共论坛，也提供私人DMs。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hiho</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hiho</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 16:02:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>HiHo is a face-forward social app for meeting interesting people and having great video conversations. With asynchronous replies and infinite threading, everyone can participate at any time. The app offers both public forums as well as private DMs.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CommerceBooster - 一个用于电子商务的开源B2B UI模板]]></title><description><![CDATA[CommerceBooster是第一个开源的B2B电子商务的UI模板。它可以在Figma社区免费使用，并针对commercetools和Vue Storefront进行了优化。它实际上为任何开始B2B电子商务项目的人节省了几个月的工作。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/commercebooster</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/commercebooster</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 15:52:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>CommerceBooster is the first open-source, UI template for B2B eCommerce. It’s available for free on the Figma Community and optimized for commercetools and Vue Storefront. It literally saves months of work for anyone starting B2B eCommerce projects.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Carrot - 你的所有购物，像魔术一样组织起来]]></title><description><![CDATA[无法跟踪你想买的东西？认识一下Carrot，这个扩展可以在你购物时自动收集你的购物车。你可以通过点击回到产品上，创建可分享和可赠送的收藏，获得降价提醒，而且完全免费！这就是Carrot。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/carrot-4400273f-0d5e-4a81-a978-0f2477a39ad6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/carrot-4400273f-0d5e-4a81-a978-0f2477a39ad6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 13:14:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Can’t keep track of the stuff you want to buy? Meet Carrot, the extension that automatically collects your carts as you shop. You can get back to products with a click, create shareable and gift-able collections, get price drop alerts, and it&apos;s totally free!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pilot - 远程团队的薪资、福利和合规性]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pilot为拥有远程团队的美国公司提供薪资、福利和合规性。轻松地在160多个国家的员工和240多个国家的承包商入职和付款。为Product Hunt用户提供特殊价格： pilot.co/producthunt]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pilot-8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pilot-8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 12:55:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Pilot provides payroll, benefits, and compliance for US-based companies with remote teams. Easily onboard and pay employees in 160+ countries and contractors in 240+ countries. Offering special pricing for Product Hunt users: pilot.co/producthunt</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Battle of Mars - 一个玩家与玩家之间的NFT游戏]]></title><description><![CDATA[火星之战是一个PVP的NFT游戏，你可以挑战对方，把对手的火星人带走。1. 铸造一个火星人（有10,000个独特的火星人） 2. 加入一个加密派别 3. 挑战朋友并夺走他们的火星人]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-battle-of-mars</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-battle-of-mars</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 10:16:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The Battle of Mars is a PVP NFT game where you can challenge each other and take your opponent&apos;s Martian away. 1. Mint a Martian (10,000 unique martians available) 2. Join a crypto faction 3. Challenge a friend and take their Martian away</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pretty Progress - 在你的iPhone主屏幕上有漂亮的倒计时小工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[漂亮的进度允许你在你的iPhone主屏幕上添加漂亮的个性化的倒计时和进度条部件。在你每天使用的设备上跟踪并提醒自己重要的事情。清晰而方便。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pretty-progress</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pretty-progress</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 10:16:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Pretty Progress allows you to add beautiful &amp; personalized Countdown &amp; Progress Bar widgets on your iPhone&apos;s Home Screen. Track and remind yourself about the important things on the device you use every day. Clear and convenient.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Adobe Creative Cloud Express - 快速、轻松地制作社交图形和更多]]></title><description><![CDATA[Creative Cloud Express（以前的Adobe Spark）使您可以轻松地开始使用数以千计的精美模板，以及用于社交媒体内容、标志和更多的资产。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/adobe-creative-cloud-express</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/adobe-creative-cloud-express</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 10:01:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Creative Cloud Express (formerly Adobe Spark) makes it easy to get started with thousands of beautiful templates, plus assets for social media content, logos, and more.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Albert - 在Slack上为你的团队提高网络安全意识]]></title><description><![CDATA[艾伯特通过Slack向你的团队传授网络安全基础知识。这些课程很短，为每个员工动态定制，具有互动性，并且全年发送。这就是为什么你的团队会喜欢它。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/albert-5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/albert-5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 09:48:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Albert teaches cybersecurity basics to your team over Slack. The courses are short, dynamically customized for each employee, interactive, and sent all year long. That&apos;s why your team will love it.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tella for Chrome - 在Chrome浏览器的任何地方都能录制精彩的视频]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tella for Chrome，屏幕和相机记录器，让你的工作看起来很棒。在Chrome浏览器的任何地方录制完全可定制的、可立即分享的视频。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tella-for-chrome</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tella-for-chrome</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 09:31:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Tella for Chrome, the screen and camera recorder that makes your work look great. Record fully customisable, instantly shareable videos from anywhere in Chrome.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Around 3.0 - 为你的下一个快乐时光提供带有音乐和游戏的视频通话]]></title><description><![CDATA[Around独特的视频通话旨在帮助混合远程团队一起创造、协作和庆祝。现在还配有音乐和游戏，以促进团队的团结和联系。在你的下一个快乐时光或联合办公会议上试试吧。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/around-3-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/around-3-0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:47:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Around&apos;s radically unique video calls are designed to help hybrid-remote teams create, collaborate and celebrate together. Now comes with music and games for team bonding and connection. Try it for your next happy hour or co-working session.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Smart VC Search by Unicorn Nest - 为你的创业公司提供免费的独特的相关风险投资商名单]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们建立了一个算法，分析38000个风险投资基金的历史数据，为初创企业推荐相关的投资者（种子期、A轮、B轮和C轮）。填写调查问卷 ➡️获得一份VC名单（包括决策者） ➡️立即开始投资者推广 🚀]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/smart-vc-search-by-unicorn-nest</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/smart-vc-search-by-unicorn-nest</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:47:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We&apos;ve built an algorithm that analyses historical data of 38,000 VC funds and suggests relevant investors for startups (seed, round A, B and C). Fill in the questionnaire ➡️ Get a list of VCs (incl. decision makers) ➡️ Start investor outreach immediately 🚀</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ZeroBlur - 模糊敏感信息，自信地分享屏幕]]></title><description><![CDATA[ZeroBlur是一个100%免费的Chrome扩展，可以快速模糊敏感信息。在提供产品演示或销售电话时，不再担心敏感数据的泄露。只需点击几下，你就能模糊任何网络应用或网站的任何元素或页面区域。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zeroblur</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zeroblur</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:47:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>ZeroBlur is a 100% free Chrome extension to quickly blur sensitive information. Stop worrying about leaking sensitive data when delivering a product demo or a sales call. In few clicks you&apos;ll be able to blur any element or page area of any web app or website.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trivia Game Center - 在你的浏览器中通过团队游戏为你的工作增添乐趣]]></title><description><![CDATA[你难道不讨厌你的周一忧郁症在周五晚上结束吗？别担心! 在实时小组电话中与你的团队一起玩猜谜和猜字游戏，并与你的团队进行虚拟的联系。不需要安装! 打开你的浏览器，准备好享受一些乐趣吧 🎉。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/trivia-game-center-1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/trivia-game-center-1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Don’t you hate it when your Monday blues end on Friday nights? Fret not! Play Quizzes and Pictionary with your team in real-time group calls and bond with your team virtually. No installation required! Fire up your browsers and get ready to have some fun 🎉</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Unicorns to the Moon - 像越共一样玩这个充满行动力的桌面游戏]]></title><description><![CDATA[独角兽登月》是一款动作类桌面游戏，将你成为炙手可热的风险投资家（VC）的梦想变成了现实 你作为风险投资家的工作是什么？投资独角兽公司，并将它们送上月球。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/unicorns-to-the-moon</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/unicorns-to-the-moon</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 02:48:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Unicorns To The Moon is an action-packed tabletop game that turns your dreams of being a hotshot venture capitalist (VC) into a reality! Your job as a VC? Invest in unicorn companies, and send them to the moon.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PodBuddy - 从你的播客中制作一口大小的社交媒体视频剪辑]]></title><description><![CDATA[PodBuddy将你的播客集做成动画视频，非常适合在社交媒体上分享。创建一个动画帖子只需几秒钟。只需选择你的播客集片段，PodBuddy就会根据你的播客作品创建一个帖子。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/podbuddy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/podbuddy</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:34:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>PodBuddy makes animated videos from your podcast episode, perfect for sharing on social media. It takes seconds to create an animated post. Simply pick your podcast episode clip and PodBuddy will create a post based on your podcast&apos;s artwork.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spatial - NFT画廊和展览的Metaverse]]></title><description><![CDATA[空间是文化的元空间，在这里我们可以一起体验一键式NFT画廊和展览。创作者、收藏家和品牌可以在网络、移动和VR上免费举办美丽的沉浸式体验。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/spatial-4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/spatial-4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:34:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Spatial is the metaverse for culture, where we can all experience one-click NFT galleries &amp; exhibitions together. Creators, collectors &amp; brands can host beautiful immersive experiences across web, mobile, and VR for free.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[OnPodium - 播客网站，吸引并扩大你的听众群]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是我去年推出的Podsite项目的继承者。我们正在根据现有客户的反馈，不断改进OnPodium。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/onpodium</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/onpodium</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:46:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>This is a successor of my previous project Podsite that was launched last year. We’re constantly improving OnPodium according to the feedback we get from existing customers.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[First 1000 Users Guide - 从构思到第一个1000个用户的互动指南]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个完全互动的指南，在1个月内从构思到1000个用户！由大量来自科技界人士的资源组成。由保罗-格雷厄姆和莱尼-拉奇茨基等科技人士提供的大量资源组成，以及一个互动界面，你可以记录并从你的发现中学习!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/first-1000-users-guide</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/first-1000-users-guide</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 14:25:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A fully interactive guide on going from ideation to 1000 users within 1 month! Composed of tons of resources from tech figures like Paul Graham and Lenny Rachitsky, as well as an interactive interface where you can record and learn from your findings!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GitHub Wrapped - 你的代码年]]></title><description><![CDATA[你在2021年写了很多代码--提交、拉动请求和评论。反思你的这一年，你所贡献的项目，以及你所支持的开发者。开放源代码。在Twitter上分享或添加到你的个人Readme。由Neat的团队制作。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/github-wrapped-4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/github-wrapped-4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 14:01:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>You coded a lot in 2021 - commits, pull requests, and reviews. Reflect on your year, the projects you contributed to, and the developers you supported. Open source. Share on Twitter or add to your personal Readme. Made by the team at Neat.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How much is your SaaS worth? - 由463项近期交易提供的SaaS估值计算器]]></title><description><![CDATA[你应该得到一个更高的估值。现在你有数据来获得它。利用我们的实时洞察力，确保你得到你的价值。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/how-much-is-your-saas-worth</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/how-much-is-your-saas-worth</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 14:01:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>You deserve a higher valuation. Now you have the data to get it. Use our real-time insights to make sure you get what you’re worth.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zen Flowchart 2.0 - 创建流程图的最简单工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[Zen Flowchart是最简单的流程图制作工具。受到全球160万用户的喜爱。从头开始重建的新的强大功能。- 实时协作 - 更多的流程图形状 - 更干净和更快的用户界面 - 图标 - 自定义颜色]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zen-flowchart-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zen-flowchart-2-0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 13:06:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Zen Flowchart is the simplest flowchart maker. Loved by 1.6M users worldwide. Rebuilt from scratch with new powerful features: - Live Collaboration - More flowchart shapes - Cleaner &amp; faster UI - Icons - Custom colors</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PocketTube 3.0 - 一个全新的YouTube体验]]></title><description><![CDATA[PocketTube是一种全新的YouTube体验。管理和分类您的订阅，创建群组，使用自动标签，标记为已观看，毫不费力地过滤您的视频源，所有这些都在YouTube自己的界面中。可用于您的浏览器]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pockettube-3-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pockettube-3-0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 12:45:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>PocketTube is a brand new YouTube experience. Manage and sort your subscriptions, create groups, use auto tags, mark as watched, filter your video feed effortlessly, all its within YouTube&apos;s own interface. Available for your browser</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Customer Service Tips by LabiDesk - 50多个针对初创企业的免费客户服务技巧]]></title><description><![CDATA[50多个客户服务技巧! 我们把共同的规则和最佳做法放在一起，这些规则和最佳做法帮助许多公司在他们的客户服务组织方式以及他们如何处理每一个客户支持查询的帮助下成长。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/customer-service-tips-by-labidesk</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/customer-service-tips-by-labidesk</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 11:46:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>50+ Customer Service Tips! We put together a list of common rules and best practices that helped so many companies grow with the help of the way their customer service was organized and how they handled each and every customer support inquiry.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sales Automation Playbook by NetHunt CRM - 通过全面的销售自动化演练来完成工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[把它想象成一本销售自动化的食谱。它一步一步地引导你完成所有销售流程的自动化，从售前到售后；为什么、何时以及我们应该如何利用它。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sales-automation-playbook-by-nethunt-crm</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sales-automation-playbook-by-nethunt-crm</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 11:16:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Picture this as a cookbook for sales automation. Step-by-step, it walks you through automation for all your sales processes, from pre-sale to post-sale; why, when, and how we should utilize it.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Triage 2 - 为您的收件箱提供急救服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[Triage是对那些努力保持收件箱顶部的人的急救措施。它并不试图取代传统的电子邮件软件，而是让你利用你的停机时间来迅速消除噪音和压力。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/triage-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/triage-2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 11:16:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Triage is first aid for people who struggle to stay on top of their inbox. It doesn’t try to replace traditional email software, but lets you use your downtime to quickly remove the noise and stress.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Delta Investment Tracker - 追踪你所有投资的应用程序，只做聪明的动作]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界第一的投资跟踪应用程序。忘记电子表格，在一个地方管理你所有的投资。如果你投资于或关注一个或多个资产类别，如股票、加密货币或ETF，Delta就是你正在寻找的工具。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/delta-investment-tracker</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/delta-investment-tracker</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 10:30:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>World’s number one Investment Tracking app. Forget about spreadsheets and manage all your investments in one place. If you’re invested in or following one or multiple asset classes, such as stocks, cryptos or ETFs, Delta is the tool you were looking for.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MySuper.Fan - 识别你在YouTube上的顶级超级粉丝]]></title><description><![CDATA[通过MySuper.fan，您可以创建一个您的超级粉丝的排行榜；立即生成一个超级粉丝档案，并深入了解您的超级粉丝在您的内容中的参与情况。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mysuper-fan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mysuper-fan</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 10:30:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With the MySuper.fan, you can create a leaderboard of your superfans; instantly generate a superfan profile and do a deep dive into your superfan&apos;s engagement across your content.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SEOptimer - SEO审计和报告工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[SEOptimer是一个全功能的SEO审计和报告平台，可以在30秒内全面审查一个网站。数字机构可以使用SEOptimer为他们的客户和潜在客户制作简单而漂亮的PDF报告。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/seoptimer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/seoptimer</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 10:30:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>SEOptimer is a full-featured SEO Audit &amp; Reporting platform which can comprehensively review a website in under 30 seconds. Digital agencies can use SEOptimer to produce simple and beautiful PDF reports for their clients and prospects.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BuildBlocks - 发现用户策划的小众无码问题的资源]]></title><description><![CDATA[BuildBlocks是一个用户策划的资源平台，帮助在几分钟内解决你的利基无代码问题。发现和添加资源，提出问题并成为社区的一部分。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/buildblocks</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/buildblocks</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 10:09:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>BuildBlocks is a user-curated resource platform to help solve your niche no-code problems in minutes. Discover and add resources, ask questions and become a part of the community.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Archimedes 2.0 - 有信心使投资成为你生活中更大的一部分]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿基米德将投资简化为简单、可操作的步骤，无论您的经验如何。作为您平易近人的投资教练，我们授权您以您想要的方式管理您的资金，实现您的目标。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/archimedes-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/archimedes-2-0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 09:23:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Archimedes simplifies investing into easy, actionable steps, no matter your experience. As your approachable investment coach, we empower you to manage your money the way you want to achieve your goals.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NativeBase Startup+ - 100多个用于网页和手机的响应式React Native屏幕]]></title><description><![CDATA[NativeBase Startup+是一个由100多个响应性的、可访问的、支持黑暗模式的、可生产的React Native屏幕组成的捆绑包，用于移动和网络。依靠NativeBase v3的信任，使用这些高度主题化的屏幕来构建你的下一个梦想项目。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nativebase-startup</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nativebase-startup</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 09:05:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>NativeBase Startup+ is a bundle of 100+ responsive, accessible, dark mode supported and production ready React Native screens for mobile and web. Rely on the trust of NativeBase v3 and use these highly themeable screens to build your next dream project.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BitsForDigits - 为自立门户的创始人免费提供部分收购市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[BitsForDigits是世界上最大的部分收购市场。我们使创始人能够匿名、简单、免费地将少数股权和多数股权出售给专业投资者。今天就列出你的企业，以获得已经在平台上的+100个投资者的报价!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bitsfordigits</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bitsfordigits</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 08:50:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>BitsForDigits is the world’s #1 partial buyout marketplace. We make it anonymous, easy and free for founders to sell minority and majority stakes to professional investors. List your business today to get offers from the +100 investors already on the platform!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Popify - 使用社会证明弹出窗口提高你的转换率]]></title><description><![CDATA[有了Popify，你可以创建设计出色的弹出式特别促销通知，并通过显示最近的客户活动，如最近的销售、添加到购物车、实时访客计数器和评论，建立FOMO（害怕错过）。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/popify</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/popify</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 20:48:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With Popify, you can create awesome designed popup notifications of special promotions and build FOMO (fear of missing out) by showing recent customer&apos;s activities like recent sales, add to cart, live visitor counter, and reviews.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Github Wrapped 2021 - 为每个GitHub用户提供个性化的回放视频]]></title><description><![CDATA[获取你的GitHub活动的个性化年度回顾视频。输入你的名字，一个下载的视频将立即生成! 使用标签&nbsp;#GithubWrapped在社交媒体上发布。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/github-wrapped-2021</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/github-wrapped-2021</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 16:55:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Get your personalized Year in Review video of your GitHub activity. Enter your name and a downloaded video will be generated immediately! Post it on social media using the hashtag&amp;nbsp;#GithubWrapped.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[thirdweb - 轻松构建Web3应用程序和游戏]]></title><description><![CDATA[⛏️ **建立**功能，如NFT、市场、代币等，只需点击几下 🧰 **实用**SDK、小工具和接口，将web3功能整合到你的应用程序中 🕹️ **支持**区块链游戏、DAO、NFT卡平台、生成艺术滴等。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/thirdweb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/thirdweb</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 14:25:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>⛏️ **Build** features such as NFT&apos;s, marketplaces, tokens, and more in a few clicks 🧰 **Utility** SDK&apos;s, widgets, and interfaces to integrate web3 features into your app 🕹️ **Powers** blockchain games, DAO&apos;s, NFT card platforms, generative art drops and more</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>