<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Product Hunt 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Product Hunt 热门App，网站和产品]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 03:18:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Unicorns to the Moon - 像越共一样玩这个充满行动力的桌面游戏]]></title><description><![CDATA[独角兽登月》是一款动作类桌面游戏，将你成为炙手可热的风险投资家（VC）的梦想变成了现实 你作为风险投资家的工作是什么？投资独角兽公司，并将它们送上月球。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/unicorns-to-the-moon</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/unicorns-to-the-moon</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 02:48:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Unicorns To The Moon is an action-packed tabletop game that turns your dreams of being a hotshot venture capitalist (VC) into a reality! Your job as a VC? Invest in unicorn companies, and send them to the moon.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PodBuddy - 从你的播客中制作一口大小的社交媒体视频剪辑]]></title><description><![CDATA[PodBuddy将你的播客集做成动画视频，非常适合在社交媒体上分享。创建一个动画帖子只需几秒钟。只需选择你的播客集片段，PodBuddy就会根据你的播客作品创建一个帖子。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/podbuddy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/podbuddy</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:34:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>PodBuddy makes animated videos from your podcast episode, perfect for sharing on social media. It takes seconds to create an animated post. Simply pick your podcast episode clip and PodBuddy will create a post based on your podcast&apos;s artwork.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spatial - NFT画廊和展览的Metaverse]]></title><description><![CDATA[空间是文化的元空间，在这里我们可以一起体验一键式NFT画廊和展览。创作者、收藏家和品牌可以在网络、移动和VR上免费举办美丽的沉浸式体验。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/spatial-4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/spatial-4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:34:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Spatial is the metaverse for culture, where we can all experience one-click NFT galleries &amp; exhibitions together. Creators, collectors &amp; brands can host beautiful immersive experiences across web, mobile, and VR for free.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[OnPodium - 播客网站，吸引并扩大你的听众群]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是我去年推出的Podsite项目的继承者。我们正在根据现有客户的反馈，不断改进OnPodium。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/onpodium</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/onpodium</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:46:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>This is a successor of my previous project Podsite that was launched last year. We’re constantly improving OnPodium according to the feedback we get from existing customers.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[First 1000 Users Guide - 从构思到第一个1000个用户的互动指南]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个完全互动的指南，在1个月内从构思到1000个用户！由大量来自科技界人士的资源组成。由保罗-格雷厄姆和莱尼-拉奇茨基等科技人士提供的大量资源组成，以及一个互动界面，你可以记录并从你的发现中学习!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/first-1000-users-guide</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/first-1000-users-guide</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 14:25:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A fully interactive guide on going from ideation to 1000 users within 1 month! Composed of tons of resources from tech figures like Paul Graham and Lenny Rachitsky, as well as an interactive interface where you can record and learn from your findings!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GitHub Wrapped - 你的代码年]]></title><description><![CDATA[你在2021年写了很多代码--提交、拉动请求和评论。反思你的这一年，你所贡献的项目，以及你所支持的开发者。开放源代码。在Twitter上分享或添加到你的个人Readme。由Neat的团队制作。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/github-wrapped-4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/github-wrapped-4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 14:01:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>You coded a lot in 2021 - commits, pull requests, and reviews. Reflect on your year, the projects you contributed to, and the developers you supported. Open source. Share on Twitter or add to your personal Readme. Made by the team at Neat.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How much is your SaaS worth? - 由463项近期交易提供的SaaS估值计算器]]></title><description><![CDATA[你应该得到一个更高的估值。现在你有数据来获得它。利用我们的实时洞察力，确保你得到你的价值。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/how-much-is-your-saas-worth</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/how-much-is-your-saas-worth</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 14:01:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>You deserve a higher valuation. Now you have the data to get it. Use our real-time insights to make sure you get what you’re worth.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zen Flowchart 2.0 - 创建流程图的最简单工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[Zen Flowchart是最简单的流程图制作工具。受到全球160万用户的喜爱。从头开始重建的新的强大功能。- 实时协作 - 更多的流程图形状 - 更干净和更快的用户界面 - 图标 - 自定义颜色]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zen-flowchart-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zen-flowchart-2-0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 13:06:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Zen Flowchart is the simplest flowchart maker. Loved by 1.6M users worldwide. Rebuilt from scratch with new powerful features: - Live Collaboration - More flowchart shapes - Cleaner &amp; faster UI - Icons - Custom colors</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PocketTube 3.0 - 一个全新的YouTube体验]]></title><description><![CDATA[PocketTube是一种全新的YouTube体验。管理和分类您的订阅，创建群组，使用自动标签，标记为已观看，毫不费力地过滤您的视频源，所有这些都在YouTube自己的界面中。可用于您的浏览器]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pockettube-3-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pockettube-3-0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 12:45:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>PocketTube is a brand new YouTube experience. Manage and sort your subscriptions, create groups, use auto tags, mark as watched, filter your video feed effortlessly, all its within YouTube&apos;s own interface. Available for your browser</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Customer Service Tips by LabiDesk - 50多个针对初创企业的免费客户服务技巧]]></title><description><![CDATA[50多个客户服务技巧! 我们把共同的规则和最佳做法放在一起，这些规则和最佳做法帮助许多公司在他们的客户服务组织方式以及他们如何处理每一个客户支持查询的帮助下成长。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/customer-service-tips-by-labidesk</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/customer-service-tips-by-labidesk</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 11:46:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>50+ Customer Service Tips! We put together a list of common rules and best practices that helped so many companies grow with the help of the way their customer service was organized and how they handled each and every customer support inquiry.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sales Automation Playbook by NetHunt CRM - 通过全面的销售自动化演练来完成工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[把它想象成一本销售自动化的食谱。它一步一步地引导你完成所有销售流程的自动化，从售前到售后；为什么、何时以及我们应该如何利用它。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sales-automation-playbook-by-nethunt-crm</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sales-automation-playbook-by-nethunt-crm</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 11:16:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Picture this as a cookbook for sales automation. Step-by-step, it walks you through automation for all your sales processes, from pre-sale to post-sale; why, when, and how we should utilize it.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Triage 2 - 为您的收件箱提供急救服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[Triage是对那些努力保持收件箱顶部的人的急救措施。它并不试图取代传统的电子邮件软件，而是让你利用你的停机时间来迅速消除噪音和压力。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/triage-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/triage-2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 11:16:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Triage is first aid for people who struggle to stay on top of their inbox. It doesn’t try to replace traditional email software, but lets you use your downtime to quickly remove the noise and stress.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Delta Investment Tracker - 追踪你所有投资的应用程序，只做聪明的动作]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界第一的投资跟踪应用程序。忘记电子表格，在一个地方管理你所有的投资。如果你投资于或关注一个或多个资产类别，如股票、加密货币或ETF，Delta就是你正在寻找的工具。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/delta-investment-tracker</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/delta-investment-tracker</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 10:30:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>World’s number one Investment Tracking app. Forget about spreadsheets and manage all your investments in one place. If you’re invested in or following one or multiple asset classes, such as stocks, cryptos or ETFs, Delta is the tool you were looking for.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MySuper.Fan - 识别你在YouTube上的顶级超级粉丝]]></title><description><![CDATA[通过MySuper.fan，您可以创建一个您的超级粉丝的排行榜；立即生成一个超级粉丝档案，并深入了解您的超级粉丝在您的内容中的参与情况。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mysuper-fan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mysuper-fan</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 10:30:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With the MySuper.fan, you can create a leaderboard of your superfans; instantly generate a superfan profile and do a deep dive into your superfan&apos;s engagement across your content.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SEOptimer - SEO审计和报告工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[SEOptimer是一个全功能的SEO审计和报告平台，可以在30秒内全面审查一个网站。数字机构可以使用SEOptimer为他们的客户和潜在客户制作简单而漂亮的PDF报告。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/seoptimer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/seoptimer</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 10:30:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>SEOptimer is a full-featured SEO Audit &amp; Reporting platform which can comprehensively review a website in under 30 seconds. Digital agencies can use SEOptimer to produce simple and beautiful PDF reports for their clients and prospects.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BuildBlocks - 发现用户策划的小众无码问题的资源]]></title><description><![CDATA[BuildBlocks是一个用户策划的资源平台，帮助在几分钟内解决你的利基无代码问题。发现和添加资源，提出问题并成为社区的一部分。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/buildblocks</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/buildblocks</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 10:09:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>BuildBlocks is a user-curated resource platform to help solve your niche no-code problems in minutes. Discover and add resources, ask questions and become a part of the community.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Archimedes 2.0 - 有信心使投资成为你生活中更大的一部分]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿基米德将投资简化为简单、可操作的步骤，无论您的经验如何。作为您平易近人的投资教练，我们授权您以您想要的方式管理您的资金，实现您的目标。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/archimedes-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/archimedes-2-0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 09:23:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Archimedes simplifies investing into easy, actionable steps, no matter your experience. As your approachable investment coach, we empower you to manage your money the way you want to achieve your goals.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NativeBase Startup+ - 100多个用于网页和手机的响应式React Native屏幕]]></title><description><![CDATA[NativeBase Startup+是一个由100多个响应性的、可访问的、支持黑暗模式的、可生产的React Native屏幕组成的捆绑包，用于移动和网络。依靠NativeBase v3的信任，使用这些高度主题化的屏幕来构建你的下一个梦想项目。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nativebase-startup</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nativebase-startup</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 09:05:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>NativeBase Startup+ is a bundle of 100+ responsive, accessible, dark mode supported and production ready React Native screens for mobile and web. Rely on the trust of NativeBase v3 and use these highly themeable screens to build your next dream project.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BitsForDigits - 为自立门户的创始人免费提供部分收购市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[BitsForDigits是世界上最大的部分收购市场。我们使创始人能够匿名、简单、免费地将少数股权和多数股权出售给专业投资者。今天就列出你的企业，以获得已经在平台上的+100个投资者的报价!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bitsfordigits</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bitsfordigits</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 08:50:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>BitsForDigits is the world’s #1 partial buyout marketplace. We make it anonymous, easy and free for founders to sell minority and majority stakes to professional investors. List your business today to get offers from the +100 investors already on the platform!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Popify - 使用社会证明弹出窗口提高你的转换率]]></title><description><![CDATA[有了Popify，你可以创建设计出色的弹出式特别促销通知，并通过显示最近的客户活动，如最近的销售、添加到购物车、实时访客计数器和评论，建立FOMO（害怕错过）。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/popify</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/popify</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 20:48:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With Popify, you can create awesome designed popup notifications of special promotions and build FOMO (fear of missing out) by showing recent customer&apos;s activities like recent sales, add to cart, live visitor counter, and reviews.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Github Wrapped 2021 - 为每个GitHub用户提供个性化的回放视频]]></title><description><![CDATA[获取你的GitHub活动的个性化年度回顾视频。输入你的名字，一个下载的视频将立即生成! 使用标签&nbsp;#GithubWrapped在社交媒体上发布。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/github-wrapped-2021</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/github-wrapped-2021</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 16:55:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Get your personalized Year in Review video of your GitHub activity. Enter your name and a downloaded video will be generated immediately! Post it on social media using the hashtag&amp;nbsp;#GithubWrapped.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[thirdweb - 轻松构建Web3应用程序和游戏]]></title><description><![CDATA[⛏️ **建立**功能，如NFT、市场、代币等，只需点击几下 🧰 **实用**SDK、小工具和接口，将web3功能整合到你的应用程序中 🕹️ **支持**区块链游戏、DAO、NFT卡平台、生成艺术滴等。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/thirdweb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/thirdweb</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 14:25:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>⛏️ **Build** features such as NFT&apos;s, marketplaces, tokens, and more in a few clicks 🧰 **Utility** SDK&apos;s, widgets, and interfaces to integrate web3 features into your app 🕹️ **Powers** blockchain games, DAO&apos;s, NFT card platforms, generative art drops and more</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Platypus (Beta) - 与拥有相同价值观的团队相匹配]]></title><description><![CDATA[通过反思什么对你的职业生活最重要，创建你的鸭嘴兽图案。探索具有你的文化优先权的团队，他们关心的事情与你相同。成为 Platypus 的早期采用者，帮助我们塑造招聘的未来。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/platypus-beta</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/platypus-beta</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 13:38:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Create your Platypus Print by reflecting on what is most important to your professional life. Explore teams with your cultural priorities who care about the same things that you do. Become a Platypus early adopter and help us shape the future of recruitment.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SuccessRate - 通过校友们的反馈意见来改进你的YC/500/TC申请]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们欢迎你在截止日期前提交你的申请草案，以获得校友的反馈。你越早提交，得到的反馈就越多。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/successrate</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/successrate</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 12:31:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>You are welcome to submit your draft application before a deadline to get alumni feedback. The sooner you submit more feedback you get.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Free AI Email Subject Line Generator - 使用AI和GPT-3创建有影响力的独特主题词]]></title><description><![CDATA[你是否已经厌倦了所有基本的主题行生成器，它们给你的是同样老套的想法？使用基于GPT-3的免费人工智能电子邮件主题行生成器创建独特的主题行。只需输入电子邮件的主题，让人工智能发挥它的魔力。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/free-ai-email-subject-line-generator</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/free-ai-email-subject-line-generator</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 11:25:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Are you tired of all the basic subject line generators that give you the same old cookie-cutter ideas? Create unique subject lines with a free AI email subject line generator based on GPT-3. Simply enter the topic of the email and let the AI do its magic.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Marketing4Makers Community - 想学习营销的创客们的反馈群体]]></title><description><![CDATA[Marketing4Makers是一个由希望提高营销技能的创客组成的私人社区。每天，我们都会分享我们的奋斗和胜利，并在营销工作中相互帮助。我们每周都会召开电话会议，分享我们目前的行动并庆祝我们的胜利。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/marketing4makers-community</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/marketing4makers-community</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 11:01:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Marketing4Makers is a private community of makers that wants to grow their marketing skills Every day, we share our struggles and wins, and we help each other in our marketing efforts. We have a weekly call to share our current actions and celebrate our wins</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Static.app - 为您的静态网站提供一键式托管解决方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[Static.app是在线托管静态HTML网站的最简单方法。拖放一个带有你的页面或整个网站的档案，我们将负责其余的工作。一切都包括在内。SSL证书、代码编辑器、表格和媒体存储都在一个地方。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/static-app-1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/static-app-1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 10:47:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Static.app is the easiest way to host a static HTML website online. Drag-and-drop an archive with your page or an entire website and we will take care of the rest. Everything is included: SSL certificate, code editor, forms and media storage all in one place.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trello Annual Report - 根据你的团队在Trello中的年份，为他们提供统计资料和奖励]]></title><description><![CDATA[想知道今年在Trello发生了什么吗？对你最喜欢的新功能说*Trello* 😎 Trello年度报告功能既有趣又免费，它能从你的团队过去一年的Trello活动中生成有趣的统计数据和奖项。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/trello-annual-report</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/trello-annual-report</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 09:46:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Wanna Know What Happened In Trello This Year? Say *Trello* to Your New Favorite Power-Up 😎 Fun &amp; free, the Trello Annual Report Power-Up generates interesting stats and awards from your team’s Trello activity over the past year</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Free Logos by Larkef - 为你的项目提供完美的标志只是一个点击的距离。]]></title><description><![CDATA[获得一个巨大的标志库，该库来自一个令人难以置信的设计师Jord Riekwel。这个有十年历史的档案馆收集了所有未使用的客户标志，Jord善意地捐赠给任何人，供他们在下一个项目中使用。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/free-logos-by-larkef</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/free-logos-by-larkef</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 09:16:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Get access to a huge library of logos from an incredible designer, Jord Riekwel. This ten-year-old archive is a collection of all unused client logos, which Jord kind donated for anyone to use in their next project.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Workbase - 使用公式为动态警报和行动提供动力]]></title><description><![CDATA[警报、观察清单和自动化，由定制的可堆叠公式提供支持。Workbase自动扫描和运行触发器，包括Salesforce、Snowflake和其他实时系统的数据源。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/workbase-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/workbase-3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 09:16:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Alerts, watchlists, and automations powered by custom stackable formulas. Workbase automatically scans and runs triggers over your data sources including Salesforce, Snowflake, and other live systems.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BuyMeACryptoCoffee - 用加密货币获得你的受众支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[摆脱传统货币，在加密货币中轻松获得受众的支持。不是创作者？你可以只用你最喜欢的创作者的钱包地址来表示对他们的支持! 还可以添加一些感谢的话语。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/buymeacryptocoffee</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/buymeacryptocoffee</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 09:01:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Move on from traditional currency, and easily get support from your audience in Crypto. Not a creator? You can show support to your favorite creators with just their wallet addresses! And also add a few words of gratitude.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021 Your Year In Meetings - 与杰夫-贝佐斯一起飞入太空，审查你的2021年]]></title><description><![CDATA[进行一次免费的太空飞行，以获得一份个性化的报告，显示对你2021年的会议的独特见解。从会议的总时长到你遇到的人的数量以及其他有趣的趋势! 通过分享你的会议报告要求你的炫耀权利!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/2021-your-year-in-meetings</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/2021-your-year-in-meetings</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 08:36:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Take a free space flight to get a personalized report showing unique insights into your meetings from 2021. From total hours in meetings to number of people you met &amp; other fun trends! Claim your bragging rights by sharing your meeting report!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bucket4J - 基于Java的令牌桶算法的速率限制]]></title><description><![CDATA[基于token-bucket算法的Java速率限制库。该库包括许多巨大的功能，为你的API提供速率限制。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bucket4j</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bucket4j</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 07:35:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Java rate-limiting library based on the token-bucket algorithm. The library includes many huge features to provide rate-limiting to your API.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gitploy - 在几分钟内围绕GitHub建立部署系统。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gitploy使你的团队或组织在几分钟内围绕GitHub建立部署系统。现在，不要浪费时间来建立部署系统。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/gitploy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/gitploy</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 05:02:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Gitploy makes your team or organization build the deployment system around GitHub in minutes. Now, do not waste the time building the deployment system.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Task Muncher - 一个帮助你保持激光专注于咀嚼你的任务的应用程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[Task Muncher是由#EverydayHustle的Adam Ali开发的。保持激光聚焦于咀嚼你的每周任务。通过我们的智能、简单和强大的任务管理应用程序，对重要的事情进行优先排序。现在开始啃食这些任务吧！!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/task-muncher</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/task-muncher</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 01:45:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Task Muncher has been developed by Adam Ali of the #EverydayHustle. Stay Laser-focused on munching your weekly tasks. Prioritize what’s important with our smart, simple, and powerful task management app. Now get to munching those tasks!!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MusicMatch - 在任何应用程序中打开音乐链接。Spotify或苹果音乐]]></title><description><![CDATA[音乐在分享时是最好的。通过MusicMatch，朋友们可以分享和打开音乐链接，即使他们使用不同的流媒体服务，如Spotify和Apple Music。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/musicmatch</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/musicmatch</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 20:30:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Music is best when shared. With MusicMatch, friends can share and open music links even if they use different streaming services, like Spotify and Apple Music.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Forte² - 培养习惯，而不是连胜]]></title><description><![CDATA[当你建立新的习惯或戒掉旧的习惯时，Forte²可以帮助你跟踪你的进展。与其他习惯跟踪器不同的是，Forte²不会因为错过一天而将你打回零分；Forte²会给你的每个习惯打分，而不是只计算连贯性。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/forte-4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/forte-4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 15:40:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Forte² is here to help you track your progress as you build new habits or quit old ones. Unlike other habits trackers, Forte² doesn&apos;t set you back to zero for missing one day; Forte² gives you a score for each habit instead of just counting streaks.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[sttr - 一个对字符串进行各种操作的cli应用程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[sttr是一个命令行软件，允许你在字符串上快速运行各种转换操作。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sttr</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sttr</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 15:40:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>sttr is command-line software that allows you to quickly run various transformation operations on the string.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stenography - 一个结合了人工智能和代码解析的智能代码库文档器]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stenography结合了最先进的人工智能技术（OpenAI Codex）和代码解析技术，创造了一个智能的代码库文档器。Stenography的设计是为了适应自然的开发流程，并做到开发工具一直以来对我们的承诺：减少认知负荷]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/stenography</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/stenography</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 11:48:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Stenography combines state of the art AI technology (OpenAI Codex) and code parsing techniques to create a smart codebase documenter. Stenography is designed to to fit the natural dev flow and do what dev tools have always promised us: decrease cognitive load!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Marble - 用一个超级网站培养超级粉丝]]></title><description><![CDATA[为你的观众和你的赞助商建立终极的内容体验，把你所有的内容放在一个地方，以提高参与度和提高你的广告收入水平。将你的Instagram、TikTok、Youtube、Spotify、Facebook、Twitter和你的外部链接结合起来。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/marble-4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/marble-4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 07:26:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Build the ultimate content experience for your audience and your sponsors by putting all your content in one place to increase engagement and level up your ad revenue. Combine your Instagram, TikTok, Youtube, Spotify, Facebook, Twitter and your external links.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[JSONverify - 一个验证和格式化JSON对象的网络工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[调试JSON可能会变得非常复杂，特别是当它们是巨大的时候，所以使用JSONverify将使调试过程更加简单和快速。另外，该应用程序可以被用于格式化JSON对象。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/jsonverify</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/jsonverify</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 00:35:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Debugging JSON can get really complicated especially when they are huge, so using the JSONverify will make the process of debugging much simpler and faster. Also, the application can be sued to format JSON objects.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ScreenREC - 一个简单的网络屏幕记录器]]></title><description><![CDATA[📹 ScreenREC : 一个真正简单的网络屏幕记录器。特点 ✔️导出类型选择器（目前是MP4/Webm） ✔️视频预览 ✔️视频下载 ✔️黑暗/光明模式切换 ✔️开放源代码]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/screenrec</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/screenrec</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 17:45:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>📹 ScreenREC : A really simple web screen recorder. ✨ Features ✔️ Export type selector (currently MP4/Webm) ✔️ Video preview ✔️ Video download ✔️ Dark/Light mode toggle ✔️ Open Source</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Work With Data - 普遍的数据来源]]></title><description><![CDATA[探索关于4M+主题和实体的各种形式的数据--由我们结合众多可靠来源的知识图谱提供支持。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/work-with-data</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/work-with-data</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 16:22:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Explore data in all its forms on 4M+ topics and entities - backed by our knowledge graph combining numerous reliable sources.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Style Dictionary Play - 亚马逊设计令牌库的免费在线游乐场所]]></title><description><![CDATA[- 在你的浏览器中实验风格字典 - 实时预览窗口 - 移动 - 桌面视图 - 分享URL以分享项目 - 开放源代码 - 无需注册/无需登录 👉https://www.style-dictionary-play.dev]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/style-dictionary-play</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/style-dictionary-play</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 16:01:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>- Experiment with style-dictionary in your browser - Live preview window - Mobile - Desktop view - Share URL to share project - Open source - No signup / No login 👉 https://www.style-dictionary-play.dev</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Movingto - 签证比较网站]]></title><description><![CDATA[搬家到不同的国家从来没有如此无缝，无压力，和成本效益。我们为你比较签证和律师事务所，确保你得到最好的价格和服务。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/movingto</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/movingto</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 15:38:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Moving to Different Countries has never been so seamless, stress-free, and cost-effective. We compare visas and law firms for you to make sure you get the best prices and service.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Novi from Meta - 数字钱包可即时移动资金，不收取任何费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[Novi是Meta公司的一个数字钱包，帮助你即时安全地发送和接收资金。为满足日常需要、每月开支和特殊场合的需要，可以跨越国界汇款--今天就不需要收费。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/novi-from-meta</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/novi-from-meta</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 14:07:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Novi is a digital wallet from Meta that helps you send and receive money instantly and securely. Move money across borders for everyday needs, monthly expenses, and special occasions — today with no fees.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1 Minute Writing Challenge - 通过每天写作来减轻压力和感受到生产力。]]></title><description><![CDATA[养成写作的习惯，每天只需拿出1分钟。🎨 寻找由最佳设计师策划的美丽背景。🥳 3000多人的社区，让你保持动力 🚀 排行榜，连胜追踪 💡 每天的新想法]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/1-minute-writing-challenge</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/1-minute-writing-challenge</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 12:28:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Get into the habit of writing by dedicating just 1 minute everyday. 👩‍🎨 Find beautiful backgrounds curated by best designers. 🥳 A community of 3000+ folks to keep you motivated 🚀 Leaderboard, streak tracking 💡 New ideas everyday</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Break - 与更大的朋友群体建立联系的简单方法]]></title><description><![CDATA[看看你的朋友什么时候有空，当你需要休息的时候就发出信号--让你的社交生活过得充实起来。向你选择的一群人发送信号，并进行自发的音频聊天，一起喝杯咖啡或相约午餐叙旧。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/break-015dfe20-416d-4905-a4a1-c144718c9481</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/break-015dfe20-416d-4905-a4a1-c144718c9481</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 11:32:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>See when your friends are available and signal when you need a break - to live your social life in full. Send a signal to a group of people you choose and have a spontaneous audio chat, grab a cup of coffee together or meet for lunch to catch up.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PinChat - 为买方和卖方提供的具有CRM功能的信使]]></title><description><![CDATA[PinChat为你提供了一种更简单的方式来开始与他人聊天。通过你的PinChat链接和二维码，其他人可以立即与你开始聊天，而无需登录或注册。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pinchat-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pinchat-2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 02:46:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>PinChat provides you with an easier way to start a chat with others. With your PinChat link and QR code, others can start a chat with you instantly without having to log in or sign up.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dear Sun - 天气一目了然Mac版]]></title><description><![CDATA[亲爱的太阳是一个可靠的Mac菜单栏应用程序，在高峰期显示准确的天气。如何做到？你为你挑选最准确的天气数据源。没有囤积数据的跟踪器或复杂的曼波-简波界面。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/dear-sun</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/dear-sun</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 01:29:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Dear Sun is a reliable Mac menu bar app that shows accurate weather at a peak. How? You pick the most accurate weather data source for you. No data hoarding trackers or complex mambo-jambo interfaces.</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>