<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Product Hunt 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Product Hunt 热门App，网站和产品]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 05:15:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[AppSwitcher for Mac - 清潔的應用程序切換。一次只切換一個應用。就像Mac上的iOS。]]></title><description><![CDATA[AppSwitcher爲您的應用程序提供漂亮的演示。在類似iOS的Big Sur上。在應用程序之間切換，並切換到，只顯示該應用程序。"隱藏其他總是在"。擁有一個乾淨的桌面+應用程序。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/appswitcher-for-mac</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/appswitcher-for-mac</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 22:14:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>AppSwitcher For Beautiful Presentation of your Apps. On the iOS-like Big Sur. Switch between Apps and Switch to, show only that App. &quot;Hide Others Always On&quot;. Have a Clean Desktop + App.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Polotno SDK - 創建網頁設計編輯器的工具包]]></title><description><![CDATA[Polotno SDK是一個JavaScript庫和一組React組件，用於在你的Web應用程序中製作畫布編輯器。它內置了對模板、谷歌字體、文本樣式、圖片、視覺編輯等的支持。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/polotno-sdk</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/polotno-sdk</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 20:36:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Polotno SDK is a JavaScript library and set of React components to make canvas editors in your web applications. With built-in support for templates, google fonts, text styles, stock photos, visual edits and more.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Product Library - 1200多個爲產品經理策劃的資源集合。]]></title><description><![CDATA[一個爲產品經理提供的1200多個有價值的網絡資源庫--根據來源和類型進行了整齊的分類。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/product-library-resources-by-zeda-io</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/product-library-resources-by-zeda-io</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 20:22:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A repository of 1200+ value-packed resources for product managers from the web - neatly categorized based on source and type.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Story Time - 一個幫助你建立認可文化的工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[得到認可的員工比沒有得到認可的員工更有動力，更有生產力，也更能投入到要完成的工作中。故事時間 "通過展示人們如何爲企業的成功做出貢獻，幫助在工作場所創造可見性、認可性和一致性。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/story-time</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/story-time</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 16:20:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Recognised employees are more motivated, productive, and engaged in the work to be done than those who are not. Story Time helps create visibility, recognition, and alignment in the workplace by surfacing how people contribute to the success of the business.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Interial Clarity - AI網絡應用，提升和銳化你的圖像分辨率]]></title><description><![CDATA[Interial Clarity是一個基於雲的工具，幫助你將圖像的分辨率放大4倍。Interial利用AI來確保放大過程儘可能準確。此外，Interial Clarity由AWS支持，以確保快速放大過程。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/interial-clarity</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/interial-clarity</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 15:38:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Interial Clarity is a cloud-based tool to help you enlarge your image&apos;s resolution 4X. Interial utilizes AI to make sure that the enlargement process as accurate as possible. In addition, Interial Clarity is backed by AWS to ensure a fast upscaling process.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blobbb Fun - 創建蓬鬆的blobby SVG形狀]]></title><description><![CDATA[Blobbb是設計師和開發人員在線創建他們的blob狀形狀SVG的有趣新方法。有了Blobbb，你可以在短時間內輕鬆生成、修改和下載一個漂亮的SVG。享受你的Blobb的樂趣吧! 🥳]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/blobbb-fun</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/blobbb-fun</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 13:53:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Blobbb is the fun new way for designers and developers to create their blob-like shapes SVG online. With Blobbb, you can easily generate, modify, and download a nice-looking SVG in no time. Have fun with your blobs! 🥳</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mastodon for iOS - 去中心化社交網絡的官方應用程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[第一個官方的Mastodon應用程序的iOS，有一個拋光的外觀和一個重點是易用性。開始使用分散的社交網絡Mastodon從來沒有這麼簡單過]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mastodon-for-ios</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mastodon-for-ios</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 09:40:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The first official Mastodon app for iOS, with a polished look and a focus on ease of use. Getting started on the decentralized social network Mastodon has never been more straightforward!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Scispot.io - 面向生命科學團隊的無代碼工作流自動化平臺]]></title><description><![CDATA[Scispot是一個無代碼工作流程自動化平臺，專爲快速成長的生命科學公司設計。生物公司使用Scispot在一個地方管理和跟蹤他們的項目、樣品和庫存。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/scispot-io-1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/scispot-io-1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 18:52:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Scispot is a no-code workflow automation platform designed for fast-growing life science companies. Bio companies use Scispot to manage &amp; track their projects, samples, and inventory all in one spot.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[UniAcquire - 商業買家和賣家的市場!]]></title><description><![CDATA[UniAcquire引入了一種新的買賣公司的方式。這是一個高效的市場，旨在幫助企業主和投資者更快地建立聯繫，並減少從開始到結束的時間。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/uniacquire</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/uniacquire</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 18:00:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>UniAcquire introduces a new way to buy and sell companies. It’s an efficient and effective marketplace designed to help business owners and investors connect faster, and reduce time from start to finish.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Visited States Map - 創建你自己的互動式受訪州/國家地圖]]></title><description><![CDATA[標記你訪問過的州，並根據你自己的喜好選擇顏色。在你的網站上嵌入地圖。分享到Facebook、Twitter等，向你的朋友展示你去過的地方。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/visited-states-map</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/visited-states-map</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 16:39:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Mark the states you&apos;ve visited and choose colors to your own liking. Embed the map on your website. Share on Facebook, Twitter, etc., and show your friends where you&apos;ve been.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aura - 用全新的眼光看待你的心情]]></title><description><![CDATA[介紹一下Aura，這是一個易於使用的情緒跟蹤應用程序，將你的日常生活情緒考慮在內。它讓你更好地瞭解自己，並幫助你在一天中保持均勻的情緒。該應用程序有各種功能，如統計、圖表等。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/aura-b260f046-6bf7-439f-8cd7-8521db48ae46</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/aura-b260f046-6bf7-439f-8cd7-8521db48ae46</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 15:25:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Introducing Aura, an easy to use mood tracking app that takes your daily life&apos;s mood into account. It allows you to understand yourself better and helps you maintain an even mood throughout the day. The app has various features such as statistics, graphs etc.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zine - 獲得讀者，並在出版前獲得直接反饋]]></title><description><![CDATA[想出寫作的想法，並弄清楚你的讀者是否會喜歡你的作品，這真的很困難。這就是爲什麼我們建立了Zine，讓你在發表前獲得讀者和直接的寫作反饋。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zine-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zine-3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 13:45:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>It&apos;s really hard to come up with ideas to write on and figure out whether your readers will like your piece or not. This is why we built Zine that allows you to gain readers and direct writing feedback before publishing.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MasterPluto—Get Free Mentorship - 免費的一對一指導，100多名導師，用戶體驗，開發，初創企業]]></title><description><![CDATA[Masterpluto是一個美麗的平臺和強大的力量，將導師和被指導者聯繫起來，進行1:1的指導。我們是一個由用戶體驗設計師、軟件開發人員、產品經理、數據科學家、創始人和領導人組成的強大社區。願這股力量與我們同在!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/masterpluto-get-free-mentorship</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/masterpluto-get-free-mentorship</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 13:05:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Masterpluto is a beautiful platform and powerful force to connect mentors and mentees for 1:1 mentorships. We are a strong community of UX Designers, Software Developers, Product Managers, Data Scientist, Founders and Leaders. May the force be with us!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Video Reviews by Reviewshake - 爲您的企業獲得視頻評論，在任何地方展示它們]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reviewshake是一款用於在線評論生成和管理的SaaS產品。我們的最新功能是視頻評論：只需點擊一下就能啓用，並開始接收視頻。你不必擔心格式、存儲或播放問題。這一切都由我們處理。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/video-reviews-by-reviewshake</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/video-reviews-by-reviewshake</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 13:05:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Reviewshake is a SaaS product for online review generation and management. Our latest feature is video reviews: enable them with a single click and start receiving them. You don&apos;t have to worry about formats, storage or playback. It&apos;s all handled by us.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ValueTools - 所有重要的開發工具都在一個應用程序中]]></title><description><![CDATA[🧰ValueTools是開發人員經常使用的重要工具的集合，全部捆綁在一個光滑的Windows應用程序中。忘掉尋找粘貼敏感信息的網站，只是爲了做一些基本的工作。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/valuetools</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/valuetools</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 12:33:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>🧰 ValueTools is a collection of important tools frequently used by developers, all bundled together in a sleek windows application. Forget about finding sites where you paste your sensitive information just to do some basic work.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Career Switch To Coding - 將新學的編碼技能轉化爲夢想的職業]]></title><description><![CDATA[你有足夠的編碼技能來完成工作，但你知道如何引起你的第一個僱主的注意嗎？職業轉換到編碼是一本書，帶你從一個不知名的編碼員到拒絕比你接受更多的工作機會。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/career-switch-to-coding</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/career-switch-to-coding</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 11:30:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>You have the coding skills to do the job, but do you know how to get the attention of your first employer? Career Switch To Coding is a book that takes you from an unknown coder to turning down more job offers than you accept.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GAUSS AI - 快速、可靠、經濟的數據標籤]]></title><description><![CDATA[高斯使任何擁有智能手機和互聯網連接的人都能成爲數據標籤員，我們的https://www.loom.com/share/ccfe9262bbb1440590fb390df0e0d23c，解鎖了一個新的標籤員生態系統。我們的https://www.loom.com/share/d05f440badf04a1cb02f5c53f530b6d8，可以爲內部項目進行多種數據格式的協作式數據貼標。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/gauss-ai</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/gauss-ai</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 10:28:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Gauss enables any person with a smartphone and an internet connection to be a data labeler, our https://www.loom.com/share/ccfe9262bbb1440590fb390df0e0d23c has unlocked a new labeler ecosystem. Our https://www.loom.com/share/d05f440badf04a1cb02f5c53f530b6d8 allows for Collaborative Data Labeling for Internal Projects across multiple data formats.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SideNotes 1.3 - 關於屏幕側的快速說明]]></title><description><![CDATA[SideNotes是一款基於Markdown的筆記應用，用於快速記錄。它比便條紙更優雅，更敏捷，也比大型文本編輯器更不顯眼。它住在屏幕一側，在你需要時出現。保存文本、顏色、任務、圖片、文件快捷方式。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sidenotes-1-3-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sidenotes-1-3-2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 10:28:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>SideNotes is a Markdown-based note-taking app for quick notes. More elegant than sticky notes, more agile, and more unobtrusive than big text editors. It lives on the screen side and appears when you need it. Save text, colors, tasks, pictures, file shortcuts.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Agency Directory - 尋找完美的機構，將你的品牌推向新的高度]]></title><description><![CDATA[瀏覽我們的資料庫，其中有1000多家提供營銷、設計、創意製作、社交媒體、公關等服務的機構 按地點、服務和規模進行篩選，準確找到你要找的東西。你對完美機構的搜索到此爲止。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-agency-directory</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-agency-directory</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 10:28:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Browse our library of 1000+ agencies offering services in marketing, design, creative production, social media, PR, and more! Filter by location, services, and size to find exactly what you’re looking for. Your search for the perfect agency ends here.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Free online MBA - 獲得20多個精心策劃的資源來學習你在MBA中的內容]]></title><description><![CDATA[這裏是一個精心策劃的資源清單，它將幫助你學習你在商學院的知識。但有一個重要的區別，它是免費的!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/free-online-mba</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/free-online-mba</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 08:24:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Here is a curated list of resources, that&apos;ll help you learn what you would in business school. But with a major difference, it&apos;s free!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Relief - 擺脫你的信用卡債務的免費應用程序。]]></title><description><![CDATA[救濟是擺脫債務的TurboTax。我們的應用程序通過直接與你的債權人談判，將你的本金餘額減少一半或更多，這很容易，而且是免費的。 加入我們的等待名單，可以得到100美元的債務補償，每次你推薦朋友，可以得到50美元。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/relief</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/relief</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 07:30:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Relief is the TurboTax for getting out of debt. Our app makes it easy by negotiating directly with your creditors to cut down your principal balance in half or more- for FREE Get $100 towards your debt by joining our waitlist &amp; $50 every time you refer friends</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Doppler for Mac - 一個爲購買音樂的人而設的音樂播放器。現在在Mac上。]]></title><description><![CDATA[多普勒是一個爲購買音樂的人提供的音樂播放器。- 加快整理你的音樂 - 不需要轉換文件 - 與iPhone應用同步 - 美麗的設計 - 強大的整合功能 多普勒讓擁有音樂和支持藝術家變得簡單。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/doppler-for-mac</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/doppler-for-mac</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 07:16:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Doppler is a music player for people who buy music. - Speed up organising your music - No need to convert files - Sync with iPhone app - Beautiful design - Powerful integrations Doppler makes owning music and supporting artists simple.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Colorize It - 安卓應用用AI將黑白照片變成彩色的]]></title><description><![CDATA["Colorize it "是一個使用AI自動爲灰度圖像着色的應用程序。它簡單、快速、有效，所以沒有人會注意到顏色是人工添加的。試試吧，讓你的舊記憶變得五彩繽紛、栩栩如生，賦予它們新的生命]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/colorize-it-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/colorize-it-3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 16:12:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&quot;Colorize it&quot; is an app that uses AI to automatically color grayscale images. It&apos;s easy, fast and effective, so no one will notice that the color was added artificially. Try it and give a new life to your old memories by turning them colorful and vivid!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pangea.app - 我們把大學生變成自由職業者]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pangea.app將公司與大學生（和剛畢業的）自由職業者聯繫起來。我們的平臺使僱用、管理和支付你未來的隊友變得容易。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pangea-app</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pangea-app</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 15:29:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Pangea.app connects companies with college (and recent grad) freelancers. Our platform makes it easy to hire, manage, and pay your future teammates.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Flagpack V2 - 爲你的數字產品提供驚人的旗幟圖標]]></title><description><![CDATA[🏴Flagpack是一個開源項目，爲您的數字產品提供250多個令人驚歎的旗幟圖標。可在您的設計或代碼項目中輕鬆實現。現在有Figma Variants和Svelte Components。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/flagpack-v2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/flagpack-v2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 14:22:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>🏴 Flagpack is an open source project of 250+ stunning flag icons for your digital product. Easily implementable in your design or code project. Now with Figma Variants and Svelte Components.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[LLC Toolkit - 註冊特拉華州有限責任公司，零費用]]></title><description><![CDATA[LLC Toolkit是一個簡單明瞭的公司成立，零開銷+零服務費! 我們的團隊有15年以上幫助其他公司成功的經驗! #buildinpublic 關注我們的旅程，享受更多的福利! 🎁]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/llc-toolkit</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/llc-toolkit</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 13:35:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>LLC Toolkit is a straightforward company formation with zero overhead + zero service fees! Our team has 15+ years helping other companies succeeded! #buildinpublic Follow our journey for more perks! 🎁</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Knights of the Flexbox Table - 用Tailwind CSS學習和記憶Flexbox的遊戲]]></title><description><![CDATA[Flexbox表的騎士是一個有趣的、互動的瀏覽器遊戲，在這裏你可以學習Flexbox如何與Tailwind CSS結合工作。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/knights-of-the-flexbox-table</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/knights-of-the-flexbox-table</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 12:09:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Knights of the Flexbox table is a fun, interactive browser game where you learn how Flexbox works in combination with Tailwind CSS.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Silex - 開放源代碼的網站建設者]]></title><description><![CDATA[無論您是創建下一個項目網站的製作者，還是爲客戶製作網站的設計師，您都會喜歡Silex。您可以選擇Wix和Webflow。可以破解，永遠免費，你的設計，你的方式! 免費不僅僅是價格問題。#Freedom.]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/silex</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/silex</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 12:09:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Whether you are a maker creating your next project&apos;s website or you are a designer making websites for customers, you will love Silex. Your alternative to Wix and Webflow. Hackable, forever free, your design, your way! Free is not just about price. #Freedom.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nash - 任何企業提供當日送達的最簡單方法]]></title><description><![CDATA[納什是一款軟件，通過在交付API（Uber、Doordash等）之上建立業務工作流程，使激活當日交付變得容易。例如，一家乾洗企業可以在客戶希望的時間提供取貨/送貨服務，而無需僱用司機。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nash-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nash-2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 11:49:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Nash is software that makes it easy to activate same-day delivery by building business workflows on top of delivery APIs (Uber, Doordash, etc). For example, a dry-cleaning business can offer pickup/delivery at a customer’s desired time, without hiring drivers.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BeTimeful Browser Extension - 讓社交媒體不那麼容易上癮，每天節省2小時]]></title><description><![CDATA[Betimeful刪除了你喜歡的社交媒體的新聞提要、推薦視頻或任何旨在讓你在工作中 "上癮 "的東西。用鼓舞人心的每日名言取代飼料，並在谷歌日曆/您自己的內置彈出式日曆上安排 "焦點區"。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/betimeful-browser-extension</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/betimeful-browser-extension</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 11:24:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Betimeful removes your preferred social media’s news feeds, recommendation videos, or anything designed to get you “hooked” during work. Replace the feed with inspiring daily quotes &amp; schedule “focus blocks” on Google Calendar/ your own built-in popup calendar</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Woodpecker Academy - 在不到一小時的時間裏，培養你的冷處理電子郵件的技能]]></title><description><![CDATA[在啄木鳥學院學習如何在不到一小時的時間內創建和優化成功的冷門電子郵件活動。免費加入我們的課程，並在之後馬上收到一份個性化的證書。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/woodpecker-academy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/woodpecker-academy</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 11:24:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Learn how to create and optimize successful cold email campaigns in less than one hour with Woodpecker Academy. Join our course for free and receive a personalized certificate right after.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ev.energy - 一種更便宜、更環保、更簡單的電動車充電方式]]></title><description><![CDATA[ev.energy可以自動讓你以最經濟、最不含碳的方式爲你的電動車充電，同時你還可以通過智能充電獲得現金獎勵! 可在https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/ev-energy-smart-ev-charging/id1418569315, https://apps.apple.com/us/app/ev-energy-smart-ev-charging/id1418569315 和 https://apps.apple.com/de/app/ev-energy-smart-ev-charging/id1418569315。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ev-energy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ev-energy</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 11:24:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>ev.energy automatically allows you to charge your electric vehicle in the most cost-effective and least carbon-intense way possible, all while you earn cash rewards for your smart charging! Available in the https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/ev-energy-smart-ev-charging/id1418569315, https://apps.apple.com/us/app/ev-energy-smart-ev-charging/id1418569315 and https://apps.apple.com/de/app/ev-energy-smart-ev-charging/id1418569315.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[FODZYME by Kiwi Biosciences - 旨在使食物成爲一種無痛的體驗]]></title><description><![CDATA[FODZYME是一種正在申請專利的新型混合酶，可以分解FODMAPs--一種可發酵纖維家族和已知的腸道麻煩製造者，特別適用於患有腸道疾病如腸易激綜合症的人。開始重新享受你最喜歡的食物吧!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fodzyme-by-kiwi-biosciences</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fodzyme-by-kiwi-biosciences</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 10:38:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>FODZYME is a novel patent-pending enzyme blend that breaks down FODMAPs — a family of fermentable fibers and known gut troublemakers, specially for folks with gut disorders like Irritable Bowel Syndrome. Start enjoying your favorite foods again!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bonjoro 2.0 - 用視頻建立驚人的客戶關係]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bonjoro 2.0幫助你通過視頻建立驚人的客戶關係。加入新客戶，預訂更多的銷售電話，收集客戶反饋，所有這些都通過快速的個性化視頻郵件來實現。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bonjoro-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bonjoro-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 09:42:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Bonjoro 2.0 helps you build amazing customer relationships with video. Onboard new customers, book more sales calls, gather customer feedback, all with quick personalized video-emails.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jovian 2.0 - 學習數據科學，建立真實世界的項目並獲得聘用]]></title><description><![CDATA[Jovian是一個數據科學和機器學習的學習平臺。你可以參加關於數據分析、機器學習、深度學習的免費初級課程，或加入爲期6個月的兼職在線訓練營，掌握行業相關技能並獲得聘用。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/jovian-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/jovian-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 09:42:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Jovian is a learning platform for data science and machine learning. You can take free beginner-friendly courses on data analysis, machine learning, deep learning or join a 6-month part-time online bootcamp to master industry-relevant skills and get hired.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Quest - 無代碼的Figma到HTML，構建令人愉悅的體驗]]></title><description><![CDATA[將您的Figma設計轉換爲實時網站。⠀ 設置自定義斷點以獲得真正的響應式體驗。輕鬆添加互動和動畫。從您自己的設計中創建完全自定義的幻燈片和表格。⠀ 實時啓動或導出乾淨的代碼。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/quest-ec0a9a1f-c1af-4ec0-8f51-1dbeb27df880</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/quest-ec0a9a1f-c1af-4ec0-8f51-1dbeb27df880</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 09:42:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Convert your Figma designs into live websites. ⠀ Set up custom breakpoints for a truly responsive experience. Add interactions &amp; animations easily. Create fully custom slideshows and forms from your own design. ⠀ Launch it live or export CLEAN code.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spline Alpha II - 下一個級別的3D優先設計工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[🔥 現在你可以從瀏覽器中使用Spline了! (在app.spline.design中嘗試)。我們正在引入材料資產和一個完整的建模工具，以及矢量編輯功能和大量的修復和改進 ⠀ 朝着3D-First設計流程邁出了一大步。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/spline-alpha-ii</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/spline-alpha-ii</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 09:42:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>🔥 Now you can use Spline from the browser! (try it at app.spline.design). We are introducing Material Assets and a full Modeling Tool alongside Vector Editing features and a ton of fixes and improvements! ⠀ A big step towards a 3D-First design process.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Viewst Workspace - 按期完成任務，擴大內容並提高創意生產]]></title><description><![CDATA[一個工作空間，讓你可以大規模地創建、協作和發佈廣告。Viewst使設計和營銷團隊的創意數量和種類成倍增加，更快地進入市場，並超越市場競爭。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/viewst-workspace</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/viewst-workspace</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 09:42:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>One workspace that allows you to create, collaborate and launch ads at scale. Viewst allows design and marketing teams to multiply creative volume and variety, go to market faster and out-market competition.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Color Glass Icons by Icons8 - 1,800多個看起來像寶石的幾何圖標]]></title><description><![CDATA[具有重疊元素的簡單幾何圖標。給它們重新上色或使其成爲單色--它們將閃閃發光 這些圖標是真正的魔法晶體，適用於歡快的設計，如遊戲、兒童應用程序，或時髦的商業網站。免費提供鏈接!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/color-glass-icons-by-icons8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/color-glass-icons-by-icons8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 08:26:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Simple geometric icons with overlapping elements. Recolor them or make them monochrome — they will shine! These icons are real magic crystals for cheerful designs like games, children apps, or funky business websites. Free for a link!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Liveblocks - 構建驚人的實時協作產品]]></title><description><![CDATA[Liveblocks是一套API，幫助你創建高性能和可靠的協作體驗。有了Liveblocks，你可以在幾分鐘內實現任何協作，這樣你就可以給你的核心產品以應有的關注。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/liveblocks</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/liveblocks</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 08:26:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Liveblocks is a set of APIs that helps you create performant and reliable collaborative experiences. With Liveblocks, you can make anything collaborative in minutes so that you can give your core product the attention it deserves.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ProjectHunt - 發現正在公開建設的頂級無碼項目]]></title><description><![CDATA[發現在公共場所建造的頂級無代碼項目 🚀 註冊後可免費獲得一本無代碼資源的電子書!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/projecthunt</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/projecthunt</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 08:26:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Discover Top No-Code projects Built In Public 🚀 Sign up to receive a free E-book of No-code Resources!!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Slip - 構建交互式編程課程的最簡單方法]]></title><description><![CDATA[🔨建立一個引人入勝的互動式編程課程 🖥嵌入可執行的代碼片段、代碼筆、figma設計，以及更多 💰直接向你的聽衆出售你的課程，用你的編程知識掙錢。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/slip</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/slip</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 08:02:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>🔨 Build an engaging interactive programming course 🖥 Embed executable code snippets, codepens, figma designs, and more 💰 Sell your course directly to your audience and earn money from your programming knowledge.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Beseda - 爲遠程團隊提供異步視頻和音頻信息服務]]></title><description><![CDATA[用Beseda來代替會議，發送視頻和音頻--都是轉錄的--有更多的時間來專注於工作，而不會分心。Standups，設計審查，報告bug，收集和給予反饋 - 天空中的應用方式是無限的。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/beseda</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/beseda</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 07:21:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Instead of meetings, use Beseda to send videos and audios — both transcribed — and have more time for focused work without distractions. Standups, design reviews, reporting bugs, collecting and giving feedback — the sky&apos;s the limit for the ways to apply.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sofa 3.0 - 用一個地方來安排你的休息時間]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們今天使用的大多數應用程序都是爲工作而設計的。Sofa是爲數不多的有意用於玩耍的生產力應用程序之一。創建應用程序、書籍、棋盤遊戲、電影、電視節目、播客、音樂專輯和視頻遊戲的清單，以便日後享用。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sofa-3-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sofa-3-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 07:21:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Most of the apps we use today are designed for work. Sofa is one of the few productivity apps intentionally intended for play. Create lists of apps, books, board games, movies, tv shows, podcasts, music albums, and video games to enjoy later.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[microletter - 創建你自己的超級簡單的迷你通訊]]></title><description><![CDATA[microletter可以讓你輕鬆地創建自己的通訊。它簡單得不能再簡單，專注於良好的寫作體驗，以及易於使用的界面。microletter是你自己的小編輯通訊的完美選擇。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/microletter</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/microletter</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 07:21:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>microletter makes it easy to create your own newsletter. It is as simple as it gets, focusing on a great writing experience, and an easy-to-use interface. microletter is perfect for your own little editorial newsletter.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ultimate eCommerce Landing Page Template - 在幾分鐘內建立可轉換的登陸頁面]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們明白，建立登陸頁面可能很難，但它們在電子商務中是如此關鍵。Builder.io與Sharma Brands合作，創建了一個易於使用、可定製和高轉化率的登陸頁面。安裝並在不到5分鐘內啓動。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ultimate-ecommerce-landing-page-template</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ultimate-ecommerce-landing-page-template</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 21:33:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We get it, building landing pages can be hard, but they&apos;re so critical in eCommerce. Builder.io partnered with Sharma Brands to create an easy-to-use, customizable, and high-converting landing page. Install and get launched in less than 5 minutes.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pencil - 機器生成的創意平臺]]></title><description><![CDATA[厭倦了爲找到一個成功的廣告而迭代數月？一旦出現創意疲勞，又要重新開始？Pencil使用人工智能從你現有的廣告集中生成全新的廣告，並自動更新，這樣你的設計團隊就可以專注於其他方面。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pencil-77af9051-19fc-4309-b686-1e2deec34ae5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pencil-77af9051-19fc-4309-b686-1e2deec34ae5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 16:15:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Tired of iterating for months to find a winning ad? Only to start all over again once creative fatigue sets in? Pencil uses AI to generate completely new ads from your existing set and updates them automatically so your design team can focus elsewhere.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donut for Hybrid Work - 爲你的混合型團隊架起溝通的橋樑]]></title><description><![CDATA[混合工作的甜甜圈幫助團隊建立關係，公平地獲得成長和麪子的機會，並在混合世界中一起享受樂趣。該版本包括 "最愛 "功能、新的混合型模板和共享頻道中的 "水坑"。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/donut-for-hybrid-work</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/donut-for-hybrid-work</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 15:29:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Donut for Hybrid Work helps teams build relationships, equitably access opportunities for growth and facetime, and have fun together in a hybrid world. Release includes Favorite Things feature, new hybrid-friendly templates, and Watercooler in shared channels.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Litnerd - 教育的皮克斯，K-5學校的閱讀計劃]]></title><description><![CDATA[Litnerd是一個在線課堂閱讀項目，通過將創作者經濟與傳統教育相融合，將書籍帶入生活。程序包括書本的情節重現、ELA課程計劃、課程和電子書。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/litnerd</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/litnerd</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 15:29:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Litnerd is an online classroom reading program that brings books to life by blending the creator economy to traditional education. Programs include episode reenactments of books, ELA lesson plans, curriculum and ebooks.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WhatsApp for Intercom by Octopods - 在您的Intercom收件箱中發送和接收WhatsApp信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[Octopods WhatsApp for Intercom爲您的Intercom收件箱帶來最受歡迎的社交信息渠道。Octopods使用官方的WhatsApp商業API與Intercom進行深度整合，爲您提供Intercom和WhatsApp的優點。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/whatsapp-for-intercom-by-octopods-1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/whatsapp-for-intercom-by-octopods-1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 14:22:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Octopods WhatsApp for Intercom brings the most popular social messaging channel to your Intercom Inbox. Octopods offers a deep integration with Intercom using the official WhatsApp Business API, giving you the best of Intercom and WhatsApp.</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>