<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Product Hunt 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Product Hunt 热门App，网站和产品]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 05:33:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Face On - 把你的臉放在任何東西上]]></title><description><![CDATA[Face on允許你把你的臉放在任何東西上，在任何視頻聊天中推銷你的想法。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/face-on</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/face-on</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 20:36:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Face on allows you to put your face on anything to pitch your idea in any video chat.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Haekka - 用Slack培訓你的員工]]></title><description><![CDATA[在Slack中培訓你的員工。Haekka是一個現代化的培訓平臺，爲熱愛Slack的人服務。帶來你自己的培訓內容或從我們不斷增長的圖書館中選擇。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/haekka</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/haekka</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 20:21:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Train your employees in Slack. Haekka is a modern training platform for people that love Slack. Bring your own training content or choose from our growing library.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MetaSapiens NFT - 第一個AR NFT項目]]></title><description><![CDATA[MetaSapiens是世界上第一個用於蘋果iOS的增強現實NFT項目。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/metasapiens-nft</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/metasapiens-nft</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 19:17:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>MetaSapiens is the world&apos;s first Augmented Reality NFT project for Apple iOS.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Optic Hub - 一體化的光纜集線器擴展器]]></title><description><![CDATA[OPTICHUB是家庭、辦公室、校園、指揮中心、監控室、編輯室或其他地方的任何數字信號情況的完美解決方案，可靈活訂購1至300米的光纜。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/optic-hub</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/optic-hub</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 19:00:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Plug and play cable of optic fiber can be ordered in flexible length from 1 to 300 meters. &amp;nbsp;OPTICHUB is the perfect solution to any digital signal situation at home, office, campus, command center, monitoring room, editing studio or others.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Product Studio Session Templates - 爲產品工作室會議策劃的模板集合]]></title><description><![CDATA[認識一下產品工作室會議模板，這是確保產品符合真實用戶需求的最節省時間的方法。有9個模板可以讓你順利地瞭解產品的想法，幫助你創建一個分步驟的計劃，將你的產品推向市場。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/product-studio-session-templates</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/product-studio-session-templates</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 19:00:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Meet the Product Studio Session Template, the most time-saving way to ensure the product will match the real users’ needs. There are 9 templates for a smooth product idea overview, that help you create a step-by-step plan to bring your product to the market.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reflect 2.0 - 一個無代碼的網絡應用程序測試平臺]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reflect是一個無代碼的、基於雲的平臺，用於創建端到端的測試。它是爲你的網絡應用創建和維護端到端測試的最快方式。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/reflect-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/reflect-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 18:25:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Reflect is a no-code, cloud-based platform for creating end-to-end tests. It&apos;s the fastest way to create and maintain end-to-end tests for your web app.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Designing Growth - 每週爲您的收件箱提供創業公司設計和增長方面的見解]]></title><description><![CDATA[加入其他創始人的行列，每週將精心策劃的初創企業設計和成長見解直接送到您的收件箱。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/designing-growth</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/designing-growth</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 15:24:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Join other founders and get weekly, curated startup design &amp; growth insight delivered straight to your inbox.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NFT Header for Twitter - 自動更新顯示你最新的NFTs的Twitter標題]]></title><description><![CDATA[一個免費的工具，可以自動更新你的Twitter個人資料標題，顯示你錢包裏的新NFT✨ 選擇我們的設計之一，定製它，或創建你自己的模板]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nft-header-for-twitter</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nft-header-for-twitter</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:22:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A free tool that automatically updates your Twitter profile header to show new NFTs in your wallet ✨ Choose one of our designs, customize it, or create your own template!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mutiny 3.0 - 將你的網站變成你的第一收入渠道]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mutiny是一個沒有代碼的人工智能平臺，爲B2B營銷人員提供他們所需要的一切，以個性化他們的網站，並轉化99%的跳出流量--從識別訪客到人工智能驅動的推薦和內容編寫。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mutiny-3-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mutiny-3-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 13:04:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Mutiny is a no-code AI platform that gives B2B marketers everything they need to personalize their website and convert the 99% of traffic that bounces — from identifying visitors to AI-powered recommendations and content writing.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Product Superstories - 100多個精心策劃的產品問題，由專家PM回答]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Product Folks & Amplitude的《產品的超級故事》是一個不爲人知的故事集，其中充滿了來自微軟、亞馬遜、Booking等公司幾十年產品經驗的見解。它揭開了產品經理旅程的有趣一面。閱讀愉快!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/product-superstories</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/product-superstories</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 13:04:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Product Superstories by The Product Folks &amp; Amplitude is a collection of untold stories filled with insights from decades of product experience at Microsoft, Amazon, Booking &amp; more. It uncovers interesting aspects of a product manager&apos;s journey. Happy reading!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Compete - 關於科技界報酬數據的即時洞察力]]></title><description><![CDATA[Compete使科技界的人力資源和財務領導能夠立即瞭解完整的薪酬方案數據。Compete得到了數百家領先科技公司的信任，它通過與市場的實時福利基準進行比較，使人們不再猜測。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/compete-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/compete-2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 11:45:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Compete empowers HR &amp; Finance leaders in tech with immediate insights into complete compensation package data. Trusted by hundreds of the leading tech companies, Compete takes the guess out of guesswork with real-time benefit benchmarks compared to the market.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Driwwwle - 就像Dribbble一樣，但爲開發者服務]]></title><description><![CDATA[Driwwwle是一個開源的社交平臺，供開發者展示他們的項目並結識全球各地的創意開發者。創建一個免費賬戶，爲你的項目獲得更多的知名度，認識新的開發者，並獲得啓發。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/driwwwle</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/driwwwle</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 11:45:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Driwwwle is an open-source social platform for developers to showcase their projects and meet creative developers across the globe. Create a free account to gain more visibility for your projects, meet new developers, and get inspired.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Voicl - 在你的網站上嵌入語音提示]]></title><description><![CDATA[有了Voicl，你可以輕鬆地將語音筆記嵌入到你的網站。以更個人化的方式與您的用戶互動，提供內容摘要、額外信息和CTA--使用您自己的聲音!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/voicl</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/voicl</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 11:45:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With Voicl you can easily embed voice notes onto your website. Engage with your users in a much more personal way, provide content summaries, extra information and CTA&apos;s - using your OWN voice!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[StoriesOnBoard Feedback Management - 以客戶反饋爲動力的整體產品管理]]></title><description><![CDATA[StoriesOnBoard反饋管理收集來自客戶、用戶和你的團隊的產品反饋到一個單一的存儲庫，並根據你創建的規則爲你組織這些反饋。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/storiesonboard-feedback-management</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/storiesonboard-feedback-management</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 10:45:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>StoriesOnBoard Feedback Management gathers product feedback from customers, users &amp; your team into a single repository and organizes them for you based on rules you create.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AppFollow 7.0 - 從一個地方開啓產品洞察力並管理應用程序評論]]></title><description><![CDATA[AppFollow爲您提供工具，將客戶評論轉化爲客戶對您的應用程序的滿意度。它自動將您和您的競爭對手的反饋劃分爲有用的類別和指標，產品和營銷部門可以用它來建立一個更好的應用程序並推動增長。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/appfollow-7-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/appfollow-7-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 10:30:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>AppFollow gives you the tools to turn customer reviews into customer satisfaction for your app. It automatically segments your &amp; your competitors’ feedback into useful categories &amp; metrics that product &amp; marketing can use to build a better app &amp; drive growth.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GetAcquired Startup Marketplace - 初創企業市場 - 對買家和賣家免費開放]]></title><description><![CDATA[GetAcquired是購買和銷售初創企業的現代市場。在OpenAI的支持下，我們的列表編輯器讓您在幾分鐘內進入市場。訪問2年的列表數據。我們的顧問市場幫助您建立您的交易團隊。對賣家和買家免費。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/getacquired-startup-marketplace</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/getacquired-startup-marketplace</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 10:30:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>GetAcquired is the modern marketplace for buying &amp; selling startups. Powered by OpenAI, our listing editor gets you to market in minutes. Access 2 years worth of listings data. Our Advisor Marketplace helps you build your deal team. Free for Sellers &amp; Buyers.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Embeddinghub - 一個用於機器學習的開源數據庫]]></title><description><![CDATA[Embeddinghub是一個用於機器學習嵌入的開源矢量數據庫。大多數現代機器學習是建立在嵌入之上的，而Embeddinghub是從頭開始建立的，以使你的ML模型走出實驗室，進入生產。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/embeddinghub</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/embeddinghub</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 10:05:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Embeddinghub is an open-source vector database for machine learning embeddings. Most modern machine learning is built atop embeddings, and Embeddinghub is built from the ground up to get your ML models out of the lab and into production.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tactiq 2.0 - 保持專注，讓Tactiq記錄你的會議]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tactiq 2.0可轉錄Google Meets和Zoom網絡電話，然後爲您創建筆記🙏 v2.0 + 自動高亮和自動彙總 + 帶時間戳的轉錄本，包括髮言者 + 會議參與 + Notion, Quip, Dropbox, Slack等 + 西班牙語、法語、德語、葡萄牙語]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tactiq-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tactiq-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 09:00:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Tactiq 2.0 transcribes Google Meets &amp; Zoom Web calls, then creates notes for you 🙏 v2.0 + auto-highlights &amp; auto-summaries + time-stamped transcripts w/ speakers + Meeting engagement + Notion, Quip, Dropbox, Slack &amp; more + Spanish, French, German, Portuguese</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[EtherFly by The Explorers (Beta) - 探索移動端上最熱門的3D遊戲元數據]]></title><description><![CDATA[📲 在iOS上下載EtherFly測試版 🦋 探索一個3D世界，其中顯示EtherFly NFT，並直接鏈接到他們的OpenSea頁面 🪐 EtherFly是The Explorers的一部分，這是一個下一代的在線元空間，在這裏你可以與你的朋友一起探索、遊戲賺錢並獲得樂趣。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/etherfly-by-the-explorers-beta</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/etherfly-by-the-explorers-beta</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 08:45:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>📲 Download EtherFly Beta on iOS 🦋 Explore a 3D World where EtherFly NFTs are displayed with a direct link to their OpenSea page 🪐 EtherFly is part of The Explorers, a next-gen online metaverse where you explore, Play-to-Earn and have fun with your friends.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GETitOUT - 像專家一樣生成營銷文本和網站]]></title><description><![CDATA[建立一個強大的營銷基礎，吸引你的理想客戶。輕鬆創建買方角色，將功能轉化爲利益，並生成網站和電子郵件--在你的設計中完成文本和佈局。是營銷自由職業者和初創企業的理想選擇。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/getitout</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/getitout</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 08:27:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Build a strong marketing foundation to attract your ideal clients: Easily create buyer personas, turn features into benefits, and generate websites and emails - complete with texts and layout, in your design. Ideal for marketing freelancers and startups.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lightstep Incident Response - 你需要的背景和自動化，以快速響應事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lightstep Incident Response是最新的事件響應平臺，旨在讓您的團隊領先正常運行時間的威脅兩步。積極主動地減少事故，建立長期的服務彈性，使您的團隊能夠更快地創新和自信地發佈。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/lightstep-incident-response</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/lightstep-incident-response</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 08:27:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Lightstep Incident Response is the newest incident response platform, built to keep your team two steps ahead of uptime threats. Proactively minimize incidents and build long-term service resiliency so your team can innovate faster and release confidently.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kaspr - 即時獲得你的潛在客戶的電話號碼和電子郵件]]></title><description><![CDATA[即時獲取你的潛在客戶的電話號碼和電子郵件。用真實的數據轉換線索，節省時間。與我們的競爭對手相比，我們找到的電話號碼是他們的2倍!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/kaspr</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/kaspr</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 08:00:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Get access to your prospects’ phone numbers and email, instantly. Convert leads with real data and save time. We find 2 times the amount of phone numbers in comparison to our competitors!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mini Course Generator - 創建迷你課程進行營銷的最快方法]]></title><description><![CDATA[1. 用各種內容類型超快地創建一個迷你課程 2. 2.獲得其鏈接，以便在你的社交網絡中分享，並無障礙地嵌入你的網站 3.展示你的迷你課程，不需要任何用戶名和密碼，開始給你的觀衆留下深刻印象]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mini-course-generator</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mini-course-generator</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 08:00:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>1. Create a mini-course super-fast with various content types 2. Get its link to share in your social network and embed in your website hassle-free 3. Present your mini-course without any need for a username and password to start impressing your audience</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Financial Freedom Calculator - 你能在經濟上獨立多長時間？]]></title><description><![CDATA[財務獨立是夢想。根據你的儲蓄和每月開支，你離實現這個夢想還有多遠？或者你的目標應該是什麼？通過這個來自Maybe的免費計算器來了解一下吧!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/financial-freedom-calculator</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/financial-freedom-calculator</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 07:22:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Financial independence is the dream. Based on your savings and monthly expenses, how close are you to making it? Or what should your goal be? Find out with this free calculator from Maybe!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Flyyer - 管理和自動化響應式鏈接預覽]]></title><description><![CDATA[Flyyer是一個SaaS、CDN和開發工具包，使人們能夠在社交媒體上分享之前管理、預覽和自動處理他們網站的鏈接預覽。預計點擊率會增加57%，並通過分享分析做出更好的決定。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/flyyer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/flyyer</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 07:22:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Flyyer is a SaaS, CDN and development toolkit that enables people to manage, preview and automate their website&apos;s link previews before they are shared on social media. Expect CTR increase by 57% and make better decisions with sharing analytics.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tokyo Degenerates - 活在以太坊區塊鏈上的動漫式收藏品]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Tokyo Degenerates是一個由10,000個獨特的動漫風格數字收藏品組成的高級收藏品，生活在以太坊區塊鏈上。我們的最終目標是創建一個以每個收藏品爲特色的動漫系列，並將該系列作爲NFTs發行。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tokyo-degenerates</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tokyo-degenerates</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 07:22:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The Tokyo Degenerates are a premium collection of 10,000 unique anime style digital collectibles living on the Ethereum blockchain. Our ultimate goal is to create an anime series featuring each collectible and distributing the series as NFTs.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YC Interviewer - 你準備好接受投資者的採訪了嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[你準備好接受投資者的採訪了嗎？在任何地方練習你的演講，並找出你的超能力💪🏻爲YC創業加速器的面試過程而設計。用❤️在烏克蘭製造 🇺🇦]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/yc-interviewer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/yc-interviewer</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 07:22:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Are you ready for an interview with investors? Practice your speech anywhere and figure out what your superpower is 💪🏻 Designed for the interview process at YC startup accelerator. Made with ❤️ in Ukraine 🇺🇦</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[onetask - 在幾個小時內貼上標籤的人工智能訓練數據，一個下午就能完成10萬+。]]></title><description><![CDATA[有了onetask，你可以自己給大規模的AI訓練數據貼上標籤。我們把弱監督和主動學習結合起來，這樣你就可以很容易地在數據中找到模式，只用手來標註需要人類認知的記錄。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/onetask</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/onetask</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 22:24:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With onetask, you can label AI training data on large-scale yourself. We combine Weak Supervision and Active Learning, so that you can easily find patterns in your data and only label records by hand that need human cognition.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Flowrift - 設計精美的Tailwind CSS用戶界面塊]]></title><description><![CDATA[Flowrift是一個由設計精美的Tailwind CSS UI塊組成的庫。所有的塊都與Tailwind CSS的默認配置一起工作。大處着眼，小處着手：將區塊相互堆疊以建立全頁面佈局，或有選擇地複製小的代碼片段。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/flowrift</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/flowrift</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 19:18:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Flowrift is a library made of beautifully designed Tailwind CSS UI blocks. All blocks work with Tailwind CSS&apos; default configuration. Go big or go small: Stack blocks on top of each other to build full-page layouts, or selectively copy small code snippets.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Discovery by Publicfast - 在幾分鐘內爲你的活動尋找完美的影響者]]></title><description><![CDATA[Discovery by Publicfast是一個自動化的解決方案，通過類別、標籤、關鍵詞、地點進行搜索，以10倍的速度找到結果，從而找到您的完美創作者和影響者。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/discovery-by-publicfast</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/discovery-by-publicfast</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 16:25:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Discovery by Publicfast is an automated solution to search through categories, hashtags, keywords, locations to find results 10x faster to find your perfect creators and influencers.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Height - 一體化的項目管理]]></title><description><![CDATA[高度是你整個團隊的一個項目管理工具。- 任務列表使你的團隊保持同步 - 聊天記錄使關於工作的對話保持在一個地方 - 通過Cmd-K、自定義快捷方式和跳轉到閃電般的速度 - 整合自動更新任務]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/height-5378b770-9fd1-4fca-ae73-a4e02d6531a0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/height-5378b770-9fd1-4fca-ae73-a4e02d6531a0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 15:23:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Height is a project management tool for your whole team. - Task lists to keep your team synced - Chats to keep conversations about work in one place - Lightning fast with Cmd-K, custom shortcuts, and jump to - Integrations to automatically update tasks</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[iPNOTE - 保護你的初創企業的知識產權，節省高達90%的費用]]></title><description><![CDATA[使用iPNOTE知識產權管理平臺和市場來獲得商標和專利，同時節省高達90%的法律預算!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ipnote</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ipnote</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 14:31:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Use iPNOTE intellectual management platform and marketplace to get trademarks and patents, while saving up to 90% of your legal budget!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Clipt - 在設備之間無縫傳輸照片、文件和文本]]></title><description><![CDATA[Clipt通過連接你的手機和筆記本剪貼板，在你的設備之間無縫和安全地傳輸文本、照片、視頻和文件。你不應該因爲擁有一個以上的設備而受到懲罰--安裝Clipt，看着你的生產力飆升。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/clipt</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/clipt</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 13:28:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Clipt seamlessly and safely transfers text, photos, videos, and files between your devices by connecting your phone &amp; laptop clipboard. You shouldn&apos;t be punished for having more than one device - install Clipt and watch your productivity soar.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Streak Mail Merge for Gmail - 發送大量的、個性化的電子郵件，並自動跟進]]></title><description><![CDATA[發送帶有後續序列的個性化羣發郵件的最佳方式。👋自動向沒有回覆的收件人發送後續信息 👋看起來和感覺是個人的 ⚠️智能提醒 🔋優化回覆 🏠完全生活在Gmail內部]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/streak-mail-merge-for-gmail</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/streak-mail-merge-for-gmail</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 13:28:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The best way to send personalized mass emails with follow-up sequences: ✨ automatically send follow-ups with recipients who don&apos;t reply 👋 looks and feels personal ⚠️ smart alerts 🔋 optimize for replies 🏠 lives entirely inside Gmail</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reel - 將播客變成視頻並在社交媒體上推廣播客]]></title><description><![CDATA[在你的社交媒體賬戶上用醒目的視頻預告你的播客劇集，吸引新的聽衆。爲你的播客添加字幕。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/reel-5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/reel-5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 13:00:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Tease your podcast episodes on your social media accounts with eye-catching videos and attract new listeners. Add subtitles to your podcasts.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Start - 從世界任何地方啓動和運行你的美國業務]]></title><description><![CDATA[有了Start，你可以從世界任何地方啓動和運行一個美國企業。我們處理您所有的後臺操作。有限責任公司的形成，註冊代理，EIN，商業銀行賬戶，每月記賬，會計和稅收（準備，申報，支付）。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/start-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/start-3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 13:00:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With Start, you can launch and run a US business from anywhere in the world. We handle all your back office operations: LLC formation, registered agent, EIN, business bank account, monthly bookkeeping, accounting and taxes (prep, filing, payment).</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hyper - 出售 Discord 和 Telegram 的會員資格]]></title><description><![CDATA[使用Hyper將你的在線社區變成一個企業。💵銷售對Discord服務器和Telegram羣組的訪問權 🥇爲不同的角色創建多種產品 🔗生成具有靈活定價的購買鏈接 在hyper.co.cn網站上不到5分鐘就能開始。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hyper-2c2cd9da-80f6-4119-bb63-ac09a99a813d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hyper-2c2cd9da-80f6-4119-bb63-ac09a99a813d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 11:16:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Use Hyper to turn your online community into a business. 💵 Sell access to Discord servers and Telegram groups 🥇 Create multiple products for different roles 🔗 Generate purchase links with flexible pricing Get started in under five minutes at hyper.co.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[No-Code App Builders Comparison - 比較最受歡迎的無代碼應用程序構建器的主要功能]]></title><description><![CDATA[最好的無代碼應用開發平臺的廣泛比較圖。Bubble, Webflow, Glide, Thunkable, Adalo, Bildr, or Wappler - 哪一個最適合你的項目？找出答案!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/no-code-app-builders-comparison</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/no-code-app-builders-comparison</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:26:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Extensive comparison chart of the best no-code app development platforms. Bubble, Webflow, Glide, Thunkable, Adalo, Bildr, or Wappler - which one is a perfect fit for your project? Find out!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[DhiWise - 立即爲網絡和移動應用程序獲得生產準備的代碼]]></title><description><![CDATA[DhiWise是一個ProCode平臺，可以幫助你立即生成乾淨、可擴展和可定製的Node.js、Android、iOS、Flutter、Laravel和React控制面板的代碼，這些代碼可以在生產中使用，只需幾個高級輸入就可以建立網絡、本地和混合應用程序。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/dhiwise-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/dhiwise-2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 09:46:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>DhiWise is a ProCode platform that helps you instantly generate clean, scalable &amp; customizable code of Node.js, Android, iOS, Flutter, Laravel &amp; React Admin Panel that is production-ready to build web, native &amp; hybrid apps with a few high-level inputs.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MarketMuse Free - 多發表，無畏地發表]]></title><description><![CDATA[MarketMuse是一個內容智能平臺，爲內容質量設定標準。我們的人工智能平臺加速了你的內容研究、創作和優化過程，因此你可以更快、更無畏地發佈。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/marketmuse-free</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/marketmuse-free</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 09:46:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>MarketMuse is a content intelligence platform that sets the standard for content quality. Our AI-powered platform accelerates your content research, creation, and optimization process so you can publish faster and fearlessly.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Airtable Invoice Maker - 超快地創建報價和發票]]></title><description><![CDATA[製作發票不是很無聊嗎？節省您的時間，瞄準您的目標，專注於您擅長的事情 Airtable Invoice Maker可以讓您超快地創建專業的報價和發票PDF。自由職業者和小機構的必備工具。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/airtable-invoice-maker</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/airtable-invoice-maker</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 09:33:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Isn&apos;t it boring to create invoices? Save your time, aim for your goal and focus on what you&apos;re good at! Airtable Invoice Maker lets you create professional quote &amp; invoice PDFs super fast. A must have for freelancers and small agencies.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hyperweb - 多合一的iOS Safari擴展]]></title><description><![CDATA[當你在Safari瀏覽器中瀏覽時，Hyperweb神奇地增強了網絡，自動阻止廣告，駁回彈出窗口，併爲你正在瀏覽的頁面建議智能替代方案。Hyperweb在設備上100%本地運行，建議的增強功能也在不斷增加。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hyperweb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hyperweb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 08:25:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Hyperweb magically enhances the web as you browse in Safari, automatically blocking ads, dismissing popups and suggesting smart alternatives to the page you&apos;re on. Hyperweb runs 100% locally on device and suggested enhancements are ever growing.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ponicode CLI - 通過AI單元測試的生成實現高的代碼質量]]></title><description><![CDATA[由於有了人工智能，現在可以直接從你的命令行中實現更快的軟件開發、更強大的代碼和高代碼覆蓋率。爲你的TS、JS和Python項目批量生成單元測試，提供最相關的測試場景。控制Bug 🎉]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ponicode-cli</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ponicode-cli</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 08:25:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Faster software development, more robust code &amp; high code coverage directly from your command line are now possible thanks to AI. Generate unit tests in bulk for your TS, JS &amp; Python projects with the most relevant test scenarios. Keep bugs under control 🎉</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Punchlist - 在網站、圖像和PDF上面的反饋層]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲你所有的創意工作提供反饋層。⠀ 分享一個網址，看所有的內容和設計的變化都是實時的，直接在你的作品上添加。⠀ 與⠀ 💻 實時網站 🌄 圖片 📁 PDF ⠀ 無限項目、評論和合作者 ⠀ 永久免費]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/punchlist</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/punchlist</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 08:25:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The feedback layer for all your creative work. ⠀ Share one url, and watch all content and design changes added in real time, directly on your work. ⠀ Works with ⠀ 💻 Live websites 🌄 Images 📁 PDFs ⠀ Unlimited projects, comments, &amp; collaborators ⠀ Free forever</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Railway - 免費部署配置：帶上你的代碼，其餘的由我們來處理。]]></title><description><![CDATA[適用於任何語言，爲大大小小的項目而製造。Railway是將運輸軟件的複雜性排除在外的雲。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/railway</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/railway</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 08:25:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Made for any language, for projects big and small. Railway is the cloud that takes the complexity out of shipping software.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Usersnap - 獲得可操作的客戶反饋以實現增長]]></title><description><![CDATA[Usersnap是一個客戶反饋軟件，用於增加用戶的反饋，以及集中處理問題和請求。通過對用戶屏幕記錄和滿意度小型調查的洞察，推出更好的產品功能。在20分鐘內開始使用 🚀]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/usersnap-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/usersnap-2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 08:25:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Usersnap is a customer feedback software to increase feedback from your users, as well as centralize issues and requests. Ship better product features with insights from user screen recordings and satisfaction mini-surveys. Get started within 20 minutes 🚀</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[LetterHunt - 10,000多份活躍的、精心策劃的新聞簡報，以推廣您的產品]]></title><description><![CDATA[LetterHunt將你與10,000多個利基、活躍的通訊作者聯繫起來，以推廣你的產品。尋找並與你的利基新聞通訊合作，爲你的產品/服務的營銷開闢一條新途徑。新聞通訊與參與度統計一起被分類 🙌]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/letterhunt</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/letterhunt</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 07:31:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>LetterHunt connects you to 10,000+ niche, active newsletter writers to promote your product. Find and partner with newsletters in your niche and unlock a new avenue for marketing your product/service. Newsletters are categorized along with engagement stats 🙌</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[IdeaOnce - 易於使用的免費在線圖形設計平臺]]></title><description><![CDATA[IdeaOnce是一個免費的圖形設計平臺，幫助專業和非設計人員輕鬆快速地創建令人驚歎的設計。https://design.ideaonce.com。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ideaonce</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ideaonce</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 07:17:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>IdeaOnce is a FREE Graphic Designing platform that helps both professional and non-designers create amazing designs easily and quickly. https://design.ideaonce.com</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Perform - 你的智能健身DJ]]></title><description><![CDATA[Perform的人工智能驅動的音樂鍛鍊對心率和節奏等實時輸入作出反應，以改善運動。經過近10萬次鍛鍊和100萬首歌曲聆聽的訓練，Perform知道在你鍛鍊的每一時刻使用正確的歌曲，以使鍛鍊效果最大化。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/perform</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/perform</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 07:17:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Perform&apos;s AI-powered music workouts respond to real-time inputs like heart rate and pace to improve exercise. Trained on nearly 100k workouts and 1M song listens, Perform knows the right song for every moment of your workout to maximize results.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stoa - 古代哲學和冥想應用程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[斯多亞將古老的斯多亞哲學與正念冥想結合在一個實用的冥想應用程序中。加入數以千計的人，用它來練習斯多葛的紀律，變得更平靜、更有彈性和更有德行。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/stoa-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/stoa-2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 01:37:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Stoa combines the ancient philosophy of Stoicism with mindfulness meditation in a practical meditation app. Join thousands by using it to practice the Stoic disciplines and becoming calmer, more resilient, and virtuous.</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>