<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Product Hunt 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Product Hunt 热门App，网站和产品]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 01:51:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[College Compendium - 爲好奇的人收集了650多門大學CS課程]]></title><description><![CDATA[最好的產品是由那些擁有最好知識的人建造的。通過衆包彙編的650多門頂級大學的CS課程，建立你的信息庫，探索你的知識好奇心。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/college-compendium</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/college-compendium</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 22:00:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The best products are built by those equipped with the best knowledge. Build your information base and explore your intellectual curiousity through a crowdsourced compilation of 650+ CS courses from top universities.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AutoComplete - 打字更快，讓AI完成你的句子]]></title><description><![CDATA[在任何文本框中，Chrome都可以自動完成你的句子。由人工智能驅動的句子完成，可在任何網頁的任何文本區域工作。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/autocomplete</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/autocomplete</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 20:12:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Chrome ext to autocomplete your sentences in any text box. AI powered sentence completion that works in any text area on any web page.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ShareDrop - 在設備之間共享文件，而不需要將它們上傳到服務器。]]></title><description><![CDATA[ShareDrop是一個免費的網絡應用，它允許你在設備之間輕鬆和安全地直接分享文件，而無需先將它們上傳到任何服務器。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sharedrop-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sharedrop-2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 19:45:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>ShareDrop is a free web app that allows you to easily and securely share files directly between devices without uploading them to any server first.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Digital Design Talks - 向世界各地的設計領袖學習]]></title><description><![CDATA[🚨 與有抱負的人分享偉大設計師的知識 🥰 每週都有新的採訪，社區建議的問題會在我們的採訪中加入。✨ 從這些對行業有影響的人的集體經驗中學習!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/digital-design-talks</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/digital-design-talks</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 16:36:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>🚨 Sharing the knowledge of great designers with the aspiring ones 🥰 New interview coming weekly with community suggested questions being added as we go. ✨ Learn from the collective experience of these industry shaping people!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Notion Party Planners - 使用Notion計劃您的所有活動]]></title><description><![CDATA[一個由3個模板組成的派對計劃包，可以計劃你所有的活動 在這個模板中，你可以得到 - 💸預算計劃器 🎈主題靈感 🌮供應商細節 📝待辦事項與協作功能 🎮遊戲派對模板 👰婚禮計劃模板 🍨食譜創意]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/notion-party-planners</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/notion-party-planners</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 13:38:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A party planning pack of 3 templates that plans out all your events In this template you get - 💸Budget planner 🎈Theme inspirations 🌮Vendor details 📝To-do list with collaborative features 🎮Game party template 👰Wedding planner template 🍨Recipe ideas</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Super Portfolio - 爲自己創建一個超級強大的投資組合頁面]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲自己創建一個超級強大的投資組合頁面 ⚡️ 所有你的在線展示都在一個地方 🥳 一個簡單的方法，使你的投資組合網站；生物，日曆，故事，鏈接，視頻，項目，工具棧和更多的東西在一個地方。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/super-portfolio</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/super-portfolio</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 10:11:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Create a super powered portfolio page for yourself ⚡️ All your online presence in one place 🥳 An easy way to make your portfolio website; bio, calendar, story, links, videos, projects, tool stack and many more in one place.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[QR Code Generator by Logaster - 在幾秒鐘內爲您的企業提供QR碼]]></title><description><![CDATA[現在，您可以在短時間內用Logaster創建QR-Code。你只需要： - 輸入公司或品牌的名稱 - 選擇一個商業領域 - 插入一個你想分享的鏈接 - 選擇QR-code樣式並點擊下載。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/qr-code-generator-by-logaster</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/qr-code-generator-by-logaster</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 02:28:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Now you can create QR-Code with Logaster in no time. All you need to do is just: - Type the name of the company or brand - Choose a business field - Insert a link you want to share - Select the QR-code style and click Download.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cookie Popup Blocker - 擺脫惱人的cookie彈出窗口]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://world.hey.com/nasir/cookie-popups-have-ruined-the-web-fdaee6fe，並使用戶體驗變得糟糕。Cookie Popup Blocker是一個免費和開源的Chrome擴展，可以在不同意任何法律條款的情況下刪除瀏覽器中的cookie彈出窗口。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/cookie-popup-blocker</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/cookie-popup-blocker</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 00:25:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>https://world.hey.com/nasir/cookie-popups-have-ruined-the-web-fdaee6fe and madee the user experience terrible. Cookie Popup Blocker is a free and open source Chrome extension that removes cookie popups in your browser without agreeing to any of the legal terms.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Primer Rooms - 與世界各地的孩子們進行現場互動體驗]]></title><description><![CDATA[Primer Rooms是現場互動的音頻體驗，世界各地有抱負的孩子在這裏探索他們的興趣，解決問題，並一起創造。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/primer-rooms</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/primer-rooms</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 00:25:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Primer Rooms are live, interactive audio experiences where ambitious kids around the world explore their interests, solve problems, and create together.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Interial - 人工智能網絡應用提高視頻幀率，使其更加流暢]]></title><description><![CDATA[Interial增強了你提供的視頻的幀率，這取決於你的選擇。Interial目前允許你做2倍或4倍的增強，這將大大改善你的視頻的幀率，使其更加流暢。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/interial</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/interial</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 18:33:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Interial enhances the frame rate of the video that you provided depending on your choosing. Interial currently allows you to do 2X or 4X enhancement which will significantly improve the frame rate of your video making it much smoother.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Copyhat - 用你的人工智能翅膀機器人告別無聊的Tinder開場白]]></title><description><![CDATA[六個月前，我們要求GPT-3生成Tinder的開場白，然後將其捆綁成一本書。他們很有趣，而且出乎意料地實用。現在有了Copyhat，你也可以把這個強大的語言模型作爲你口袋裏的一個僚機。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/copyhat</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/copyhat</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 14:13:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Six months ago, we asked GPT-3 to generate Tinder openers that we then bundled into a book. They were funny and surprisingly practical. Now with Copyhat, you can also have this powerful language model as a wingman in your pocket.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[VitaDAO - 分散的集體資助長壽研究]]></title><description><![CDATA[VitaDAO是一個分散的集體，資助早期的長壽研究。我們的使命是以開放和民主的方式，通過研究、資助和商業化長壽療法來延長人類的壽命。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/vitadao</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/vitadao</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 13:42:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>VitaDAO is a decentralized collective funding early stage longevity research. Our mission is to extend human lifespan by researching, financing, and commercializing longevity therapeutics in an open and democratic manner.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[EDGE - 第一個模塊化的在家工作套件]]></title><description><![CDATA[你的工作站，在任何地方。EDGE是筆記本電腦和平板電腦的終極配件，可以在你在家工作時提高生產力。⠀ 始終將需要的信息放在眼睛的高度，減少分心，爲你的手機充電，照亮你的會議。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/edge-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/edge-2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 13:13:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Your workstation, anywhere. EDGE is the ultimate laptop and tablet accessory to boost productivity while you work from home. ⠀ Always have the needed information at eye level, reduce distractions, charge your phone and light up your meetings.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[dewey. - 充分利用你的Twitter書籤]]></title><description><![CDATA[有了dewey.你可以抓取你現有的所有Twitter書籤，搜索、分類、標記、創建和分享收藏，是的，甚至可以將你的Twitter書籤導出到你最喜歡的記事應用程序。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/dewey-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/dewey-3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 13:13:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With dewey. you can grab all of your existing Twitter Bookmarks, search, sort, tag, create and share collections, and yes even export your Twitter Bookmarks to your favorite note-taking app.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[FEED - 第一個用於聯合流媒體視頻內容的社交網絡]]></title><description><![CDATA[FEED是一款新的社交視頻應用，讓想法的分享變得更加有趣! 在任何地方，與任何人實時交談，並製作集體電影。不用再打字了--FEED的聯合流媒體功能是聊天和合作的新方式。分享你的想法；今天就加入一個新的feed!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/feed-5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/feed-5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 11:18:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>FEED is the new social video app that makes idea-sharing more fun! Talk to anyone, anywhere, in real-time, &amp; make collective movies. No more typing - FEED’s co-streaming function is the new way to chat &amp; collaborate. Share your ideas; join a new feed today!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Apostrophe 3.0 - 一個建立在開源CMS上的強大的網站建設者]]></title><description><![CDATA[一個強大的網站建設者，建立在一個開源的CMS上，提供實時編輯和動態視覺設計工具，並支持多站點。一個在全堆棧JS環境中的可擴展和模塊化系統，可用於傳統或無頭部署。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/apostrophe-3-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/apostrophe-3-0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 10:00:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A powerful website builder built on an open source CMS, offering in-context live editing and dynamic visual design tools with multisite enablement. An extensible and modular system in a full stack JS environment ready for traditional or headless deployment.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Notion Portfolio - 使用Notion創建一個專業的作品集]]></title><description><![CDATA[一個Notion模板，在短短几分鐘內建立你的作品集。🖥️ 展示你的工作 ✍️ 自定義所有內容 🖥️ 鏈接到社交網絡檔案 🎙️ 分享你的不同項目，專業經驗，你最好的內容和播客集]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/notion-portfolio</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/notion-portfolio</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 09:48:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A Notion template to build your portfolio in just a few minutes. 🖥️ Showcase your work ✍️ Customize all the content 📱 Link to social networks profiles 🎙️ Share your different projects, professional experiences, your best content and podcast episodes</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Battlecard - 授予顛覆性公司的銷售技術積分]]></title><description><![CDATA[最好的銷售工具希望與具有最大長期價值的初創企業合作。如果你是一個追求大市場的顛覆者，我們將爲你指出成功所需的確切工具，加上免費的信貸，使你的投資回報率最大化。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/battlecard-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/battlecard-2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 07:26:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The best sales tools want to work with startups with the largest long-term value. If you&apos;re a disruptor going after a big market, we&apos;ll point you toward exactly the tools you need to succeed, plus free credits to maximize your ROI.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Annie Music - 分享好音樂的最簡單方式]]></title><description><![CDATA[安妮音樂使你能夠在一個鏈接中分享你在所有流媒體平臺上最喜歡的歌曲。現在，你的朋友可以享受你最喜歡的歌曲，而不需要通過谷歌搜索來尋找鏈接。只要與安妮分享，就可以了]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/annie-music</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/annie-music</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 07:00:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Annie Music enables you share your favorite songs from all streaming platforms, within one link. Now your friends can enjoy your favorite songs without tons of google search to find the link. Just share with annie and voila!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Podpage 2.0 - 即時播客網站，以盈利和吸引聽衆。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Podpage 2.0配備了先進的貨幣化工具、與聽衆聯繫的更好方式、整合平臺、嘉賓管理、多用戶和多播客賬戶，以及完全重新設計的用戶儀表盤。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/podpage-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/podpage-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 22:09:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Podpage 2.0 comes with advanced monetization tools, better ways to connect with your listeners, an integration platform, guest management, multi-user and multi-podcast accounts, and a totally redesigned user dashboard.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Learney - 用知識圖譜進行個性化的科技學習]]></title><description><![CDATA[李爾尼通過社區建立的知識圖譜，根據你的知識和興趣，爲你規劃最佳路徑，從而節省你的時間。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/learney-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/learney-2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 21:24:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Learney saves you time by planning the optimal path for you through community-built knowledge graphs, given your knowledge and interests.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[jebra - 實現複雜工作流程的自動化]]></title><description><![CDATA[一個具有2個模塊的數據管理軟件。(1) 一個連接第三方API的數據交換。這個現在在內部使用，不久也會用於外部開發者。(2) 一個分析工作區，使Jebra團隊能夠自動化複雜的工作流程。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/jebra</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/jebra</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 19:22:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A data management software with 2 modules: (1) A data exchange that connects third-party APIs. This is used in-house now and soon for external developers. (2) An analytics workspace that enables the Jebra team to automate complex workflows.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Maker Stations - 來自全球各地製造商的家庭辦公室設置]]></title><description><![CDATA[Maker Stations是一份致力於鼓舞人心的家庭辦公室和用心生活的出版物。我們從世界各地的創客那裏策劃了美麗而實用的家庭辦公室設置。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/maker-stations</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/maker-stations</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 17:52:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Maker Stations is a publication dedicated to inspirational home offices and mindful living. We curate beautiful &amp; functional home office setups from makers around the world.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Namify - 有意義的品牌名稱，免費的標誌，社會和域名檢查]]></title><description><![CDATA[Namify.tech是一個直觀的企業名稱生成器，它試圖理解你的搜索的本質，並建議實際可用的名稱，1000個朗朗上口和有意義的品牌名稱的想法 ✅社會手柄可用性 ✅域名可用性 ✅免費標誌 ✅]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/namify</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/namify</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 16:41:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Namify.tech is an intuitive business name generator that tries to understand the essence of your search and suggests names that are actually usable 1000s of catchy &amp; meaningful brand name ideas ✅ Social handle availability ✅ Domain availability ✅ Free logo ✅</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Captivate 2.0 - 你需要的每一個工具來啓動、管理和盈利你的播客]]></title><description><![CDATA[以最簡單、最流暢的方式創建、管理和擴展你的播客。2.0版包括一個完全革新的儀表盤、簡化的工作流程、糟糕的推廣工具、甚至更多的可定製元素，併爲未來的更多工作奠定了基礎。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/captivate-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/captivate-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 14:30:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Create, manage and scale your podcast in the simplest, slickest way possible. 2.0 includes a completely overhauled dashboard, simplified workflows, badass promotional tools, even more customizable elements and lays the groundwork for more to come.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Realm - 你需要導航擁有房子的所有數據]]></title><description><![CDATA[Realm正在爲您的房子建立一個現代財務顧問。您的免費Realm賬戶包括對當前和潛在房屋價值的分析，對裝修項目的準確成本和投資回報率的估計，以及根據預算和目標確定優先次序的工具。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/realm-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/realm-2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 14:30:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Realm is building a modern financial advisor for your house. Your free Realm account includes an analysis of current and potential home value, accurate costs &amp; ROI estimates for renovation projects, and tools to prioritize based on budget &amp; goals.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Refinery Website Editor - 在任何地方立即改進你的文案]]></title><description><![CDATA[Refinery可以在任何地方改進你的文案，無論是靜態網站還是React應用程序。獲得人工智能生成的建議，在瀏覽器中進行編輯，併發布它們。PM、創始人和營銷人員使用Refinery來進行文案調整，而不必麻煩工程師。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/refinery-website-editor</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/refinery-website-editor</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 14:12:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Refinery improves your copy anywhere, whether it’s a static website or a React app. Get AI generated suggestions, make edits in-browser, and publish them. Refinery is used by PMs, founders, &amp; marketers to make copy tweaks without bothering engineers.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Notionery Automation Recipes - Notion中獨立黑客和無代碼者的自動化配方]]></title><description><![CDATA[在Notion中爲獨立黑客和無代碼者提供的Zapier自動化配方的集合。只需點擊幾下就能實現自動化，每週可節省8個多小時。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/notionery-automation-recipes</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/notionery-automation-recipes</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 13:41:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A collection of Zapier automation recipes for indie hackers and no-coders made in Notion. Enable automations with a single click in seconds and save 8+ hours every week.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[No CS Degree Community - 加入一個自學成才的開發者社區]]></title><description><![CDATA[加入一個支持自學成才和訓練營的開發者的社區。我們與有經驗的開發者進行語音通話AMA，你可以向他們提出任何關於學習代碼、獲得聘用或如何成爲一個更好的開發者的問題。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/no-cs-degree-community</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/no-cs-degree-community</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 13:11:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Join a supportive community for self-taught and bootcamp developers. We do voice call AMAs with experienced developers were you can ask them anything you like about learning to code, getting hired or how to be a better developer.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tability - 簡化你的OKRs，實現目標跟蹤的自動化]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tability是一種更智能、更簡單的方式，讓團隊圍繞結果保持一致，而不會讓人覺得這是一件苦差事。以一種簡單易行的方式計劃、跟蹤和實現你的目標--所有這些都來自一個地方。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tability-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tability-2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 12:36:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Tability is a smarter, simpler way for teams to stay aligned around outcomes without making it feel like a chore. Plan, track &amp; work on your goals in a simple and easy way – all from one place.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Resume - 10+ 免費的Figma簡歷模板]]></title><description><![CDATA[下載10多個免費的高質量Figma簡歷模板]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/resume</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/resume</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 12:00:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Download 10+ free high-quality resume templates for Figma</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ViaSocket EBL - 低代碼定製工作流程自動化工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[ViaSocket EBL允許您通過將多個應用程序與您的數據源無縫連接，實現自定義工作流的自動化。它只需要幾分鐘的開發注意力就能實現工作流程的自動化，否則需要開發人員花費數天的時間。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/viasocket-ebl</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/viasocket-ebl</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 11:48:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>ViaSocket EBL allows you to automate your custom workflows by connecting multiple apps with your data source seamlessly. It requires just minutes of dev attention to automate workflows that would otherwise require days of developer work.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Travel Guide by MyLuggage - 在10分鐘的簡報中包含30多個小時的旅行研究]]></title><description><![CDATA[😱 你是否曾經在一個新的地方旅行，感到毫無準備？🙉想象一下，在你的旅行中，經過10分鐘的閱讀，你會覺得自己像個當地人 ⚙ ️獲得關於目的地的綜合和最重要的見解 👉用我們的指南讓你的旅行發揮最大作用]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/travel-guide-by-myluggage</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/travel-guide-by-myluggage</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 10:48:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>😱 Have you ever been on a trip in a new place where you felt unprepared? 🙉 Imagine you feel like a local during your trip after a 10-min read ⚙ ️Get synthesized and most important insights about destinations 👉 Make the most of your trip with our guide</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Super 2.0 - 用Notion的簡單性建立網站]]></title><description><![CDATA[Super 2.0包括一套用Notion建立網站的新功能，包括super.site子域、每頁代碼和SEO設置、密碼保護頁面、實時網站編輯器、自動漂亮URL、RTL語言支持等。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/super-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/super-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 10:28:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Super 2.0 includes a suite of new features to build websites with Notion, including super.site subdomains, per-page code &amp; SEO settings, password-protected pages, live site editor, automatic pretty URLs, RTL language support, and more.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Komodor - Kubernetes原生故障排除平臺]]></title><description><![CDATA[Komodor是一個Kubernetes原生平臺，使開發人員和隨叫隨到的團隊能夠高效、獨立地進行故障排除。通過提供對整個k8s堆棧的所有代碼、配置和第三方應用程序變化的集中查看。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/komodor</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/komodor</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 10:00:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Komodor is a Kubernetes-native platform that empowers developers and on-call teams to troubleshoot efficiently and independently. By providing a centralized view of all code,configurations, and 3rd-party app changes across the entire k8s stack,</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mega Creator - 在幾分鐘內做出專業的圖形]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mega Creator是一個在線圖形應用程序，讓每個人都能創造出令人敬畏的視覺效果，無需特殊技能和昂貴的設計軟件。使用模板或用我們的插圖、照片、圖標、甚至AI生成的臉來創建你自己的模板。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mega-creator</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mega-creator</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 08:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Mega Creator is an online graphic app that lets everyone create awesome visuals without special skills and costly design software. Use templates or create your own with our illustrations, photos, icons, and even AI-generated faces.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Peppertype.ai - 在幾秒鐘內創建更好的內容的最簡單方法。]]></title><description><![CDATA[🚀 使用Peppertype.ai寫得更好、更快! 擁有超過25種驚人的內容類型，包括廣告副本、博客、文案、網站內容、產品描述等等，Peppertype.ai是你唯一需要的內容工具。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/peppertype-ai</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/peppertype-ai</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 08:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>🚀 Write better and faster with Peppertype.ai! With over 25+ amazing content types including Ad copies, blog, copywriting, website content, product descriptions and so much more, Peppertype.ai is the only content tool you&apos;ll need.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ricotta Trivia - 在Slack上爲你的團隊提供小遊戲、破冰遊戲和有趣的遊戲]]></title><description><![CDATA[在Slack上與你的團隊一起玩耍! 玩引人入勝的小遊戲、趣味遊戲和破冰遊戲。- 小遊戲；15k+問題，15+類別 - 免費破冰遊戲 - 培訓、入職的自定義競賽 提供鏈接 - https://www.ricotta.team/trivia?ref=producthunt]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ricotta-trivia</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ricotta-trivia</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 08:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Have fun with your team on Slack! Play engaging trivia, fun games &amp; Icebreakers. - Trivia games; 15k+ questions with 15+ categories - FREE Ice-breaker games - Custom contests for training, onboarding Offer link - https://www.ricotta.team/trivia?ref=producthunt</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GraphCDN - 具有緩存、分析和安全功能的GraphQL CDN]]></title><description><![CDATA[使用GraphCDN擴展、檢查和保護你的GraphQL API。利用我們的 GraphQL 邊緣緩存，將你的源流量減少 95%，通過分析瞭解你的請求，跟蹤你的錯誤，並保護你的 API 免受惡意查詢。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/graphcdn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/graphcdn</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 07:45:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Scale, inspect &amp; protect your GraphQL API with GraphCDN. Reduce your origin traffic by up to 95% with our GraphQL edge cache, get insights about your requests with analytics, track your errors and protect your API from malicious queries.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trustpage - 與客戶建立信任變得更加容易]]></title><description><![CDATA[客戶希望知道他們的數據受到保護。Trustpage使你可以很容易地向他們展示你是如何做到的。採取正確的措施來保護你的業務，並通過一個多合一的信任中心讓你的客戶滿意。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/trustpage</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/trustpage</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 07:29:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Customers want to know their data is protected. Trustpage makes it easy to show them how you do it. Take the right steps to safeguard your business and keep your customers happy with an all-in-one Trust Center.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SocialBook Checker - 批量聯繫YouTube影響者的最簡單方法]]></title><description><![CDATA[尋找優酷網友製作視頻是推廣你的產品和服務的一個超級有效的方法。然而，要與他們取得聯繫並不那麼容易。有了SocialBook checker，你可以從YouTube的搜索結果中直接給數百名優酷網友發郵件。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/socialbook-checker</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/socialbook-checker</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 19:45:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Finding YouTubers to make videos is a super effective way to promote your product and services. However, getting in touch with them is not so easy. With SocialBook checker, you can email hundreds of YouTubers right from the YouTube search result.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Design+Code iOS 2.0 - 學習SwiftUI、React和UI設計，完全重新設計]]></title><description><![CDATA[通過使用Swift、React、Flutter等構建真正的應用程序來學習。完全重新設計，100%使用SwiftUI製作。新功能包括下載、畫中畫、收藏夾、歷史和小工具。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/design-code-ios-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/design-code-ios-2-0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 17:21:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Learn by building real apps using Swift, React, Flutter and more. Completely redesigned and 100% made with SwiftUI. New features include downloads, picture-in-picture, favorites, history and widgets.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Greenroom by Spotify - 現場談論音樂、體育和文化]]></title><description><![CDATA[Spotify的最新應用讓你通過虛擬房間主持和參與現場討論。不需要Spotify賬戶。討論可以被記錄下來，有聊天，發言者可以賺取寶石。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/greenroom-by-spotify</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/greenroom-by-spotify</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 17:21:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Spotify&apos;s latest app letting you host and participate in live discussions through virtual rooms. No Spotify account needed. Discussion can be recorded, there&apos;s chat, and speakers can earn gems.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[UI & UX Checklist - 在Notion模板上學習、練習和檢查UI UX法則]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你們能看看我的第一個模板產品，這將是很可愛和有幫助的。我還將在不久之後推出一份關於創業公司文化創建和管理的濃縮概念文件，其靈感來自Ben Horowitz。謝謝你們對我的支持。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ui-ux-checklist</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ui-ux-checklist</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 17:21:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>It&apos;ll lovely and helpful if you guys will check out my first template-product. I&apos;ll also be launching a condensed notion doc on culture creation and management in a startup inspired by Ben Horowitz soon. Thanks for supporting me guys.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chatterbug Streams - 通過直播課程學習一門新的語言]]></title><description><![CDATA[通過Chatterbug Streams學習新的語言，這是第一款通過互動直播學習西班牙語、法語和德語的應用程序。通過實時測驗和投票，觀看爲您的水平量身定做的類似於Peloton的直播流。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/chatterbug-streams</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/chatterbug-streams</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 16:01:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Learn a new language with Chatterbug Streams, the first app for learning Spanish, French and German through interactive live streams. Watch Peloton-like live streams tailored to your level with real-time quizzes and polls.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cartoon Selfie by Cutout.pro - 自動將你的肖像變成卡通自拍]]></title><description><![CDATA[利用人工智能的魔力，將你的肖像自動變成卡通自拍。現在就上傳自己的肖像，只需輕輕一點，就能把自己變成卡通人物。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/cartoon-selfie-by-cutout-pro</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/cartoon-selfie-by-cutout-pro</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 15:41:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Turn your portrait into cartoon selfie automatically using the magic of Artificial Intelligence. Upload a portrait of yourself now to cartoon yourself in one tap.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AdventureVue - 在線冒險、逃生室、神祕事件和三國演義]]></title><description><![CDATA[錯過了與朋友們的遊戲之夜的靈感？AdventureVue是聊天機器人娛樂的Netflix，以瘋狂的故事和謎團爲特色，將考驗你的邏輯能力，把你的夜晚變成一個冒險。免費玩!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/adventurevue</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/adventurevue</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 15:12:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Missing inspiration for game nights with your friends? AdventureVue is the Netflix for chatbot entertainment, featuring crazy stories and mysteries that will test your logic skills, transforming your night into an adventure. Free to play!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Creators Toolkit - 爲創作者提供250多個工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲了不起的創造者提供的最大的工具集。爲播客、作家、視頻製作者、社區/通訊擁有者和其他驚人的類別找到最佳工具。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/creators-toolkit</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/creators-toolkit</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 15:12:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The Largest Collection of Tools for amazing Creators. Find the best tool for Podcasters, Writers, Video Makers, Community/Newsletter Owners and other amazing categories.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Notion Tools 2.0 - 一個新的Notion應用程序、工具和資源的精心策劃的列表]]></title><description><![CDATA[我大約在6個月前做了Notion工具的https://www.notion.so/Notion-Tools-25d054da911344199cdf403cc04f317c，來自https://www.reddit.com/r/Notion/comments/j2nnhj/a_curated_list_of_notion_third_party_apps_tools/ 和https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K24H6b0msrc 的人幫助我在列表中添加了更多內容。你們還要求我添加更多關於價格的信息，並告訴你們我推薦哪些工具，所以我把它添加到了V2🙌。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/notion-tools-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/notion-tools-2-0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 14:16:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>I made the https://www.notion.so/Notion-Tools-25d054da911344199cdf403cc04f317c of Notion Tools around 6 months ago, and people from https://www.reddit.com/r/Notion/comments/j2nnhj/a_curated_list_of_notion_third_party_apps_tools/ and https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K24H6b0msrc helped me add more to the list. You guys also asked me to add more information about the pricing and to tell you which ones I recommend, so I added it to the V2🙌</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Editr - 自動生成70多種語言的字幕]]></title><description><![CDATA[Editr自動爲你的視頻添加近乎完美的字幕。增強你的視頻，吸引那些在靜音狀態下觀看你內容的人。上傳你的視頻，然後看我們的機器學習和人工智能在幾分鐘內轉錄你的視頻。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/editr</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/editr</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 13:14:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Editr automatically adds near perfect subtitles to your video. Enhance your video and captivate those who watch your content on mute. Upload your video, then watch our machine learning and AI transcribe your video in a matter of minutes.</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>