<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Product Hunt 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Product Hunt 热门App，网站和产品]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 05:15:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[AppSwitcher for Mac - 清洁的应用程序切换。一次只切换一个应用。就像Mac上的iOS。]]></title><description><![CDATA[AppSwitcher为您的应用程序提供漂亮的演示。在类似iOS的Big Sur上。在应用程序之间切换，并切换到，只显示该应用程序。"隐藏其他总是在"。拥有一个干净的桌面+应用程序。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/appswitcher-for-mac</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/appswitcher-for-mac</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 22:14:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>AppSwitcher For Beautiful Presentation of your Apps. On the iOS-like Big Sur. Switch between Apps and Switch to, show only that App. &quot;Hide Others Always On&quot;. Have a Clean Desktop + App.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Polotno SDK - 创建网页设计编辑器的工具包]]></title><description><![CDATA[Polotno SDK是一个JavaScript库和一组React组件，用于在你的Web应用程序中制作画布编辑器。它内置了对模板、谷歌字体、文本样式、图片、视觉编辑等的支持。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/polotno-sdk</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/polotno-sdk</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 20:36:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Polotno SDK is a JavaScript library and set of React components to make canvas editors in your web applications. With built-in support for templates, google fonts, text styles, stock photos, visual edits and more.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Product Library - 1200多个为产品经理策划的资源集合。]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个为产品经理提供的1200多个有价值的网络资源库--根据来源和类型进行了整齐的分类。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/product-library-resources-by-zeda-io</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/product-library-resources-by-zeda-io</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 20:22:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A repository of 1200+ value-packed resources for product managers from the web - neatly categorized based on source and type.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Story Time - 一个帮助你建立认可文化的工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[得到认可的员工比没有得到认可的员工更有动力，更有生产力，也更能投入到要完成的工作中。故事时间 "通过展示人们如何为企业的成功做出贡献，帮助在工作场所创造可见性、认可性和一致性。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/story-time</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/story-time</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 16:20:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Recognised employees are more motivated, productive, and engaged in the work to be done than those who are not. Story Time helps create visibility, recognition, and alignment in the workplace by surfacing how people contribute to the success of the business.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Interial Clarity - AI网络应用，提升和锐化你的图像分辨率]]></title><description><![CDATA[Interial Clarity是一个基于云的工具，帮助你将图像的分辨率放大4倍。Interial利用AI来确保放大过程尽可能准确。此外，Interial Clarity由AWS支持，以确保快速放大过程。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/interial-clarity</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/interial-clarity</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 15:38:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Interial Clarity is a cloud-based tool to help you enlarge your image&apos;s resolution 4X. Interial utilizes AI to make sure that the enlargement process as accurate as possible. In addition, Interial Clarity is backed by AWS to ensure a fast upscaling process.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blobbb Fun - 创建蓬松的blobby SVG形状]]></title><description><![CDATA[Blobbb是设计师和开发人员在线创建他们的blob状形状SVG的有趣新方法。有了Blobbb，你可以在短时间内轻松生成、修改和下载一个漂亮的SVG。享受你的Blobb的乐趣吧! 🥳]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/blobbb-fun</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/blobbb-fun</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 13:53:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Blobbb is the fun new way for designers and developers to create their blob-like shapes SVG online. With Blobbb, you can easily generate, modify, and download a nice-looking SVG in no time. Have fun with your blobs! 🥳</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mastodon for iOS - 去中心化社交网络的官方应用程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[第一个官方的Mastodon应用程序的iOS，有一个抛光的外观和一个重点是易用性。开始使用分散的社交网络Mastodon从来没有这么简单过]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mastodon-for-ios</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mastodon-for-ios</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 09:40:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The first official Mastodon app for iOS, with a polished look and a focus on ease of use. Getting started on the decentralized social network Mastodon has never been more straightforward!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Scispot.io - 面向生命科学团队的无代码工作流自动化平台]]></title><description><![CDATA[Scispot是一个无代码工作流程自动化平台，专为快速成长的生命科学公司设计。生物公司使用Scispot在一个地方管理和跟踪他们的项目、样品和库存。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/scispot-io-1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/scispot-io-1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 18:52:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Scispot is a no-code workflow automation platform designed for fast-growing life science companies. Bio companies use Scispot to manage &amp; track their projects, samples, and inventory all in one spot.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[UniAcquire - 商业买家和卖家的市场!]]></title><description><![CDATA[UniAcquire引入了一种新的买卖公司的方式。这是一个高效的市场，旨在帮助企业主和投资者更快地建立联系，并减少从开始到结束的时间。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/uniacquire</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/uniacquire</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 18:00:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>UniAcquire introduces a new way to buy and sell companies. It’s an efficient and effective marketplace designed to help business owners and investors connect faster, and reduce time from start to finish.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Visited States Map - 创建你自己的互动式受访州/国家地图]]></title><description><![CDATA[标记你访问过的州，并根据你自己的喜好选择颜色。在你的网站上嵌入地图。分享到Facebook、Twitter等，向你的朋友展示你去过的地方。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/visited-states-map</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/visited-states-map</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 16:39:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Mark the states you&apos;ve visited and choose colors to your own liking. Embed the map on your website. Share on Facebook, Twitter, etc., and show your friends where you&apos;ve been.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aura - 用全新的眼光看待你的心情]]></title><description><![CDATA[介绍一下Aura，这是一个易于使用的情绪跟踪应用程序，将你的日常生活情绪考虑在内。它让你更好地了解自己，并帮助你在一天中保持均匀的情绪。该应用程序有各种功能，如统计、图表等。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/aura-b260f046-6bf7-439f-8cd7-8521db48ae46</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/aura-b260f046-6bf7-439f-8cd7-8521db48ae46</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 15:25:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Introducing Aura, an easy to use mood tracking app that takes your daily life&apos;s mood into account. It allows you to understand yourself better and helps you maintain an even mood throughout the day. The app has various features such as statistics, graphs etc.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zine - 获得读者，并在出版前获得直接反馈]]></title><description><![CDATA[想出写作的想法，并弄清楚你的读者是否会喜欢你的作品，这真的很困难。这就是为什么我们建立了Zine，让你在发表前获得读者和直接的写作反馈。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zine-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zine-3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 13:45:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>It&apos;s really hard to come up with ideas to write on and figure out whether your readers will like your piece or not. This is why we built Zine that allows you to gain readers and direct writing feedback before publishing.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MasterPluto—Get Free Mentorship - 免费的一对一指导，100多名导师，用户体验，开发，初创企业]]></title><description><![CDATA[Masterpluto是一个美丽的平台和强大的力量，将导师和被指导者联系起来，进行1:1的指导。我们是一个由用户体验设计师、软件开发人员、产品经理、数据科学家、创始人和领导人组成的强大社区。愿这股力量与我们同在!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/masterpluto-get-free-mentorship</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/masterpluto-get-free-mentorship</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 13:05:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Masterpluto is a beautiful platform and powerful force to connect mentors and mentees for 1:1 mentorships. We are a strong community of UX Designers, Software Developers, Product Managers, Data Scientist, Founders and Leaders. May the force be with us!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Video Reviews by Reviewshake - 为您的企业获得视频评论，在任何地方展示它们]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reviewshake是一款用于在线评论生成和管理的SaaS产品。我们的最新功能是视频评论：只需点击一下就能启用，并开始接收视频。你不必担心格式、存储或播放问题。这一切都由我们处理。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/video-reviews-by-reviewshake</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/video-reviews-by-reviewshake</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 13:05:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Reviewshake is a SaaS product for online review generation and management. Our latest feature is video reviews: enable them with a single click and start receiving them. You don&apos;t have to worry about formats, storage or playback. It&apos;s all handled by us.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ValueTools - 所有重要的开发工具都在一个应用程序中]]></title><description><![CDATA[🧰ValueTools是开发人员经常使用的重要工具的集合，全部捆绑在一个光滑的Windows应用程序中。忘掉寻找粘贴敏感信息的网站，只是为了做一些基本的工作。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/valuetools</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/valuetools</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 12:33:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>🧰 ValueTools is a collection of important tools frequently used by developers, all bundled together in a sleek windows application. Forget about finding sites where you paste your sensitive information just to do some basic work.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Career Switch To Coding - 将新学的编码技能转化为梦想的职业]]></title><description><![CDATA[你有足够的编码技能来完成工作，但你知道如何引起你的第一个雇主的注意吗？职业转换到编码是一本书，带你从一个不知名的编码员到拒绝比你接受更多的工作机会。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/career-switch-to-coding</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/career-switch-to-coding</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 11:30:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>You have the coding skills to do the job, but do you know how to get the attention of your first employer? Career Switch To Coding is a book that takes you from an unknown coder to turning down more job offers than you accept.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GAUSS AI - 快速、可靠、经济的数据标签]]></title><description><![CDATA[高斯使任何拥有智能手机和互联网连接的人都能成为数据标签员，我们的https://www.loom.com/share/ccfe9262bbb1440590fb390df0e0d23c，解锁了一个新的标签员生态系统。我们的https://www.loom.com/share/d05f440badf04a1cb02f5c53f530b6d8，可以为内部项目进行多种数据格式的协作式数据贴标。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/gauss-ai</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/gauss-ai</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 10:28:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Gauss enables any person with a smartphone and an internet connection to be a data labeler, our https://www.loom.com/share/ccfe9262bbb1440590fb390df0e0d23c has unlocked a new labeler ecosystem. Our https://www.loom.com/share/d05f440badf04a1cb02f5c53f530b6d8 allows for Collaborative Data Labeling for Internal Projects across multiple data formats.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SideNotes 1.3 - 关于屏幕侧的快速说明]]></title><description><![CDATA[SideNotes是一款基于Markdown的笔记应用，用于快速记录。它比便条纸更优雅，更敏捷，也比大型文本编辑器更不显眼。它住在屏幕一侧，在你需要时出现。保存文本、颜色、任务、图片、文件快捷方式。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sidenotes-1-3-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sidenotes-1-3-2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 10:28:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>SideNotes is a Markdown-based note-taking app for quick notes. More elegant than sticky notes, more agile, and more unobtrusive than big text editors. It lives on the screen side and appears when you need it. Save text, colors, tasks, pictures, file shortcuts.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Agency Directory - 寻找完美的机构，将你的品牌推向新的高度]]></title><description><![CDATA[浏览我们的资料库，其中有1000多家提供营销、设计、创意制作、社交媒体、公关等服务的机构 按地点、服务和规模进行筛选，准确找到你要找的东西。你对完美机构的搜索到此为止。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-agency-directory</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-agency-directory</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 10:28:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Browse our library of 1000+ agencies offering services in marketing, design, creative production, social media, PR, and more! Filter by location, services, and size to find exactly what you’re looking for. Your search for the perfect agency ends here.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Free online MBA - 获得20多个精心策划的资源来学习你在MBA中的内容]]></title><description><![CDATA[这里是一个精心策划的资源清单，它将帮助你学习你在商学院的知识。但有一个重要的区别，它是免费的!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/free-online-mba</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/free-online-mba</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 08:24:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Here is a curated list of resources, that&apos;ll help you learn what you would in business school. But with a major difference, it&apos;s free!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Relief - 摆脱你的信用卡债务的免费应用程序。]]></title><description><![CDATA[救济是摆脱债务的TurboTax。我们的应用程序通过直接与你的债权人谈判，将你的本金余额减少一半或更多，这很容易，而且是免费的。 加入我们的等待名单，可以得到100美元的债务补偿，每次你推荐朋友，可以得到50美元。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/relief</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/relief</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 07:30:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Relief is the TurboTax for getting out of debt. Our app makes it easy by negotiating directly with your creditors to cut down your principal balance in half or more- for FREE Get $100 towards your debt by joining our waitlist &amp; $50 every time you refer friends</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Doppler for Mac - 一个为购买音乐的人而设的音乐播放器。现在在Mac上。]]></title><description><![CDATA[多普勒是一个为购买音乐的人提供的音乐播放器。- 加快整理你的音乐 - 不需要转换文件 - 与iPhone应用同步 - 美丽的设计 - 强大的整合功能 多普勒让拥有音乐和支持艺术家变得简单。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/doppler-for-mac</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/doppler-for-mac</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 07:16:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Doppler is a music player for people who buy music. - Speed up organising your music - No need to convert files - Sync with iPhone app - Beautiful design - Powerful integrations Doppler makes owning music and supporting artists simple.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Colorize It - 安卓应用用AI将黑白照片变成彩色的]]></title><description><![CDATA["Colorize it "是一个使用AI自动为灰度图像着色的应用程序。它简单、快速、有效，所以没有人会注意到颜色是人工添加的。试试吧，让你的旧记忆变得五彩缤纷、栩栩如生，赋予它们新的生命]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/colorize-it-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/colorize-it-3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 16:12:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&quot;Colorize it&quot; is an app that uses AI to automatically color grayscale images. It&apos;s easy, fast and effective, so no one will notice that the color was added artificially. Try it and give a new life to your old memories by turning them colorful and vivid!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pangea.app - 我们把大学生变成自由职业者]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pangea.app将公司与大学生（和刚毕业的）自由职业者联系起来。我们的平台使雇用、管理和支付你未来的队友变得容易。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pangea-app</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pangea-app</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 15:29:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Pangea.app connects companies with college (and recent grad) freelancers. Our platform makes it easy to hire, manage, and pay your future teammates.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Flagpack V2 - 为你的数字产品提供惊人的旗帜图标]]></title><description><![CDATA[🏴Flagpack是一个开源项目，为您的数字产品提供250多个令人惊叹的旗帜图标。可在您的设计或代码项目中轻松实现。现在有Figma Variants和Svelte Components。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/flagpack-v2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/flagpack-v2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 14:22:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>🏴 Flagpack is an open source project of 250+ stunning flag icons for your digital product. Easily implementable in your design or code project. Now with Figma Variants and Svelte Components.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[LLC Toolkit - 注册特拉华州有限责任公司，零费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[LLC Toolkit是一个简单明了的公司成立，零开销+零服务费! 我们的团队有15年以上帮助其他公司成功的经验! #buildinpublic 关注我们的旅程，享受更多的福利! 🎁]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/llc-toolkit</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/llc-toolkit</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 13:35:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>LLC Toolkit is a straightforward company formation with zero overhead + zero service fees! Our team has 15+ years helping other companies succeeded! #buildinpublic Follow our journey for more perks! 🎁</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Knights of the Flexbox Table - 用Tailwind CSS学习和记忆Flexbox的游戏]]></title><description><![CDATA[Flexbox表的骑士是一个有趣的、互动的浏览器游戏，在这里你可以学习Flexbox如何与Tailwind CSS结合工作。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/knights-of-the-flexbox-table</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/knights-of-the-flexbox-table</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 12:09:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Knights of the Flexbox table is a fun, interactive browser game where you learn how Flexbox works in combination with Tailwind CSS.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Silex - 开放源代码的网站建设者]]></title><description><![CDATA[无论您是创建下一个项目网站的制作者，还是为客户制作网站的设计师，您都会喜欢Silex。您可以选择Wix和Webflow。可以破解，永远免费，你的设计，你的方式! 免费不仅仅是价格问题。#Freedom.]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/silex</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/silex</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 12:09:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Whether you are a maker creating your next project&apos;s website or you are a designer making websites for customers, you will love Silex. Your alternative to Wix and Webflow. Hackable, forever free, your design, your way! Free is not just about price. #Freedom.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nash - 任何企业提供当日送达的最简单方法]]></title><description><![CDATA[纳什是一款软件，通过在交付API（Uber、Doordash等）之上建立业务工作流程，使激活当日交付变得容易。例如，一家干洗企业可以在客户希望的时间提供取货/送货服务，而无需雇用司机。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nash-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nash-2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 11:49:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Nash is software that makes it easy to activate same-day delivery by building business workflows on top of delivery APIs (Uber, Doordash, etc). For example, a dry-cleaning business can offer pickup/delivery at a customer’s desired time, without hiring drivers.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BeTimeful Browser Extension - 让社交媒体不那么容易上瘾，每天节省2小时]]></title><description><![CDATA[Betimeful删除了你喜欢的社交媒体的新闻提要、推荐视频或任何旨在让你在工作中 "上瘾 "的东西。用鼓舞人心的每日名言取代饲料，并在谷歌日历/您自己的内置弹出式日历上安排 "焦点区"。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/betimeful-browser-extension</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/betimeful-browser-extension</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 11:24:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Betimeful removes your preferred social media’s news feeds, recommendation videos, or anything designed to get you “hooked” during work. Replace the feed with inspiring daily quotes &amp; schedule “focus blocks” on Google Calendar/ your own built-in popup calendar</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Woodpecker Academy - 在不到一小时的时间里，培养你的冷处理电子邮件的技能]]></title><description><![CDATA[在啄木鸟学院学习如何在不到一小时的时间内创建和优化成功的冷门电子邮件活动。免费加入我们的课程，并在之后马上收到一份个性化的证书。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/woodpecker-academy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/woodpecker-academy</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 11:24:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Learn how to create and optimize successful cold email campaigns in less than one hour with Woodpecker Academy. Join our course for free and receive a personalized certificate right after.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ev.energy - 一种更便宜、更环保、更简单的电动车充电方式]]></title><description><![CDATA[ev.energy可以自动让你以最经济、最不含碳的方式为你的电动车充电，同时你还可以通过智能充电获得现金奖励! 可在https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/ev-energy-smart-ev-charging/id1418569315, https://apps.apple.com/us/app/ev-energy-smart-ev-charging/id1418569315 和 https://apps.apple.com/de/app/ev-energy-smart-ev-charging/id1418569315。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ev-energy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ev-energy</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 11:24:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>ev.energy automatically allows you to charge your electric vehicle in the most cost-effective and least carbon-intense way possible, all while you earn cash rewards for your smart charging! Available in the https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/ev-energy-smart-ev-charging/id1418569315, https://apps.apple.com/us/app/ev-energy-smart-ev-charging/id1418569315 and https://apps.apple.com/de/app/ev-energy-smart-ev-charging/id1418569315.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[FODZYME by Kiwi Biosciences - 旨在使食物成为一种无痛的体验]]></title><description><![CDATA[FODZYME是一种正在申请专利的新型混合酶，可以分解FODMAPs--一种可发酵纤维家族和已知的肠道麻烦制造者，特别适用于患有肠道疾病如肠易激综合症的人。开始重新享受你最喜欢的食物吧!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fodzyme-by-kiwi-biosciences</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fodzyme-by-kiwi-biosciences</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 10:38:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>FODZYME is a novel patent-pending enzyme blend that breaks down FODMAPs — a family of fermentable fibers and known gut troublemakers, specially for folks with gut disorders like Irritable Bowel Syndrome. Start enjoying your favorite foods again!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bonjoro 2.0 - 用视频建立惊人的客户关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bonjoro 2.0帮助你通过视频建立惊人的客户关系。加入新客户，预订更多的销售电话，收集客户反馈，所有这些都通过快速的个性化视频邮件来实现。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bonjoro-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bonjoro-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 09:42:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Bonjoro 2.0 helps you build amazing customer relationships with video. Onboard new customers, book more sales calls, gather customer feedback, all with quick personalized video-emails.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jovian 2.0 - 学习数据科学，建立真实世界的项目并获得聘用]]></title><description><![CDATA[Jovian是一个数据科学和机器学习的学习平台。你可以参加关于数据分析、机器学习、深度学习的免费初级课程，或加入为期6个月的兼职在线训练营，掌握行业相关技能并获得聘用。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/jovian-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/jovian-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 09:42:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Jovian is a learning platform for data science and machine learning. You can take free beginner-friendly courses on data analysis, machine learning, deep learning or join a 6-month part-time online bootcamp to master industry-relevant skills and get hired.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Quest - 无代码的Figma到HTML，构建令人愉悦的体验]]></title><description><![CDATA[将您的Figma设计转换为实时网站。⠀ 设置自定义断点以获得真正的响应式体验。轻松添加互动和动画。从您自己的设计中创建完全自定义的幻灯片和表格。⠀ 实时启动或导出干净的代码。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/quest-ec0a9a1f-c1af-4ec0-8f51-1dbeb27df880</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/quest-ec0a9a1f-c1af-4ec0-8f51-1dbeb27df880</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 09:42:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Convert your Figma designs into live websites. ⠀ Set up custom breakpoints for a truly responsive experience. Add interactions &amp; animations easily. Create fully custom slideshows and forms from your own design. ⠀ Launch it live or export CLEAN code.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spline Alpha II - 下一个级别的3D优先设计工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[🔥 现在你可以从浏览器中使用Spline了! (在app.spline.design中尝试)。我们正在引入材料资产和一个完整的建模工具，以及矢量编辑功能和大量的修复和改进 ⠀ 朝着3D-First设计流程迈出了一大步。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/spline-alpha-ii</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/spline-alpha-ii</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 09:42:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>🔥 Now you can use Spline from the browser! (try it at app.spline.design). We are introducing Material Assets and a full Modeling Tool alongside Vector Editing features and a ton of fixes and improvements! ⠀ A big step towards a 3D-First design process.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Viewst Workspace - 按期完成任务，扩大内容并提高创意生产]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个工作空间，让你可以大规模地创建、协作和发布广告。Viewst使设计和营销团队的创意数量和种类成倍增加，更快地进入市场，并超越市场竞争。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/viewst-workspace</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/viewst-workspace</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 09:42:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>One workspace that allows you to create, collaborate and launch ads at scale. Viewst allows design and marketing teams to multiply creative volume and variety, go to market faster and out-market competition.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Color Glass Icons by Icons8 - 1,800多个看起来像宝石的几何图标]]></title><description><![CDATA[具有重叠元素的简单几何图标。给它们重新上色或使其成为单色--它们将闪闪发光 这些图标是真正的魔法晶体，适用于欢快的设计，如游戏、儿童应用程序，或时髦的商业网站。免费提供链接!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/color-glass-icons-by-icons8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/color-glass-icons-by-icons8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 08:26:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Simple geometric icons with overlapping elements. Recolor them or make them monochrome — they will shine! These icons are real magic crystals for cheerful designs like games, children apps, or funky business websites. Free for a link!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Liveblocks - 构建惊人的实时协作产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[Liveblocks是一套API，帮助你创建高性能和可靠的协作体验。有了Liveblocks，你可以在几分钟内实现任何协作，这样你就可以给你的核心产品以应有的关注。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/liveblocks</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/liveblocks</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 08:26:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Liveblocks is a set of APIs that helps you create performant and reliable collaborative experiences. With Liveblocks, you can make anything collaborative in minutes so that you can give your core product the attention it deserves.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ProjectHunt - 发现正在公开建设的顶级无码项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[发现在公共场所建造的顶级无代码项目 🚀 注册后可免费获得一本无代码资源的电子书!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/projecthunt</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/projecthunt</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 08:26:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Discover Top No-Code projects Built In Public 🚀 Sign up to receive a free E-book of No-code Resources!!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Slip - 构建交互式编程课程的最简单方法]]></title><description><![CDATA[🔨建立一个引人入胜的互动式编程课程 🖥嵌入可执行的代码片段、代码笔、figma设计，以及更多 💰直接向你的听众出售你的课程，用你的编程知识挣钱。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/slip</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/slip</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 08:02:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>🔨 Build an engaging interactive programming course 🖥 Embed executable code snippets, codepens, figma designs, and more 💰 Sell your course directly to your audience and earn money from your programming knowledge.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Beseda - 为远程团队提供异步视频和音频信息服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[用Beseda来代替会议，发送视频和音频--都是转录的--有更多的时间来专注于工作，而不会分心。Standups，设计审查，报告bug，收集和给予反馈 - 天空中的应用方式是无限的。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/beseda</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/beseda</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 07:21:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Instead of meetings, use Beseda to send videos and audios — both transcribed — and have more time for focused work without distractions. Standups, design reviews, reporting bugs, collecting and giving feedback — the sky&apos;s the limit for the ways to apply.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sofa 3.0 - 用一个地方来安排你的休息时间]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们今天使用的大多数应用程序都是为工作而设计的。Sofa是为数不多的有意用于玩耍的生产力应用程序之一。创建应用程序、书籍、棋盘游戏、电影、电视节目、播客、音乐专辑和视频游戏的清单，以便日后享用。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sofa-3-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sofa-3-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 07:21:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Most of the apps we use today are designed for work. Sofa is one of the few productivity apps intentionally intended for play. Create lists of apps, books, board games, movies, tv shows, podcasts, music albums, and video games to enjoy later.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[microletter - 创建你自己的超级简单的迷你通讯]]></title><description><![CDATA[microletter可以让你轻松地创建自己的通讯。它简单得不能再简单，专注于良好的写作体验，以及易于使用的界面。microletter是你自己的小编辑通讯的完美选择。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/microletter</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/microletter</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 07:21:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>microletter makes it easy to create your own newsletter. It is as simple as it gets, focusing on a great writing experience, and an easy-to-use interface. microletter is perfect for your own little editorial newsletter.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ultimate eCommerce Landing Page Template - 在几分钟内建立可转换的登陆页面]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们明白，建立登陆页面可能很难，但它们在电子商务中是如此关键。Builder.io与Sharma Brands合作，创建了一个易于使用、可定制和高转化率的登陆页面。安装并在不到5分钟内启动。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ultimate-ecommerce-landing-page-template</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ultimate-ecommerce-landing-page-template</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 21:33:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We get it, building landing pages can be hard, but they&apos;re so critical in eCommerce. Builder.io partnered with Sharma Brands to create an easy-to-use, customizable, and high-converting landing page. Install and get launched in less than 5 minutes.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pencil - 机器生成的创意平台]]></title><description><![CDATA[厌倦了为找到一个成功的广告而迭代数月？一旦出现创意疲劳，又要重新开始？Pencil使用人工智能从你现有的广告集中生成全新的广告，并自动更新，这样你的设计团队就可以专注于其他方面。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pencil-77af9051-19fc-4309-b686-1e2deec34ae5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pencil-77af9051-19fc-4309-b686-1e2deec34ae5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 16:15:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Tired of iterating for months to find a winning ad? Only to start all over again once creative fatigue sets in? Pencil uses AI to generate completely new ads from your existing set and updates them automatically so your design team can focus elsewhere.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donut for Hybrid Work - 为你的混合型团队架起沟通的桥梁]]></title><description><![CDATA[混合工作的甜甜圈帮助团队建立关系，公平地获得成长和面子的机会，并在混合世界中一起享受乐趣。该版本包括 "最爱 "功能、新的混合型模板和共享频道中的 "水坑"。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/donut-for-hybrid-work</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/donut-for-hybrid-work</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 15:29:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Donut for Hybrid Work helps teams build relationships, equitably access opportunities for growth and facetime, and have fun together in a hybrid world. Release includes Favorite Things feature, new hybrid-friendly templates, and Watercooler in shared channels.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Litnerd - 教育的皮克斯，K-5学校的阅读计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[Litnerd是一个在线课堂阅读项目，通过将创作者经济与传统教育相融合，将书籍带入生活。程序包括书本的情节重现、ELA课程计划、课程和电子书。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/litnerd</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/litnerd</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 15:29:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Litnerd is an online classroom reading program that brings books to life by blending the creator economy to traditional education. Programs include episode reenactments of books, ELA lesson plans, curriculum and ebooks.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WhatsApp for Intercom by Octopods - 在您的Intercom收件箱中发送和接收WhatsApp信息]]></title><description><![CDATA[Octopods WhatsApp for Intercom为您的Intercom收件箱带来最受欢迎的社交信息渠道。Octopods使用官方的WhatsApp商业API与Intercom进行深度整合，为您提供Intercom和WhatsApp的优点。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/whatsapp-for-intercom-by-octopods-1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/whatsapp-for-intercom-by-octopods-1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 14:22:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Octopods WhatsApp for Intercom brings the most popular social messaging channel to your Intercom Inbox. Octopods offers a deep integration with Intercom using the official WhatsApp Business API, giving you the best of Intercom and WhatsApp.</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>