<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Product Hunt 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Product Hunt 热门App，网站和产品]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 05:33:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Face On - 把你的脸放在任何东西上]]></title><description><![CDATA[Face on允许你把你的脸放在任何东西上，在任何视频聊天中推销你的想法。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/face-on</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/face-on</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 20:36:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Face on allows you to put your face on anything to pitch your idea in any video chat.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Haekka - 用Slack培训你的员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[在Slack中培训你的员工。Haekka是一个现代化的培训平台，为热爱Slack的人服务。带来你自己的培训内容或从我们不断增长的图书馆中选择。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/haekka</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/haekka</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 20:21:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Train your employees in Slack. Haekka is a modern training platform for people that love Slack. Bring your own training content or choose from our growing library.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MetaSapiens NFT - 第一个AR NFT项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[MetaSapiens是世界上第一个用于苹果iOS的增强现实NFT项目。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/metasapiens-nft</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/metasapiens-nft</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 19:17:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>MetaSapiens is the world&apos;s first Augmented Reality NFT project for Apple iOS.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Optic Hub - 一体化的光缆集线器扩展器]]></title><description><![CDATA[OPTICHUB是家庭、办公室、校园、指挥中心、监控室、编辑室或其他地方的任何数字信号情况的完美解决方案，可灵活订购1至300米的光缆。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/optic-hub</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/optic-hub</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 19:00:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Plug and play cable of optic fiber can be ordered in flexible length from 1 to 300 meters. &amp;nbsp;OPTICHUB is the perfect solution to any digital signal situation at home, office, campus, command center, monitoring room, editing studio or others.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Product Studio Session Templates - 为产品工作室会议策划的模板集合]]></title><description><![CDATA[认识一下产品工作室会议模板，这是确保产品符合真实用户需求的最节省时间的方法。有9个模板可以让你顺利地了解产品的想法，帮助你创建一个分步骤的计划，将你的产品推向市场。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/product-studio-session-templates</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/product-studio-session-templates</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 19:00:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Meet the Product Studio Session Template, the most time-saving way to ensure the product will match the real users’ needs. There are 9 templates for a smooth product idea overview, that help you create a step-by-step plan to bring your product to the market.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reflect 2.0 - 一个无代码的网络应用程序测试平台]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reflect是一个无代码的、基于云的平台，用于创建端到端的测试。它是为你的网络应用创建和维护端到端测试的最快方式。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/reflect-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/reflect-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 18:25:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Reflect is a no-code, cloud-based platform for creating end-to-end tests. It&apos;s the fastest way to create and maintain end-to-end tests for your web app.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Designing Growth - 每周为您的收件箱提供创业公司设计和增长方面的见解]]></title><description><![CDATA[加入其他创始人的行列，每周将精心策划的初创企业设计和成长见解直接送到您的收件箱。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/designing-growth</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/designing-growth</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 15:24:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Join other founders and get weekly, curated startup design &amp; growth insight delivered straight to your inbox.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NFT Header for Twitter - 自动更新显示你最新的NFTs的Twitter标题]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个免费的工具，可以自动更新你的Twitter个人资料标题，显示你钱包里的新NFT✨ 选择我们的设计之一，定制它，或创建你自己的模板]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nft-header-for-twitter</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nft-header-for-twitter</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:22:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A free tool that automatically updates your Twitter profile header to show new NFTs in your wallet ✨ Choose one of our designs, customize it, or create your own template!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mutiny 3.0 - 将你的网站变成你的第一收入渠道]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mutiny是一个没有代码的人工智能平台，为B2B营销人员提供他们所需要的一切，以个性化他们的网站，并转化99%的跳出流量--从识别访客到人工智能驱动的推荐和内容编写。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mutiny-3-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mutiny-3-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 13:04:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Mutiny is a no-code AI platform that gives B2B marketers everything they need to personalize their website and convert the 99% of traffic that bounces — from identifying visitors to AI-powered recommendations and content writing.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Product Superstories - 100多个精心策划的产品问题，由专家PM回答]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Product Folks & Amplitude的《产品的超级故事》是一个不为人知的故事集，其中充满了来自微软、亚马逊、Booking等公司几十年产品经验的见解。它揭开了产品经理旅程的有趣一面。阅读愉快!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/product-superstories</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/product-superstories</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 13:04:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Product Superstories by The Product Folks &amp; Amplitude is a collection of untold stories filled with insights from decades of product experience at Microsoft, Amazon, Booking &amp; more. It uncovers interesting aspects of a product manager&apos;s journey. Happy reading!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Compete - 关于科技界报酬数据的即时洞察力]]></title><description><![CDATA[Compete使科技界的人力资源和财务领导能够立即了解完整的薪酬方案数据。Compete得到了数百家领先科技公司的信任，它通过与市场的实时福利基准进行比较，使人们不再猜测。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/compete-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/compete-2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 11:45:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Compete empowers HR &amp; Finance leaders in tech with immediate insights into complete compensation package data. Trusted by hundreds of the leading tech companies, Compete takes the guess out of guesswork with real-time benefit benchmarks compared to the market.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Driwwwle - 就像Dribbble一样，但为开发者服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[Driwwwle是一个开源的社交平台，供开发者展示他们的项目并结识全球各地的创意开发者。创建一个免费账户，为你的项目获得更多的知名度，认识新的开发者，并获得启发。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/driwwwle</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/driwwwle</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 11:45:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Driwwwle is an open-source social platform for developers to showcase their projects and meet creative developers across the globe. Create a free account to gain more visibility for your projects, meet new developers, and get inspired.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Voicl - 在你的网站上嵌入语音提示]]></title><description><![CDATA[有了Voicl，你可以轻松地将语音笔记嵌入到你的网站。以更个人化的方式与您的用户互动，提供内容摘要、额外信息和CTA--使用您自己的声音!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/voicl</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/voicl</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 11:45:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With Voicl you can easily embed voice notes onto your website. Engage with your users in a much more personal way, provide content summaries, extra information and CTA&apos;s - using your OWN voice!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[StoriesOnBoard Feedback Management - 以客户反馈为动力的整体产品管理]]></title><description><![CDATA[StoriesOnBoard反馈管理收集来自客户、用户和你的团队的产品反馈到一个单一的存储库，并根据你创建的规则为你组织这些反馈。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/storiesonboard-feedback-management</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/storiesonboard-feedback-management</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 10:45:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>StoriesOnBoard Feedback Management gathers product feedback from customers, users &amp; your team into a single repository and organizes them for you based on rules you create.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AppFollow 7.0 - 从一个地方开启产品洞察力并管理应用程序评论]]></title><description><![CDATA[AppFollow为您提供工具，将客户评论转化为客户对您的应用程序的满意度。它自动将您和您的竞争对手的反馈划分为有用的类别和指标，产品和营销部门可以用它来建立一个更好的应用程序并推动增长。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/appfollow-7-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/appfollow-7-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 10:30:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>AppFollow gives you the tools to turn customer reviews into customer satisfaction for your app. It automatically segments your &amp; your competitors’ feedback into useful categories &amp; metrics that product &amp; marketing can use to build a better app &amp; drive growth.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GetAcquired Startup Marketplace - 初创企业市场 - 对买家和卖家免费开放]]></title><description><![CDATA[GetAcquired是购买和销售初创企业的现代市场。在OpenAI的支持下，我们的列表编辑器让您在几分钟内进入市场。访问2年的列表数据。我们的顾问市场帮助您建立您的交易团队。对卖家和买家免费。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/getacquired-startup-marketplace</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/getacquired-startup-marketplace</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 10:30:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>GetAcquired is the modern marketplace for buying &amp; selling startups. Powered by OpenAI, our listing editor gets you to market in minutes. Access 2 years worth of listings data. Our Advisor Marketplace helps you build your deal team. Free for Sellers &amp; Buyers.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Embeddinghub - 一个用于机器学习的开源数据库]]></title><description><![CDATA[Embeddinghub是一个用于机器学习嵌入的开源矢量数据库。大多数现代机器学习是建立在嵌入之上的，而Embeddinghub是从头开始建立的，以使你的ML模型走出实验室，进入生产。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/embeddinghub</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/embeddinghub</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 10:05:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Embeddinghub is an open-source vector database for machine learning embeddings. Most modern machine learning is built atop embeddings, and Embeddinghub is built from the ground up to get your ML models out of the lab and into production.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tactiq 2.0 - 保持专注，让Tactiq记录你的会议]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tactiq 2.0可转录Google Meets和Zoom网络电话，然后为您创建笔记🙏 v2.0 + 自动高亮和自动汇总 + 带时间戳的转录本，包括发言者 + 会议参与 + Notion, Quip, Dropbox, Slack等 + 西班牙语、法语、德语、葡萄牙语]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tactiq-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tactiq-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 09:00:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Tactiq 2.0 transcribes Google Meets &amp; Zoom Web calls, then creates notes for you 🙏 v2.0 + auto-highlights &amp; auto-summaries + time-stamped transcripts w/ speakers + Meeting engagement + Notion, Quip, Dropbox, Slack &amp; more + Spanish, French, German, Portuguese</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[EtherFly by The Explorers (Beta) - 探索移动端上最热门的3D游戏元数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[📲 在iOS上下载EtherFly测试版 🦋 探索一个3D世界，其中显示EtherFly NFT，并直接链接到他们的OpenSea页面 🪐 EtherFly是The Explorers的一部分，这是一个下一代的在线元空间，在这里你可以与你的朋友一起探索、游戏赚钱并获得乐趣。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/etherfly-by-the-explorers-beta</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/etherfly-by-the-explorers-beta</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 08:45:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>📲 Download EtherFly Beta on iOS 🦋 Explore a 3D World where EtherFly NFTs are displayed with a direct link to their OpenSea page 🪐 EtherFly is part of The Explorers, a next-gen online metaverse where you explore, Play-to-Earn and have fun with your friends.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GETitOUT - 像专家一样生成营销文本和网站]]></title><description><![CDATA[建立一个强大的营销基础，吸引你的理想客户。轻松创建买方角色，将功能转化为利益，并生成网站和电子邮件--在你的设计中完成文本和布局。是营销自由职业者和初创企业的理想选择。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/getitout</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/getitout</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 08:27:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Build a strong marketing foundation to attract your ideal clients: Easily create buyer personas, turn features into benefits, and generate websites and emails - complete with texts and layout, in your design. Ideal for marketing freelancers and startups.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lightstep Incident Response - 你需要的背景和自动化，以快速响应事件]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lightstep Incident Response是最新的事件响应平台，旨在让您的团队领先正常运行时间的威胁两步。积极主动地减少事故，建立长期的服务弹性，使您的团队能够更快地创新和自信地发布。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/lightstep-incident-response</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/lightstep-incident-response</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 08:27:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Lightstep Incident Response is the newest incident response platform, built to keep your team two steps ahead of uptime threats. Proactively minimize incidents and build long-term service resiliency so your team can innovate faster and release confidently.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kaspr - 即时获得你的潜在客户的电话号码和电子邮件]]></title><description><![CDATA[即时获取你的潜在客户的电话号码和电子邮件。用真实的数据转换线索，节省时间。与我们的竞争对手相比，我们找到的电话号码是他们的2倍!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/kaspr</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/kaspr</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 08:00:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Get access to your prospects’ phone numbers and email, instantly. Convert leads with real data and save time. We find 2 times the amount of phone numbers in comparison to our competitors!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mini Course Generator - 创建迷你课程进行营销的最快方法]]></title><description><![CDATA[1. 用各种内容类型超快地创建一个迷你课程 2. 2.获得其链接，以便在你的社交网络中分享，并无障碍地嵌入你的网站 3.展示你的迷你课程，不需要任何用户名和密码，开始给你的观众留下深刻印象]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mini-course-generator</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mini-course-generator</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 08:00:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>1. Create a mini-course super-fast with various content types 2. Get its link to share in your social network and embed in your website hassle-free 3. Present your mini-course without any need for a username and password to start impressing your audience</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Financial Freedom Calculator - 你能在经济上独立多长时间？]]></title><description><![CDATA[财务独立是梦想。根据你的储蓄和每月开支，你离实现这个梦想还有多远？或者你的目标应该是什么？通过这个来自Maybe的免费计算器来了解一下吧!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/financial-freedom-calculator</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/financial-freedom-calculator</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 07:22:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Financial independence is the dream. Based on your savings and monthly expenses, how close are you to making it? Or what should your goal be? Find out with this free calculator from Maybe!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Flyyer - 管理和自动化响应式链接预览]]></title><description><![CDATA[Flyyer是一个SaaS、CDN和开发工具包，使人们能够在社交媒体上分享之前管理、预览和自动处理他们网站的链接预览。预计点击率会增加57%，并通过分享分析做出更好的决定。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/flyyer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/flyyer</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 07:22:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Flyyer is a SaaS, CDN and development toolkit that enables people to manage, preview and automate their website&apos;s link previews before they are shared on social media. Expect CTR increase by 57% and make better decisions with sharing analytics.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tokyo Degenerates - 活在以太坊区块链上的动漫式收藏品]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Tokyo Degenerates是一个由10,000个独特的动漫风格数字收藏品组成的高级收藏品，生活在以太坊区块链上。我们的最终目标是创建一个以每个收藏品为特色的动漫系列，并将该系列作为NFTs发行。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tokyo-degenerates</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tokyo-degenerates</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 07:22:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The Tokyo Degenerates are a premium collection of 10,000 unique anime style digital collectibles living on the Ethereum blockchain. Our ultimate goal is to create an anime series featuring each collectible and distributing the series as NFTs.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YC Interviewer - 你准备好接受投资者的采访了吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[你准备好接受投资者的采访了吗？在任何地方练习你的演讲，并找出你的超能力💪🏻为YC创业加速器的面试过程而设计。用❤️在乌克兰制造 🇺🇦]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/yc-interviewer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/yc-interviewer</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 07:22:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Are you ready for an interview with investors? Practice your speech anywhere and figure out what your superpower is 💪🏻 Designed for the interview process at YC startup accelerator. Made with ❤️ in Ukraine 🇺🇦</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[onetask - 在几个小时内贴上标签的人工智能训练数据，一个下午就能完成10万+。]]></title><description><![CDATA[有了onetask，你可以自己给大规模的AI训练数据贴上标签。我们把弱监督和主动学习结合起来，这样你就可以很容易地在数据中找到模式，只用手来标注需要人类认知的记录。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/onetask</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/onetask</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 22:24:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With onetask, you can label AI training data on large-scale yourself. We combine Weak Supervision and Active Learning, so that you can easily find patterns in your data and only label records by hand that need human cognition.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Flowrift - 设计精美的Tailwind CSS用户界面块]]></title><description><![CDATA[Flowrift是一个由设计精美的Tailwind CSS UI块组成的库。所有的块都与Tailwind CSS的默认配置一起工作。大处着眼，小处着手：将区块相互堆叠以建立全页面布局，或有选择地复制小的代码片段。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/flowrift</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/flowrift</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 19:18:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Flowrift is a library made of beautifully designed Tailwind CSS UI blocks. All blocks work with Tailwind CSS&apos; default configuration. Go big or go small: Stack blocks on top of each other to build full-page layouts, or selectively copy small code snippets.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Discovery by Publicfast - 在几分钟内为你的活动寻找完美的影响者]]></title><description><![CDATA[Discovery by Publicfast是一个自动化的解决方案，通过类别、标签、关键词、地点进行搜索，以10倍的速度找到结果，从而找到您的完美创作者和影响者。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/discovery-by-publicfast</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/discovery-by-publicfast</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 16:25:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Discovery by Publicfast is an automated solution to search through categories, hashtags, keywords, locations to find results 10x faster to find your perfect creators and influencers.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Height - 一体化的项目管理]]></title><description><![CDATA[高度是你整个团队的一个项目管理工具。- 任务列表使你的团队保持同步 - 聊天记录使关于工作的对话保持在一个地方 - 通过Cmd-K、自定义快捷方式和跳转到闪电般的速度 - 整合自动更新任务]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/height-5378b770-9fd1-4fca-ae73-a4e02d6531a0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/height-5378b770-9fd1-4fca-ae73-a4e02d6531a0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 15:23:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Height is a project management tool for your whole team. - Task lists to keep your team synced - Chats to keep conversations about work in one place - Lightning fast with Cmd-K, custom shortcuts, and jump to - Integrations to automatically update tasks</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[iPNOTE - 保护你的初创企业的知识产权，节省高达90%的费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[使用iPNOTE知识产权管理平台和市场来获得商标和专利，同时节省高达90%的法律预算!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ipnote</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ipnote</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 14:31:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Use iPNOTE intellectual management platform and marketplace to get trademarks and patents, while saving up to 90% of your legal budget!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Clipt - 在设备之间无缝传输照片、文件和文本]]></title><description><![CDATA[Clipt通过连接你的手机和笔记本剪贴板，在你的设备之间无缝和安全地传输文本、照片、视频和文件。你不应该因为拥有一个以上的设备而受到惩罚--安装Clipt，看着你的生产力飙升。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/clipt</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/clipt</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 13:28:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Clipt seamlessly and safely transfers text, photos, videos, and files between your devices by connecting your phone &amp; laptop clipboard. You shouldn&apos;t be punished for having more than one device - install Clipt and watch your productivity soar.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Streak Mail Merge for Gmail - 发送大量的、个性化的电子邮件，并自动跟进]]></title><description><![CDATA[发送带有后续序列的个性化群发邮件的最佳方式。👋自动向没有回复的收件人发送后续信息 👋看起来和感觉是个人的 ⚠️智能提醒 🔋优化回复 🏠完全生活在Gmail内部]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/streak-mail-merge-for-gmail</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/streak-mail-merge-for-gmail</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 13:28:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The best way to send personalized mass emails with follow-up sequences: ✨ automatically send follow-ups with recipients who don&apos;t reply 👋 looks and feels personal ⚠️ smart alerts 🔋 optimize for replies 🏠 lives entirely inside Gmail</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reel - 将播客变成视频并在社交媒体上推广播客]]></title><description><![CDATA[在你的社交媒体账户上用醒目的视频预告你的播客剧集，吸引新的听众。为你的播客添加字幕。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/reel-5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/reel-5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 13:00:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Tease your podcast episodes on your social media accounts with eye-catching videos and attract new listeners. Add subtitles to your podcasts.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Start - 从世界任何地方启动和运行你的美国业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[有了Start，你可以从世界任何地方启动和运行一个美国企业。我们处理您所有的后台操作。有限责任公司的形成，注册代理，EIN，商业银行账户，每月记账，会计和税收（准备，申报，支付）。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/start-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/start-3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 13:00:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With Start, you can launch and run a US business from anywhere in the world. We handle all your back office operations: LLC formation, registered agent, EIN, business bank account, monthly bookkeeping, accounting and taxes (prep, filing, payment).</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hyper - 出售 Discord 和 Telegram 的会员资格]]></title><description><![CDATA[使用Hyper将你的在线社区变成一个企业。💵销售对Discord服务器和Telegram群组的访问权 🥇为不同的角色创建多种产品 🔗生成具有灵活定价的购买链接 在hyper.co.cn网站上不到5分钟就能开始。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hyper-2c2cd9da-80f6-4119-bb63-ac09a99a813d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hyper-2c2cd9da-80f6-4119-bb63-ac09a99a813d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 11:16:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Use Hyper to turn your online community into a business. 💵 Sell access to Discord servers and Telegram groups 🥇 Create multiple products for different roles 🔗 Generate purchase links with flexible pricing Get started in under five minutes at hyper.co.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[No-Code App Builders Comparison - 比较最受欢迎的无代码应用程序构建器的主要功能]]></title><description><![CDATA[最好的无代码应用开发平台的广泛比较图。Bubble, Webflow, Glide, Thunkable, Adalo, Bildr, or Wappler - 哪一个最适合你的项目？找出答案!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/no-code-app-builders-comparison</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/no-code-app-builders-comparison</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:26:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Extensive comparison chart of the best no-code app development platforms. Bubble, Webflow, Glide, Thunkable, Adalo, Bildr, or Wappler - which one is a perfect fit for your project? Find out!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[DhiWise - 立即为网络和移动应用程序获得生产准备的代码]]></title><description><![CDATA[DhiWise是一个ProCode平台，可以帮助你立即生成干净、可扩展和可定制的Node.js、Android、iOS、Flutter、Laravel和React控制面板的代码，这些代码可以在生产中使用，只需几个高级输入就可以建立网络、本地和混合应用程序。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/dhiwise-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/dhiwise-2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 09:46:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>DhiWise is a ProCode platform that helps you instantly generate clean, scalable &amp; customizable code of Node.js, Android, iOS, Flutter, Laravel &amp; React Admin Panel that is production-ready to build web, native &amp; hybrid apps with a few high-level inputs.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MarketMuse Free - 多发表，无畏地发表]]></title><description><![CDATA[MarketMuse是一个内容智能平台，为内容质量设定标准。我们的人工智能平台加速了你的内容研究、创作和优化过程，因此你可以更快、更无畏地发布。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/marketmuse-free</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/marketmuse-free</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 09:46:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>MarketMuse is a content intelligence platform that sets the standard for content quality. Our AI-powered platform accelerates your content research, creation, and optimization process so you can publish faster and fearlessly.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Airtable Invoice Maker - 超快地创建报价和发票]]></title><description><![CDATA[制作发票不是很无聊吗？节省您的时间，瞄准您的目标，专注于您擅长的事情 Airtable Invoice Maker可以让您超快地创建专业的报价和发票PDF。自由职业者和小机构的必备工具。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/airtable-invoice-maker</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/airtable-invoice-maker</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 09:33:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Isn&apos;t it boring to create invoices? Save your time, aim for your goal and focus on what you&apos;re good at! Airtable Invoice Maker lets you create professional quote &amp; invoice PDFs super fast. A must have for freelancers and small agencies.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hyperweb - 多合一的iOS Safari扩展]]></title><description><![CDATA[当你在Safari浏览器中浏览时，Hyperweb神奇地增强了网络，自动阻止广告，驳回弹出窗口，并为你正在浏览的页面建议智能替代方案。Hyperweb在设备上100%本地运行，建议的增强功能也在不断增加。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hyperweb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hyperweb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 08:25:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Hyperweb magically enhances the web as you browse in Safari, automatically blocking ads, dismissing popups and suggesting smart alternatives to the page you&apos;re on. Hyperweb runs 100% locally on device and suggested enhancements are ever growing.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ponicode CLI - 通过AI单元测试的生成实现高的代码质量]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于有了人工智能，现在可以直接从你的命令行中实现更快的软件开发、更强大的代码和高代码覆盖率。为你的TS、JS和Python项目批量生成单元测试，提供最相关的测试场景。控制Bug 🎉]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ponicode-cli</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ponicode-cli</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 08:25:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Faster software development, more robust code &amp; high code coverage directly from your command line are now possible thanks to AI. Generate unit tests in bulk for your TS, JS &amp; Python projects with the most relevant test scenarios. Keep bugs under control 🎉</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Punchlist - 在网站、图像和PDF上面的反馈层]]></title><description><![CDATA[为你所有的创意工作提供反馈层。⠀ 分享一个网址，看所有的内容和设计的变化都是实时的，直接在你的作品上添加。⠀ 与⠀ 💻 实时网站 🌄 图片 📁 PDF ⠀ 无限项目、评论和合作者 ⠀ 永久免费]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/punchlist</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/punchlist</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 08:25:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The feedback layer for all your creative work. ⠀ Share one url, and watch all content and design changes added in real time, directly on your work. ⠀ Works with ⠀ 💻 Live websites 🌄 Images 📁 PDFs ⠀ Unlimited projects, comments, &amp; collaborators ⠀ Free forever</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Railway - 免费部署配置：带上你的代码，其余的由我们来处理。]]></title><description><![CDATA[适用于任何语言，为大大小小的项目而制造。Railway是将运输软件的复杂性排除在外的云。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/railway</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/railway</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 08:25:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Made for any language, for projects big and small. Railway is the cloud that takes the complexity out of shipping software.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Usersnap - 获得可操作的客户反馈以实现增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[Usersnap是一个客户反馈软件，用于增加用户的反馈，以及集中处理问题和请求。通过对用户屏幕记录和满意度小型调查的洞察，推出更好的产品功能。在20分钟内开始使用 🚀]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/usersnap-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/usersnap-2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 08:25:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Usersnap is a customer feedback software to increase feedback from your users, as well as centralize issues and requests. Ship better product features with insights from user screen recordings and satisfaction mini-surveys. Get started within 20 minutes 🚀</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[LetterHunt - 10,000多份活跃的、精心策划的新闻简报，以推广您的产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[LetterHunt将你与10,000多个利基、活跃的通讯作者联系起来，以推广你的产品。寻找并与你的利基新闻通讯合作，为你的产品/服务的营销开辟一条新途径。新闻通讯与参与度统计一起被分类 🙌]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/letterhunt</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/letterhunt</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 07:31:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>LetterHunt connects you to 10,000+ niche, active newsletter writers to promote your product. Find and partner with newsletters in your niche and unlock a new avenue for marketing your product/service. Newsletters are categorized along with engagement stats 🙌</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[IdeaOnce - 易于使用的免费在线图形设计平台]]></title><description><![CDATA[IdeaOnce是一个免费的图形设计平台，帮助专业和非设计人员轻松快速地创建令人惊叹的设计。https://design.ideaonce.com。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ideaonce</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ideaonce</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 07:17:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>IdeaOnce is a FREE Graphic Designing platform that helps both professional and non-designers create amazing designs easily and quickly. https://design.ideaonce.com</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Perform - 你的智能健身DJ]]></title><description><![CDATA[Perform的人工智能驱动的音乐锻炼对心率和节奏等实时输入作出反应，以改善运动。经过近10万次锻炼和100万首歌曲聆听的训练，Perform知道在你锻炼的每一时刻使用正确的歌曲，以使锻炼效果最大化。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/perform</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/perform</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 07:17:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Perform&apos;s AI-powered music workouts respond to real-time inputs like heart rate and pace to improve exercise. Trained on nearly 100k workouts and 1M song listens, Perform knows the right song for every moment of your workout to maximize results.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stoa - 古代哲学和冥想应用程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[斯多亚将古老的斯多亚哲学与正念冥想结合在一个实用的冥想应用程序中。加入数以千计的人，用它来练习斯多葛的纪律，变得更平静、更有弹性和更有德行。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/stoa-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/stoa-2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 01:37:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Stoa combines the ancient philosophy of Stoicism with mindfulness meditation in a practical meditation app. Join thousands by using it to practice the Stoic disciplines and becoming calmer, more resilient, and virtuous.</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>