<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Product Hunt 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Product Hunt 热门App，网站和产品]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 04:44:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[PodRoom - 播客社交网络平台]]></title><description><![CDATA[PodRoom为播客提供所需的平台，以便与志同道合的人建立联系，提高他们自营媒体的知名度，并最终在数字领域获得更大的广告收入份额。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/podroom</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/podroom</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 19:03:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>PodRoom provides podcasters with the platform needed to connect with like-minded individuals, raise awareness for their self-owned media outlet, and ultimately, command a greater share of ad revenue in the digital realm.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Awkward Silences Podcast - 来自用户访谈的用户体验研究播客]]></title><description><![CDATA[欢迎来到 "尴尬的沉默"，这是一个播客，我们采访那些采访人的人。听听我们对用户体验研究、定性数据和理解人的技巧的所有事情的研究，以建立更好的产品和业务。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/awkward-silences-podcast</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/awkward-silences-podcast</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 18:00:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Welcome to Awkward Silences, the podcast where we interview people who interview people. Listen as we geek out on all things UX research, qualitative data, and the craft of understanding people to build better products and businesses.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[FREEKIN' - 非旅游地的社交网络和市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[比 "像当地人一样 "更好的东西。没有旅行团，没有导游，没有人群，没有垃圾邮件，没有COVID-19。一个特别的旅游应用程序，用于与志同道合的人分享非主流的、硬核的、大多是免费的旅游地。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/freekin</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/freekin</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 16:24:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Something better than &quot;like a local&quot;. No tours, no guides, no crowds, no spam, no COVID-19. A special travel app for sharing off the beaten, hardcore and mostly free places to visit with like-minded people.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Newsy - 将你未使用的域名变成一个完整的网络应用程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[你是否有目前不使用的域名或未使用的域名？为什么不把它变成一个完整的、功能性的社会新闻聚合器，就像Reddit一样，只需3次点击就可以了？Newsy可以让你强大地做到这一点，并具有你需要的所有功能。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/newsy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/newsy</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 16:24:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Do you have domains that you are not using at the moment or unused domains? Why not turn it into a complete, functional social news aggregator like Reddit in 3 clicks? Newsy lets you do this powerfully with all the features that you need.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[papapal - 学习一种新的语言，与有趣的人写电子邮件]]></title><description><![CDATA[🌍 学习外语，与有趣的人写电子邮件。🎁 填写表格--并得到一份礼物。💌 认识你的朋友。✍️ 写作和学习。🗝 简单是这里的关键。没有应用程序。没有费用。👉让我们回到基础：与新朋友见面和讨论。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/papapal</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/papapal</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 16:24:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>🌍 Learn a foreign language writing emails with interesting people. 🎁 Fill the form -and get a gift. 💌 Meet your pal. ✍️ Write and learn. 🗝 Simplicity is key here. No app. No fees. 👉 Let&apos;s go back to basics: meet and discuss with new people.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reach.Live 2.0 - 主持直播和点播的技术讲座和产品演示]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reach.Live (YC W20)允许工程师、产品经理、社区经理主持实时和按需的技术讲座和产品演示 💻 集成工具 ⚙️ 分析仪表板，用于创造商机 🎉 通过创建一个公共内容库推动产品增长]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/reach-live-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/reach-live-2-0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 14:33:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Reach.Live (YC W20) allows engineers, product managers, community managers to host live &amp; on-demand Tech Talks &amp; Product Demos 💻 Integrated tools ⚙️ Analytics dashboards for lead generation 🎉 Drive product growth by creating a public content library</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Channel Tools for Slack - 邀请并导出Slack上的所有频道或团队成员]]></title><description><![CDATA[通过https://www.channeltools.io，你可以批量邀请一个Slack团队或一个频道的所有成员到另一个频道。它还可以帮助你快速导出一个频道的所有成员。它配备了方便的实用命令，用于清除屏幕和挑选一个随机用户]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/channel-tools-for-slack</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/channel-tools-for-slack</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 12:42:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With https://www.channeltools.io, you can bulk invite all members of a Slack team, or a channel, to another channel. It also helps you quickly export all members from a channel. It comes with handy utility commands for clearing the screen and picking a random user</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Remote Meetings Handbook - 远程销售和客户成功会议的战术指南]]></title><description><![CDATA[与面对面的会议相比，远程会议有独特的优势，但为了最大限度地发挥这些独特的优势，你需要让自己适应新的做事方式。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-remote-meetings-handbook</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-remote-meetings-handbook</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 12:42:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Remote meetings have unique advantages compared to in-person meetings, but to maximize these unique advantages, you’ll need to adapt yourself to the new way of doing things.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Venture Capital Interview Trainer - 用60多个真实问题练习你的面试]]></title><description><![CDATA[你想进入风险投资，但不知道面试过程会是怎样的？我们收集了60多个风险投资公司在申请过程中问候选人的真实问题。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/venture-capital-interview-trainer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/venture-capital-interview-trainer</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 10:51:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>You want to get into venture capital but don&apos;t know how the interview process will be like? We collected 60+ real questions VC firms ask their candidates during the application process.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YesPromo - 100多个成功的自我推广Reddit帖子的免费数据库]]></title><description><![CDATA[了解如何利用Reddit为你的业务服务。免费收集了100多个成功的自我推广帖子，涉及30多个子红点。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/yespromo</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/yespromo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 09:30:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Learn how to leverage Reddit for your business. A free collection of 100+ successful self promotion posts across 30+ subreddits.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Codejudge - 通过模拟真实世界的评估实现技术招聘的自动化]]></title><description><![CDATA[Codejudge通过自动化的真实世界评估帮助企业更快、更智能、更好地建立技术团队。我们的真实任务能在几秒钟内捕获超过127个技能数据点，以确保你在建立技术团队时基于数据而不是猜测。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/codejudge</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/codejudge</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 09:00:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Codejudge helps companies build tech teams faster, smarter and better through automated real world assessments. Our real world tasks capture over 127+ skill data points within seconds to ensure you’re building tech teams based on data and not guesswork.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donate to India's Covid Relief - 通过COVID第二波行动，加紧帮助印度]]></title><description><![CDATA[捐款帮助印度渡过第二波难关，并获得与印度最优秀的产品建造者一起工作的时间作为回报!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/donate-to-india-s-covid-relief</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/donate-to-india-s-covid-relief</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 08:50:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Donate to help India through the second wave and get time with India&apos;s best product builders in return!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[bMoves - 管理你的现场活动的聪明方法]]></title><description><![CDATA[bMoves是管理您现场活动的地理定位解决方案。无论是在现场还是在办公室，bMoves都能让您记录、可视化并输出您所做的一切。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bmoves</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bmoves</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 08:25:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>bMoves is the geo-localized solution to manage your field activities. Available on the field and in the office, bMoves enables you to document, visualize and export everything you do.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cohort-Based Courses by Pathwright - 创建社区课程，促进不孤独的学习]]></title><description><![CDATA[邀请你的在线学习者使用Cohorts共同学习。因为最好的学习发生在我们与同路人交流思想、提出问题和互动的时候。https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4tDcdhoo0Ug]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/cohort-based-courses-by-pathwright</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/cohort-based-courses-by-pathwright</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 07:28:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Invite your online learners to learn together with Cohorts. Because the best learning happens when we&apos;re exchanging ideas, asking questions, and interacting with people on our same path. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4tDcdhoo0Ug</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Royalties Calculator - 知道任何音乐家能赚多少钱]]></title><description><![CDATA[这个工具使你能够搜索任何音乐家，它可以估算出在所有主要流媒体平台上的版税收入，如Spotify、Apple Music、Amazon和许多其他平台！完全免费。完全免费!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/royalties-calculator</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/royalties-calculator</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 07:28:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>This tool enables you to search for ANY musician and it approximates how much money generates on royalties on all the major streaming platforms such as Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon, and many others! Completely free!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[⚡️Iconic - 免费的，"做你想做的事 "的像素完美的图标。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Iconic是一个免费的，不断增长的像素完美的图标集合。每周都有新的图标加入。150个图标和计数（.svg，png，fig）。享受 😘]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/iconic-6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/iconic-6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 07:28:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Iconic is a free, ever-growing collection of pixel-perfect icons. New icons added every week. 150 icons and counting (.svg,png,fig). Enjoy 😘</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ping - 为你的远程团队提供会所]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ping允许你与你的团队进行自发的、随机的音频聊天。临时会议不需要调度和复制粘贴的Zoom链接。看到一个队友在Ping上直播？只需点击他们的图标，就可以立即与他们交谈! 现在可以免费使用!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ping-15</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ping-15</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 04:32:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Ping allows for spontaneous, drop-in audio chats with your team. Ad hoc meetings don&apos;t need scheduling and copy pasted Zoom links. See a teammate is live on ping? Simply click on their icon to talk to them instantly! Now available for free!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Skotty - 为专业人士提供更智能的在线交流]]></title><description><![CDATA[Skotty使用智能模块块加强了你与客户的沟通。一个区块可以是任何东西，从一个文件或消息，到一个文件请求、签名或视频通话。你可以根据你的工作流程来组合和重新排列块，然后将它们发送给任何人。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/skotty</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/skotty</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 04:32:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Skotty enhances your communication with clients using smart modular blocks. A block can be anything from a file or message, to a file-request, signature or a video-call. You can combine and reorder blocks to match your workflows, then send them to anyone.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Make.rs - 制造者向世界展示他们所制造的东西的地方]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个制造者向世界展示他们所制造的东西的地方。这是一个不同的个人资料页面，它不是关于你所工作的公司，而是你所做的事情。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/make-rs</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/make-rs</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 03:57:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>This is a place where makers show the world what they&apos;ve made. It&apos;s a different kind of profile page where it&apos;s not about the companies you worked for but what you&apos;ve done.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jira Work Management - Jira上业务团队的新家]]></title><description><![CDATA[Jira工作管理是一种新的友好和直观的方式，使企业团队能够使用Jira的力量，并具有为现代协作风格建立的新功能。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/jira-work-management</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/jira-work-management</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 23:49:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Jira Work Management is a new friendly and intuitive way for business teams to access the power of Jira with new functionality built for modern styles of collaboration.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Prox - 专家意见随叫随到，即时安排1:1视频通话]]></title><description><![CDATA[Prox是一个由畅销书作者、TEDx演讲者、商业顾问、影响者和内容创造者等顶级专家组成的策划网络。从已经证明相关成功的人那里获得个性化的建议、真实的洞察力和及时的答案。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/prox</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/prox</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 21:37:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Prox is a curated network of top experts from best selling authors, TEDx speakers, business advisors, influencers, and content creators. Get personalized advice, real insight, and timely answers from people who have proven related success.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ubiq Security - 使开发者能够在几分钟内将加密技术植入应用程序中]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们为开发者简化了加密程序。加密很难做对，也很容易做错，这就是为什么我们建立了Ubiq，一个完全基于API的SaaS平台，使开发者能够通过几行代码和2个API调用直接在其应用程序中建立加密。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ubiq-security</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ubiq-security</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 21:15:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We simplify encryption for developers. Encryption is hard to get right and very easy to get wrong, that’s why we built Ubiq, an entirely API-based SaaS platform that enables developers to build encryption directly into their applications with a few lines of code and 2 API calls.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lean Incubator - 用Notion孵化你的想法]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个工作系统模板，用于孵化和管理你的想法发展。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/lean-incubator</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/lean-incubator</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:25:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A work system template to incubate &amp; manage your idea development.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Skio - 在Shopify上销售订阅和给予团体折扣]]></title><description><![CDATA[Skio帮助Shopify商户销售订阅和给予团体折扣。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/skio</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/skio</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:25:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Skio helps Shopify merchants sell subscriptions and give group discounts.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[RevOps Cashflow API - 用低代码和无代码的方式使你的闭环操作自动化]]></title><description><![CDATA[更快地提供价值，而不必为账户配置、计费设置和入职沟通感到头痛。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/revops-cashflow-api</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/revops-cashflow-api</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 15:29:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Deliver value faster without the headache of account provisioning, billing setup, and onboarding communications.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Product Market Fit Toolkit - 使用你已经拥有的数据来衡量你的产品与市场的匹配度]]></title><description><![CDATA[这个工具包是由salesfit.io制作的。它让你使用在购买过程中自动收集的数据来衡量和改善产品与市场的契合度（不过你可以使用不同的数据--他们的手册帮助你选择正确的指标）。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/product-market-fit-toolkit</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/product-market-fit-toolkit</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 14:11:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>This toolkit is made by salesfit.io. It lets you measure and improve product-market fit using data automatically collected during a purchase process (you can use different data though - their manual helps you to choose the right metric).</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rare Things (Beta) - 来自世界级工匠的短视频购物]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rare Things为您带来了来自世界级工匠的短视频购物。在这里，你可以购买有限的产品，并走进来自全球各地的陶瓷专家、金属匠、木工、纺织艺术家、皮革工艺师和裁缝师的工作室工作室。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/rare-things-beta</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/rare-things-beta</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 13:53:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Rare Things brings you short-form video shopping from world-class artisans. Shop limited collections and step into the studio workshops of expert ceramicists, metalsmiths, woodworkers, textile artists, leather crafters, and seamstresses from around the globe.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BIGVU WordTrim - 通过在手机上选择单词轻松地修剪你的视频]]></title><description><![CDATA[有了BIGVU，你可以在短时间内剪切你的谈话视频，用我们的提词器应用程序录制或导入文件。你的视频会自动转录。你只需要在你想让你的视频开始和结束的地方选择单词。这很快速和简单。所有这些都来自你的手机。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bigvu-wordtrim</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bigvu-wordtrim</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 13:12:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With BIGVU, cut your talking videos in a snap, record with our teleprompter app or import a file. Your video is automatically transcribed. You just need to select the words where you want your video to start and end. It’s fast and easy. All from your Phone.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Emaily - 创建一个可随时发送的电子邮件给任何人]]></title><description><![CDATA[厌倦了写长长的电子邮件？Emaily是一个易于使用的服务，只需点击两下就可以创建专业的电子邮件。获得任何目的的建议，如冷漠的电子邮件，工作机会，通讯，等等。了解更多 - https://emaily.app/]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/emaily</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/emaily</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 13:12:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Sick and tired of writing long emails? Emaily is an easy-to-use service for creating professional emails in two clicks. Get suggestions for any purpose like cold email, job offer, newsletter, etc. Learn more — https://emaily.app/</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Moni Talks - 每日加密货币摘要，内含未来100倍项目]]></title><description><![CDATA[Moni Talks 🌶是一份每日加密通讯，包含从400多个资源中精心挑选的大量内容，以5分钟报告的形式发送到你的收件箱。每一天都是如此。不要错过下一个100倍的项目和F🤐CK FOMO。btw，我们的Twitter：https://twitter.com/getmoni_talks]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/moni-talks-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/moni-talks-2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 10:30:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Moni Talks 🌶 is a daily crypto newsletter with tons of content handpicked from 400+ resources and delivered to your inbox as a 5-min report. Every freaking day. Don’t miss next 100x projects and F🤐CK FOMO. btw, our Twitter: https://twitter.com/getmoni_talks</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Notea - 免费的自我托管的开源笔记应用程序，如Notion]]></title><description><![CDATA[Notea是一个存储在S3上的自我托管的笔记应用程序，你可以一键部署到Vercel、AWS，或用Docker🐳部署。它支持亚马逊S3、MinIO、阿里云OSS等的存储。它由TypeScript🚀驱动，喜欢Mark Down。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/notea</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/notea</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 08:41:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Notea is a Self hosted Note taking app stored on S3, that you can deploy with one click to Vercel, AWS, or deploy with Docker 🐳. It supports storage in Amazon S3, MinIO, Aliyun OSS and others. It&apos;s powered by TypeScript 🚀 and loves Mark Down.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The SaaS CPO Checklist - 为你的用户建立一个最佳的分析体验]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们将8年多的研发工作和100多个数据可视化项目打包在这个综合清单中，以帮助你为你的用户创建与众不同的、可扩展的仪表盘 📊 用它来降低分析项目的复杂性、成本和价值时间💪 享受 🤩]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-saas-cpo-checklist</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-saas-cpo-checklist</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 08:41:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We’ve packaged 8+ years of R&amp;D &amp; 100s of data viz projects in this comprehensive checklist to help you create differentiated, scalable dashboards for your users 📊 Use it to reduce the complexity, cost &amp; time to value of your analytics projects 💪 Enjoy 🤩</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Face Generator - 实时生成独特的、富有表现力的AI生成的面孔]]></title><description><![CDATA[塑造完美的面孔来代表你的下一个项目。脸谱生成器可以让你从你的虚拟身份中拨出你想要的特征和情感，然后实时生成它们!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/face-generator</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/face-generator</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 07:45:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Craft the perfect face to represent your next project. Face Generator lets you dial-in the features and emotions you want from your virtual identity, then generate them in real-time!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Email Verify API - 简单的电子邮件验证API，39美元的终身许可证]]></title><description><![CDATA[准确的API，在一个简单的GET请求中验证电子邮件地址。很容易检测到一次性的电子邮件，验证邮箱是否活跃。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/email-verify-api</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/email-verify-api</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 06:59:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Accurate API to validate email addresses in a simple GET request. Easily detect disposable emails, verify mailbox is active.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bookshlf - 为你策划的内容赚取小费]]></title><description><![CDATA[对数字内容的无限访问为我们提供了一个发现、学习和成长的巨大机会。Bookshlf专注于质量和品味，授权创作者（策展人）通过分享他们喜爱的内容来实现其知识和专长的盈利。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bookshlf-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bookshlf-2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 02:58:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Unlimited access to digital content has provided us with an enormous opportunity to discover, learn and grow. Bookshlf focuses on quality and taste, empowering creators (Curators) to monetize their knowledge and expertise by sharing the content they love.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Glitch Instant Sites - 在一分钟内制作一个实时的、全栈的或静态的网站]]></title><description><![CDATA[使用React或Eleventy等框架，在一分钟之内在浏览器中创建并启动一个真正的、全栈的或静态的网站--免费的。Glitch让你的网站比无代码工具或网站建设者更快、更容易，但没有锁定。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/glitch-instant-sites</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/glitch-instant-sites</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 02:58:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Create &amp; launch a real, full-stack or static site at a live URL using frameworks like React or Eleventy, all in under a minute in your browser — for free. Glitch lets you make a site faster &amp; easier than a no-code tool or site builder, but with no lock-in.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Frido - 用自己的方式做事]]></title><description><![CDATA[Frido是一个待办事项应用程序，旨在将你从创建无尽的待办事项清单的负担中解放出来，你最终放弃了。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/frido</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/frido</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 21:00:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Frido is a to-do app designed to free you from the burden of creating endless to-do lists you eventually give up on.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sellou - 分享，购物，并向世界销售]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sellou重新设计了我们在线购买和销售的方式! 📦💰发现世界各地的人🌎🌍销售产品，并在Sellou上展示您的产品进行销售。这是我们的开放测试版，所以我们将非常感谢您的反馈! 🙌 注册 https://sellou.com]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sellou</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sellou</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 17:54:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Sellou redesigns the way we buy and sell online! 📦💰 Discover people all over the world 🌎 🌍 selling products, and display your products for sale on Sellou. This is our open beta, so we would greatly appreciate your feedback! 🙌 Sign up https://sellou.com</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Instagram Engagement Report 2021 - 从1亿多条Instagram帖子中收集的数据和洞察力]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们分析了100万用户分享的1亿多条Instagram帖子，为你提供最完整、最新的Instagram营销资源--免费的。与其猜测什么是有效的，不如依靠我们的数据和专业知识，以确保你的Instagram策略是完全优化和最新的。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/instagram-engagement-report-2021</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/instagram-engagement-report-2021</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 17:02:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We analyzed over 100 million Instagram posts shared across 1 million users to give you the most complete, up-to-date resource on Instagram marketing - for free. Instead of guessing what works, rely on our data and expertise to make sure your Instagram strategy is fully optimized and up-to-date.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mars26 - 开源、高分辨率、自然色彩的火星地图]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mars26是一个高分辨率、自然色彩的开源火星地图。它建立在以前的CTX和维京卫星摄影的基础上，合并成一个全覆盖的互动地图。放大，探索，并在你最喜欢的火星地点放置推特。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mars26</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mars26</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 15:47:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Mars26 is an open source Mars map in high-resolution, natural color. Built on top of previous CTX &amp; Viking satellite photography, merged into an interactive map with full coverage. Zoom in, explore and place tweets at your favorite Mars locations.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PowerBen Powerbank - 下一代便携式发电站]]></title><description><![CDATA[真正准备好的备用电源在你手中。结合24000mAh的超大电池容量，你可以在短短3分钟内获得你的iPhone 12的容量! 使用汽车、太阳能、AC适配器或PD适配器为你的PowerBen充电。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/powerben-powerbank</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/powerben-powerbank</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 15:47:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Truly ready-to-go backup power by your hand. Combined with a super large battery capacity of 24000mAh, you can get your iPhone 12 capacity in ONLY 3 minutes! Charging your PowerBen using a car, solar power, AC Adapter, or PD Adapter.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Product Virality - 学习创造有感染力的产品]]></title><description><![CDATA[在这本免费的电子书中，你将了解到。为什么你应该去 "病毒"，不同类型的产品病毒性，病毒性产品的形成，大量的现实世界的例子，以及你今天可以实施的可操作的策略和技巧。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/product-virality</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/product-virality</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 13:31:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>In this free ebook, you’ll learn: ✅ why exactly you should go “viral”, ✅ different types of product virality, ✅ the making of a viral product, ✅ tons of real world examples, ✅ and actionable strategies and tips you can implement today.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Immersive Scenes by VirtualOffice - 品牌的虚拟背景为Zoom的身临其境的看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[为Zoom的沉浸式视图创建品牌场景。只需选择一个场景，上传你的标志，然后就可以了--你的虚拟办公室已经准备好与Zoom的新的沉浸式视图一起工作了!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/immersive-scenes-by-virtualoffice-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/immersive-scenes-by-virtualoffice-2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 12:55:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Create branded scenes for Zoom&apos;s Immersive View. Simply select a scene, upload your logo and voilà - your Virtual Office is ready to work with Zoom&apos;s new Immersive View!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Arc 2.0 - 寻找世界上的远程开发工作的最简单方法]]></title><description><![CDATA[为寻找远程工作的开发者提供一站式服务。Arc汇总了全球的远程工作机会，并为您生成了一份最适合的工作清单。通过加入Arc的远程开发者社区，获得支持并提升你的职业水平。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/arc-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/arc-2-0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 12:14:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The one-stop-shop for developers looking for remote jobs. Arc aggregates the world&apos;s remote opportunities and generates a list of best-fit jobs for you. Get support &amp; level up your career by joining Arc&apos;s remote developer community.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mockup Generator by Pixeltrue - 只需点击几下就能创建漂亮的产品模拟图]]></title><description><![CDATA[有了Mockup Generator，你只需点击几下就能创建漂亮的产品模型 完全免费。有了5种设备类型的30多个不同的模型，你将有足够的材料为你的项目和营销活动创建漂亮的产品模型。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mockup-generator-by-pixeltrue</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mockup-generator-by-pixeltrue</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 12:14:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With Mockup Generator you can create beautiful product mockups in just a few clicks! Completely free. With over 30 different mockups on 5 device types you&apos;ll have enough material to create beautiful product mockups for your projects and marketing campaigns.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Codemap 2.0 - 世界上第一个无代码/自动化的人才市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[Codemap是世界上第一个无代码/低代码和自动化的自由职业者市场。使用我们的智能简报描述您的项目，我们将为您匹配顶级的、预先审查过的无代码专家和团队。在几天或几周内推出你的产品、工具或工作流程!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/codemap-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/codemap-2-0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 11:25:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Codemap is the world&apos;s first freelance marketplace for no-code/low-code and automation. Describe your project using our smart brief and we&apos;ll match you with top, pre-vetted no-code experts &amp; teams. Launch your product, tool, or workflow in days or weeks!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zestack - 营销与增长的Stackoverflow]]></title><description><![CDATA[Zestack是营销和增长战略的 "Stack Overflow"。我们500多人的社区专注于帮助彼此学习和实施实用的增长活动。为什么要等待？现在就免费加入。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zestack</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zestack</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 10:51:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Zestack is the &quot;Stack Overflow&quot; for marketing &amp; growth strategies. Our 500+ strong community is focussed on helping each other learn and implement practical growth campaigns. Why wait? Join now for free.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CSML Playground - 玩转CSML，聊天机器人的编程语言]]></title><description><![CDATA[使用CSML（对话标准元语言）直接从您的浏览器中设计、构建和测试丰富的对话体验，有了全新的开放平台。即时分享您的聊天机器人代码，不需要登录。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/csml-playground</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/csml-playground</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 10:30:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Design, build, and test rich conversational experiences using CSML (Conversational Standard Meta Language) straight from your browser with the brand new open playground. Share your chatbot code on the fly, no login required.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Devbook - 开发者的搜索引擎]]></title><description><![CDATA[Devbook是一个面向开发者的搜索引擎，帮助他们更快地找到所需的资源并回答他们的问题。速度快，可以直接从代码编辑器中访问，而且只需一个键盘就可以完全控制。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/devbook</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/devbook</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 09:15:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Devbook is a search engine for developers that helps them to find the resources they need and answer their questions faster. Fast, accessible right from a code editor, and fully controllable with just a keyboard.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stacks Accelerator - 5万美元投资+3个月的网络3.0初创企业计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们投资5万美元给优秀的创业团队，与Stacks（以前的Blockstack）一起在比特币网络上建设。演讲者和导师包括Eric Ries, Meltem Demirors, Thomas France, Sergey Nazarov, +more. 我们接受任何阶段的创业公司，并帮助你提升水平。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/stacks-accelerator</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/stacks-accelerator</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 09:15:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We invest $50k in outstanding startup teams building on the Bitcoin network with Stacks (formerly Blockstack). Speakers &amp; Mentors include Eric Ries, Meltem Demirors, Thomas France, Sergey Nazarov, +more. We accept startups at any stage and help you level up.</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>