<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Product Hunt 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Product Hunt 热门App，网站和产品]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 10:08:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[2021 Looped - What does your calendar say about 2021?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Curious to know how you spend your time at work? 2021 Looped rounds up your calendar year and generates unique insights like time spent in meetings, the number of people met along with some other cool stats.]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/2021-looped</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/2021-looped</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:48:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Curious to know how you spend your time at work? 2021 Looped rounds up your calendar year and generates unique insights like time spent in meetings, the number of people met along with some other cool stats.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Detail 2 - Cinematic video made simple]]></title><description><![CDATA[Record and stream high-quality video with your Mac. Turn your Mac into a production studio with Scenes, multi-cam, and auto framing. Detail works with your iPhone, iPad, built-in webcam, or any other camera.]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/detail-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/detail-2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:48:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Record and stream high-quality video with your Mac. Turn your Mac into a production studio with Scenes, multi-cam, and auto framing. Detail works with your iPhone, iPad, built-in webcam, or any other camera.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Multiversial - 科技和商業新聞變得更聰明的西班牙語日報]]></title><description><![CDATA[MultiVersial是一份每日通訊，以西班牙語提供最新的科技商業信息。語言仍然是獲取知識的一個障礙。一份有趣而簡單的通訊，讓你在5分鐘內掌握最新信息，瞭解科技戰略，實現專業成長。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/multiversial</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/multiversial</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:16:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>MultiVersial is a daily newsletter with the latest in tech business in Spanish. Languages are still a barrier to accessing knowledge. A fun and simple newsletter that allows you to stay up to date, understand tech strategy, and grow professionally in 5 mins</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Opal C1 - 第一個幫助你看起來更好的專業網絡攝像機。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們正在爲那些與他們的工作--他們的團隊、員工、客戶--的主要聯繫是通過視頻通話的人建立Opal。我們希望通過一個即插即用的系統，讓每個人都能輕鬆擁有專業的設置。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/opal-c1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/opal-c1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:16:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We’re building Opal for anyone who’s primary connection to their job – their team, their employees, their customers – is through video calls. We want to make it easy for everyone to have a professional setup, with a single plug and play system.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Face Swapper - 免費交換面孔，前所未有]]></title><description><![CDATA[忘記那些來自圖片庫的過度使用的面孔。忘掉有不適當許可證的照片。改變面孔或身體，在廣告、電子商務、社交媒體、教育、光鮮的雜誌等方面使用它們。卓越的質量。無與倫比的分辨率。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/face-swapper</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/face-swapper</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:01:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Forget about overused faces from stock photos. Forget about photos with an inappropriate license. Change faces or bodies and use them in ads, e-commerce, social media, education, glossy magazines, etc. Exceptional quality. Unrivaled resolution.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ripple - 掌控你的情緒，贏得一天，每一天]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ripple是一款情緒跟蹤應用程序，通過擺脫焦慮、抑鬱和毒性，幫助人們改善心理健康。只要在1到10的範圍內選擇你的滿意度和能量水平。Ripple將翻譯你的情緒，並將其轉化爲文字!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ripple-13</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ripple-13</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:01:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Ripple is a mood tracking app that helps people improve their mental health by getting rid of anxiety, depression, and toxicity. Just choose your satisfaction and energy level on a scale of 1 to 10. Ripple will translate your emotions and put them into words!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AutoCloud - 自動化的三維雲基礎設施圖和洞察力]]></title><description><![CDATA[對於在AWS、Azure和GCP上運行工作負載的人來說，AutoCloud可以自動繪製架構圖，進行合規性檢查和漂移檢測。使用3D環境或通過查詢GraphQL端點來探索洞察力。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/autocloud</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/autocloud</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 08:48:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>For anyone running workloads on AWS, Azure, and GCP, AutoCloud automates architecture diagrams, compliance checks, and drift detection. Explore insights using a 3D environment or by querying a GraphQL endpoint.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Magic Sidebar by BlackMagic.so - 爲Twitter提供強大的增強體驗]]></title><description><![CDATA[Magic Sidebar是Twitter的最佳瀏覽器擴展。今天就使用它，解開你從不知道的見解，與你的受衆更好地溝通，並建立強大的1：1關係。也可使用iOS和Android的移動應用程序!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/magic-sidebar-by-blackmagic-so</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/magic-sidebar-by-blackmagic-so</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 08:36:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Magic Sidebar is the best browser extension for Twitter. Use it today and unlock insights you never knew about, communicate better with your audience, and build strong 1:1 relationships. Mobile apps for iOS and Android are also available!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Creativity Booster by Alpe Audio - 爲你的教學和內容尋找故事和例子]]></title><description><![CDATA[不再有寫作障礙。不要一直糾結於如何打開你的課程、文章或視頻。自動生成偉大的開場鉤子、故事和相關的例子，涉及你想教的或想寫的任何東西!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/creativity-booster-by-alpe-audio</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/creativity-booster-by-alpe-audio</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 23:28:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>No more writers block. Don&apos;t stay stuck wondering how to open your lesson, article or video. Automatically generate great opening hooks, stories and relevant examples about anything you want to teach or write about!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Christmas Design Assets by Iconfinder - 免費的節日圖標、插圖和動畫]]></title><description><![CDATA[用這些節日的好東西灑在你的季節性內容上。小精靈們來了，他們帶來了充滿設計資產的聖誕贈品，非常適合你的節日通訊、簡報和社交媒體帖子。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/christmas-design-assets-by-iconfinder</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/christmas-design-assets-by-iconfinder</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 16:02:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Sprinkle up your seasonal content with these festive goodies. Here come the elves with a Christmas freebie full of design assets that are perfect for your holiday newsletters, presentations &amp; social media posts.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[HiHo - 具有無限線程的異步視頻討論區]]></title><description><![CDATA[HiHo是一個面對面的社交應用程序，用於認識有趣的人並進行精彩的視頻對話。通過異步回覆和無限線程，每個人都可以在任何時間參與。該應用程序既提供公共論壇，也提供私人DMs。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hiho</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hiho</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 16:02:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>HiHo is a face-forward social app for meeting interesting people and having great video conversations. With asynchronous replies and infinite threading, everyone can participate at any time. The app offers both public forums as well as private DMs.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CommerceBooster - 一個用於電子商務的開源B2B UI模板]]></title><description><![CDATA[CommerceBooster是第一個開源的B2B電子商務的UI模板。它可以在Figma社區免費使用，並針對commercetools和Vue Storefront進行了優化。它實際上爲任何開始B2B電子商務項目的人節省了幾個月的工作。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/commercebooster</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/commercebooster</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 15:52:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>CommerceBooster is the first open-source, UI template for B2B eCommerce. It’s available for free on the Figma Community and optimized for commercetools and Vue Storefront. It literally saves months of work for anyone starting B2B eCommerce projects.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Carrot - 你的所有購物，像魔術一樣組織起來]]></title><description><![CDATA[無法跟蹤你想買的東西？認識一下Carrot，這個擴展可以在你購物時自動收集你的購物車。你可以通過點擊回到產品上，創建可分享和可贈送的收藏，獲得降價提醒，而且完全免費！這就是Carrot。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/carrot-4400273f-0d5e-4a81-a978-0f2477a39ad6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/carrot-4400273f-0d5e-4a81-a978-0f2477a39ad6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 13:14:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Can’t keep track of the stuff you want to buy? Meet Carrot, the extension that automatically collects your carts as you shop. You can get back to products with a click, create shareable and gift-able collections, get price drop alerts, and it&apos;s totally free!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pilot - 遠程團隊的薪資、福利和合規性]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pilot爲擁有遠程團隊的美國公司提供薪資、福利和合規性。輕鬆地在160多個國家的員工和240多個國家的承包商入職和付款。爲Product Hunt用戶提供特殊價格： pilot.co/producthunt]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pilot-8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pilot-8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 12:55:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Pilot provides payroll, benefits, and compliance for US-based companies with remote teams. Easily onboard and pay employees in 160+ countries and contractors in 240+ countries. Offering special pricing for Product Hunt users: pilot.co/producthunt</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Battle of Mars - 一個玩家與玩家之間的NFT遊戲]]></title><description><![CDATA[火星之戰是一個PVP的NFT遊戲，你可以挑戰對方，把對手的火星人帶走。1. 鑄造一個火星人（有10,000個獨特的火星人） 2. 加入一個加密派別 3. 挑戰朋友並奪走他們的火星人]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-battle-of-mars</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-battle-of-mars</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 10:16:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The Battle of Mars is a PVP NFT game where you can challenge each other and take your opponent&apos;s Martian away. 1. Mint a Martian (10,000 unique martians available) 2. Join a crypto faction 3. Challenge a friend and take their Martian away</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pretty Progress - 在你的iPhone主屏幕上有漂亮的倒計時小工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[漂亮的進度允許你在你的iPhone主屏幕上添加漂亮的個性化的倒計時和進度條部件。在你每天使用的設備上跟蹤並提醒自己重要的事情。清晰而方便。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pretty-progress</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pretty-progress</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 10:16:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Pretty Progress allows you to add beautiful &amp; personalized Countdown &amp; Progress Bar widgets on your iPhone&apos;s Home Screen. Track and remind yourself about the important things on the device you use every day. Clear and convenient.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Adobe Creative Cloud Express - 快速、輕鬆地製作社交圖形和更多]]></title><description><![CDATA[Creative Cloud Express（以前的Adobe Spark）使您可以輕鬆地開始使用數以千計的精美模板，以及用於社交媒體內容、標誌和更多的資產。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/adobe-creative-cloud-express</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/adobe-creative-cloud-express</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 10:01:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Creative Cloud Express (formerly Adobe Spark) makes it easy to get started with thousands of beautiful templates, plus assets for social media content, logos, and more.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Albert - 在Slack上爲你的團隊提高網絡安全意識]]></title><description><![CDATA[艾伯特通過Slack向你的團隊傳授網絡安全基礎知識。這些課程很短，爲每個員工動態定製，具有互動性，並且全年發送。這就是爲什麼你的團隊會喜歡它。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/albert-5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/albert-5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 09:48:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Albert teaches cybersecurity basics to your team over Slack. The courses are short, dynamically customized for each employee, interactive, and sent all year long. That&apos;s why your team will love it.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tella for Chrome - 在Chrome瀏覽器的任何地方都能錄製精彩的視頻]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tella for Chrome，屏幕和相機記錄器，讓你的工作看起來很棒。在Chrome瀏覽器的任何地方錄製完全可定製的、可立即分享的視頻。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tella-for-chrome</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tella-for-chrome</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 09:31:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Tella for Chrome, the screen and camera recorder that makes your work look great. Record fully customisable, instantly shareable videos from anywhere in Chrome.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Around 3.0 - 爲你的下一個快樂時光提供帶有音樂和遊戲的視頻通話]]></title><description><![CDATA[Around獨特的視頻通話旨在幫助混合遠程團隊一起創造、協作和慶祝。現在還配有音樂和遊戲，以促進團隊的團結和聯繫。在你的下一個快樂時光或聯合辦公會議上試試吧。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/around-3-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/around-3-0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:47:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Around&apos;s radically unique video calls are designed to help hybrid-remote teams create, collaborate and celebrate together. Now comes with music and games for team bonding and connection. Try it for your next happy hour or co-working session.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Smart VC Search by Unicorn Nest - 爲你的創業公司提供免費的獨特的相關風險投資商名單]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們建立了一個算法，分析38000個風險投資基金的歷史數據，爲初創企業推薦相關的投資者（種子期、A輪、B輪和C輪）。填寫調查問卷 ➡️獲得一份VC名單（包括決策者） ➡️立即開始投資者推廣 🚀]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/smart-vc-search-by-unicorn-nest</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/smart-vc-search-by-unicorn-nest</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:47:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We&apos;ve built an algorithm that analyses historical data of 38,000 VC funds and suggests relevant investors for startups (seed, round A, B and C). Fill in the questionnaire ➡️ Get a list of VCs (incl. decision makers) ➡️ Start investor outreach immediately 🚀</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ZeroBlur - 模糊敏感信息，自信地分享屏幕]]></title><description><![CDATA[ZeroBlur是一個100%免費的Chrome擴展，可以快速模糊敏感信息。在提供產品演示或銷售電話時，不再擔心敏感數據的泄露。只需點擊幾下，你就能模糊任何網絡應用或網站的任何元素或頁面區域。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zeroblur</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zeroblur</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:47:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>ZeroBlur is a 100% free Chrome extension to quickly blur sensitive information. Stop worrying about leaking sensitive data when delivering a product demo or a sales call. In few clicks you&apos;ll be able to blur any element or page area of any web app or website.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trivia Game Center - 在你的瀏覽器中通過團隊遊戲爲你的工作增添樂趣]]></title><description><![CDATA[你難道不討厭你的週一憂鬱症在週五晚上結束嗎？別擔心! 在實時小組電話中與你的團隊一起玩猜謎和猜字遊戲，並與你的團隊進行虛擬的聯繫。不需要安裝! 打開你的瀏覽器，準備好享受一些樂趣吧 🎉。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/trivia-game-center-1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/trivia-game-center-1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:36:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Don’t you hate it when your Monday blues end on Friday nights? Fret not! Play Quizzes and Pictionary with your team in real-time group calls and bond with your team virtually. No installation required! Fire up your browsers and get ready to have some fun 🎉</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Unicorns to the Moon - 像越共一樣玩這個充滿行動力的桌面遊戲]]></title><description><![CDATA[獨角獸登月》是一款動作類桌面遊戲，將你成爲炙手可熱的風險投資家（VC）的夢想變成了現實 你作爲風險投資家的工作是什麼？投資獨角獸公司，並將它們送上月球。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/unicorns-to-the-moon</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/unicorns-to-the-moon</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 02:48:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Unicorns To The Moon is an action-packed tabletop game that turns your dreams of being a hotshot venture capitalist (VC) into a reality! Your job as a VC? Invest in unicorn companies, and send them to the moon.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PodBuddy - 從你的播客中製作一口大小的社交媒體視頻剪輯]]></title><description><![CDATA[PodBuddy將你的播客集做成動畫視頻，非常適合在社交媒體上分享。創建一個動畫帖子只需幾秒鐘。只需選擇你的播客集片段，PodBuddy就會根據你的播客作品創建一個帖子。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/podbuddy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/podbuddy</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:34:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>PodBuddy makes animated videos from your podcast episode, perfect for sharing on social media. It takes seconds to create an animated post. Simply pick your podcast episode clip and PodBuddy will create a post based on your podcast&apos;s artwork.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spatial - NFT畫廊和展覽的Metaverse]]></title><description><![CDATA[空間是文化的元空間，在這裏我們可以一起體驗一鍵式NFT畫廊和展覽。創作者、收藏家和品牌可以在網絡、移動和VR上免費舉辦美麗的沉浸式體驗。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/spatial-4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/spatial-4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:34:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Spatial is the metaverse for culture, where we can all experience one-click NFT galleries &amp; exhibitions together. Creators, collectors &amp; brands can host beautiful immersive experiences across web, mobile, and VR for free.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[OnPodium - 播客網站，吸引並擴大你的聽衆羣]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是我去年推出的Podsite項目的繼承者。我們正在根據現有客戶的反饋，不斷改進OnPodium。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/onpodium</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/onpodium</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 15:46:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>This is a successor of my previous project Podsite that was launched last year. We’re constantly improving OnPodium according to the feedback we get from existing customers.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[First 1000 Users Guide - 從構思到第一個1000個用戶的互動指南]]></title><description><![CDATA[一個完全互動的指南，在1個月內從構思到1000個用戶！由大量來自科技界人士的資源組成。由保羅-格雷厄姆和萊尼-拉奇茨基等科技人士提供的大量資源組成，以及一個互動界面，你可以記錄並從你的發現中學習!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/first-1000-users-guide</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/first-1000-users-guide</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 14:25:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A fully interactive guide on going from ideation to 1000 users within 1 month! Composed of tons of resources from tech figures like Paul Graham and Lenny Rachitsky, as well as an interactive interface where you can record and learn from your findings!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GitHub Wrapped - 你的代碼年]]></title><description><![CDATA[你在2021年寫了很多代碼--提交、拉動請求和評論。反思你的這一年，你所貢獻的項目，以及你所支持的開發者。開放源代碼。在Twitter上分享或添加到你的個人Readme。由Neat的團隊製作。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/github-wrapped-4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/github-wrapped-4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 14:01:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>You coded a lot in 2021 - commits, pull requests, and reviews. Reflect on your year, the projects you contributed to, and the developers you supported. Open source. Share on Twitter or add to your personal Readme. Made by the team at Neat.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How much is your SaaS worth? - 由463項近期交易提供的SaaS估值計算器]]></title><description><![CDATA[你應該得到一個更高的估值。現在你有數據來獲得它。利用我們的實時洞察力，確保你得到你的價值。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/how-much-is-your-saas-worth</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/how-much-is-your-saas-worth</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 14:01:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>You deserve a higher valuation. Now you have the data to get it. Use our real-time insights to make sure you get what you’re worth.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zen Flowchart 2.0 - 創建流程圖的最簡單工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[Zen Flowchart是最簡單的流程圖製作工具。受到全球160萬用戶的喜愛。從頭開始重建的新的強大功能。- 實時協作 - 更多的流程圖形狀 - 更乾淨和更快的用戶界面 - 圖標 - 自定義顏色]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zen-flowchart-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zen-flowchart-2-0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 13:06:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Zen Flowchart is the simplest flowchart maker. Loved by 1.6M users worldwide. Rebuilt from scratch with new powerful features: - Live Collaboration - More flowchart shapes - Cleaner &amp; faster UI - Icons - Custom colors</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PocketTube 3.0 - 一個全新的YouTube體驗]]></title><description><![CDATA[PocketTube是一種全新的YouTube體驗。管理和分類您的訂閱，創建羣組，使用自動標籤，標記爲已觀看，毫不費力地過濾您的視頻源，所有這些都在YouTube自己的界面中。可用於您的瀏覽器]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pockettube-3-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pockettube-3-0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 12:45:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>PocketTube is a brand new YouTube experience. Manage and sort your subscriptions, create groups, use auto tags, mark as watched, filter your video feed effortlessly, all its within YouTube&apos;s own interface. Available for your browser</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Customer Service Tips by LabiDesk - 50多個針對初創企業的免費客戶服務技巧]]></title><description><![CDATA[50多個客戶服務技巧! 我們把共同的規則和最佳做法放在一起，這些規則和最佳做法幫助許多公司在他們的客戶服務組織方式以及他們如何處理每一個客戶支持查詢的幫助下成長。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/customer-service-tips-by-labidesk</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/customer-service-tips-by-labidesk</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 11:46:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>50+ Customer Service Tips! We put together a list of common rules and best practices that helped so many companies grow with the help of the way their customer service was organized and how they handled each and every customer support inquiry.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sales Automation Playbook by NetHunt CRM - 通過全面的銷售自動化演練來完成工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[把它想象成一本銷售自動化的食譜。它一步一步地引導你完成所有銷售流程的自動化，從售前到售後；爲什麼、何時以及我們應該如何利用它。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sales-automation-playbook-by-nethunt-crm</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sales-automation-playbook-by-nethunt-crm</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 11:16:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Picture this as a cookbook for sales automation. Step-by-step, it walks you through automation for all your sales processes, from pre-sale to post-sale; why, when, and how we should utilize it.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Triage 2 - 爲您的收件箱提供急救服務]]></title><description><![CDATA[Triage是對那些努力保持收件箱頂部的人的急救措施。它並不試圖取代傳統的電子郵件軟件，而是讓你利用你的停機時間來迅速消除噪音和壓力。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/triage-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/triage-2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 11:16:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Triage is first aid for people who struggle to stay on top of their inbox. It doesn’t try to replace traditional email software, but lets you use your downtime to quickly remove the noise and stress.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Delta Investment Tracker - 追蹤你所有投資的應用程序，只做聰明的動作]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界第一的投資跟蹤應用程序。忘記電子表格，在一個地方管理你所有的投資。如果你投資於或關注一個或多個資產類別，如股票、加密貨幣或ETF，Delta就是你正在尋找的工具。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/delta-investment-tracker</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/delta-investment-tracker</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 10:30:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>World’s number one Investment Tracking app. Forget about spreadsheets and manage all your investments in one place. If you’re invested in or following one or multiple asset classes, such as stocks, cryptos or ETFs, Delta is the tool you were looking for.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MySuper.Fan - 識別你在YouTube上的頂級超級粉絲]]></title><description><![CDATA[通過MySuper.fan，您可以創建一個您的超級粉絲的排行榜；立即生成一個超級粉絲檔案，並深入瞭解您的超級粉絲在您的內容中的參與情況。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mysuper-fan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mysuper-fan</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 10:30:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With the MySuper.fan, you can create a leaderboard of your superfans; instantly generate a superfan profile and do a deep dive into your superfan&apos;s engagement across your content.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SEOptimer - SEO審計和報告工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[SEOptimer是一個全功能的SEO審計和報告平臺，可以在30秒內全面審查一個網站。數字機構可以使用SEOptimer爲他們的客戶和潛在客戶製作簡單而漂亮的PDF報告。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/seoptimer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/seoptimer</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 10:30:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>SEOptimer is a full-featured SEO Audit &amp; Reporting platform which can comprehensively review a website in under 30 seconds. Digital agencies can use SEOptimer to produce simple and beautiful PDF reports for their clients and prospects.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BuildBlocks - 發現用戶策劃的小衆無碼問題的資源]]></title><description><![CDATA[BuildBlocks是一個用戶策劃的資源平臺，幫助在幾分鐘內解決你的利基無代碼問題。發現和添加資源，提出問題併成爲社區的一部分。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/buildblocks</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/buildblocks</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 10:09:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>BuildBlocks is a user-curated resource platform to help solve your niche no-code problems in minutes. Discover and add resources, ask questions and become a part of the community.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Archimedes 2.0 - 有信心使投資成爲你生活中更大的一部分]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿基米德將投資簡化爲簡單、可操作的步驟，無論您的經驗如何。作爲您平易近人的投資教練，我們授權您以您想要的方式管理您的資金，實現您的目標。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/archimedes-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/archimedes-2-0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 09:23:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Archimedes simplifies investing into easy, actionable steps, no matter your experience. As your approachable investment coach, we empower you to manage your money the way you want to achieve your goals.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NativeBase Startup+ - 100多個用於網頁和手機的響應式React Native屏幕]]></title><description><![CDATA[NativeBase Startup+是一個由100多個響應性的、可訪問的、支持黑暗模式的、可生產的React Native屏幕組成的捆綁包，用於移動和網絡。依靠NativeBase v3的信任，使用這些高度主題化的屏幕來構建你的下一個夢想項目。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nativebase-startup</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nativebase-startup</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 09:05:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>NativeBase Startup+ is a bundle of 100+ responsive, accessible, dark mode supported and production ready React Native screens for mobile and web. Rely on the trust of NativeBase v3 and use these highly themeable screens to build your next dream project.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BitsForDigits - 爲自立門戶的創始人免費提供部分收購市場]]></title><description><![CDATA[BitsForDigits是世界上最大的部分收購市場。我們使創始人能夠匿名、簡單、免費地將少數股權和多數股權出售給專業投資者。今天就列出你的企業，以獲得已經在平臺上的+100個投資者的報價!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bitsfordigits</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bitsfordigits</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 08:50:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>BitsForDigits is the world’s #1 partial buyout marketplace. We make it anonymous, easy and free for founders to sell minority and majority stakes to professional investors. List your business today to get offers from the +100 investors already on the platform!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Popify - 使用社會證明彈出窗口提高你的轉換率]]></title><description><![CDATA[有了Popify，你可以創建設計出色的彈出式特別促銷通知，並通過顯示最近的客戶活動，如最近的銷售、添加到購物車、實時訪客計數器和評論，建立FOMO（害怕錯過）。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/popify</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/popify</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 20:48:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With Popify, you can create awesome designed popup notifications of special promotions and build FOMO (fear of missing out) by showing recent customer&apos;s activities like recent sales, add to cart, live visitor counter, and reviews.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Github Wrapped 2021 - 爲每個GitHub用戶提供個性化的回放視頻]]></title><description><![CDATA[獲取你的GitHub活動的個性化年度回顧視頻。輸入你的名字，一個下載的視頻將立即生成! 使用標籤&nbsp;#GithubWrapped在社交媒體上發佈。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/github-wrapped-2021</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/github-wrapped-2021</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 16:55:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Get your personalized Year in Review video of your GitHub activity. Enter your name and a downloaded video will be generated immediately! Post it on social media using the hashtag&amp;nbsp;#GithubWrapped.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[thirdweb - 輕鬆構建Web3應用程序和遊戲]]></title><description><![CDATA[⛏️ **建立**功能，如NFT、市場、代幣等，只需點擊幾下 🧰 **實用**SDK、小工具和接口，將web3功能整合到你的應用程序中 🕹️ **支持**區塊鏈遊戲、DAO、NFT卡平臺、生成藝術滴等。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/thirdweb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/thirdweb</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 14:25:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>⛏️ **Build** features such as NFT&apos;s, marketplaces, tokens, and more in a few clicks 🧰 **Utility** SDK&apos;s, widgets, and interfaces to integrate web3 features into your app 🕹️ **Powers** blockchain games, DAO&apos;s, NFT card platforms, generative art drops and more</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Platypus (Beta) - 與擁有相同價值觀的團隊相匹配]]></title><description><![CDATA[通過反思什麼對你的職業生活最重要，創建你的鴨嘴獸圖案。探索具有你的文化優先權的團隊，他們關心的事情與你相同。成爲 Platypus 的早期採用者，幫助我們塑造招聘的未來。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/platypus-beta</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/platypus-beta</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 13:38:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Create your Platypus Print by reflecting on what is most important to your professional life. Explore teams with your cultural priorities who care about the same things that you do. Become a Platypus early adopter and help us shape the future of recruitment.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SuccessRate - 通過校友們的反饋意見來改進你的YC/500/TC申請]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們歡迎你在截止日期前提交你的申請草案，以獲得校友的反饋。你越早提交，得到的反饋就越多。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/successrate</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/successrate</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 12:31:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>You are welcome to submit your draft application before a deadline to get alumni feedback. The sooner you submit more feedback you get.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Free AI Email Subject Line Generator - 使用AI和GPT-3創建有影響力的獨特主題詞]]></title><description><![CDATA[你是否已經厭倦了所有基本的主題行生成器，它們給你的是同樣老套的想法？使用基於GPT-3的免費人工智能電子郵件主題行生成器創建獨特的主題行。只需輸入電子郵件的主題，讓人工智能發揮它的魔力。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/free-ai-email-subject-line-generator</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/free-ai-email-subject-line-generator</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 11:25:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Are you tired of all the basic subject line generators that give you the same old cookie-cutter ideas? Create unique subject lines with a free AI email subject line generator based on GPT-3. Simply enter the topic of the email and let the AI do its magic.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Marketing4Makers Community - 想學習營銷的創客們的反饋羣體]]></title><description><![CDATA[Marketing4Makers是一個由希望提高營銷技能的創客組成的私人社區。每天，我們都會分享我們的奮鬥和勝利，並在營銷工作中相互幫助。我們每週都會召開電話會議，分享我們目前的行動並慶祝我們的勝利。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/marketing4makers-community</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/marketing4makers-community</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 11:01:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Marketing4Makers is a private community of makers that wants to grow their marketing skills Every day, we share our struggles and wins, and we help each other in our marketing efforts. We have a weekly call to share our current actions and celebrate our wins</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Static.app - 爲您的靜態網站提供一鍵式託管解決方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[Static.app是在線託管靜態HTML網站的最簡單方法。拖放一個帶有你的頁面或整個網站的檔案，我們將負責其餘的工作。一切都包括在內。SSL證書、代碼編輯器、表格和媒體存儲都在一個地方。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/static-app-1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/static-app-1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 10:47:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Static.app is the easiest way to host a static HTML website online. Drag-and-drop an archive with your page or an entire website and we will take care of the rest. Everything is included: SSL certificate, code editor, forms and media storage all in one place.</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>