<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Product Hunt 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Product Hunt 热门App，网站和产品]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 09:33:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Zero to MVP - 無需編碼即可構建應用程序的終極指南]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一週內學會不用編碼就能構建應用程序。21個章節，帶你完成無需編碼的應用程序構建過程，並有120多個無代碼工具的獎勵策劃，這些工具的下載量超過2000次。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zero-to-mvp</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zero-to-mvp</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 09:00:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Learn to build apps without coding in one week. 21 chapters that take you through the app-building process without coding, with bonus curation of 120+ No-code tools having over 2,000+ downloads.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alfread - 實際閱讀的文章被保存下來，供以後使用]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alfread是一種新型的稍後閱讀應用程序。它幫助你真正閱讀保存的文章。或者跳過它們。沒有壓力。Alfread幫助你重新發現你對閱讀你所保存的內容的熱愛。一次只讀一篇文章。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/alfread</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/alfread</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 08:46:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Alfread is a new kind of a read later app. It helps you to actually read saved articles. Or skip them. No pressure. Alfread helps you rediscover your love for reading what you&apos;ve saved. One article at a time.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Designify Pro - 在幾秒鐘內批量編輯任何數量的產品照片]]></title><description><![CDATA[批量編輯任何數量的產品照片，獲得高分辨率的下載，保存您的設計，並將Designify Pro API集成到您的網站、應用程序或工作流程中。讓我們的視覺人工智能處理您的產品照片--自動和在幾秒鐘內完成! 👉&nbsp; https://www.designify.com/pro]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/designify-pro</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/designify-pro</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 08:46:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Bulk-edit any number of product photos, get high-res downloads, save your designs and integrate the Designify Pro API into your website, app, or workflow. Let our visual AI handle your product photos - automatically and in seconds! 👉&amp;nbsp; https://www.designify.com/pro</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Directus 9 - 即時無代碼應用和動態API，適用於任何SQL數據庫]]></title><description><![CDATA[Directus將任何SQL數據庫變成一個無代碼的應用程序和強大的API。我們的開源平臺是完全免遷移的，無縫地分層在你新的或現有的數據庫之上，爲你提供一套工具來管理和連接你的內容。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/directus-9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/directus-9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 08:46:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Directus turns any SQL database into a no-code app and powerful API. Our open-source platform is completely migration-free, seamlessly layering on top of your new or existing database, providing you with a suite of tools to manage and connect your content.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Progressive Upload by api.video - 一種革命性的視頻處理方法]]></title><description><![CDATA[⏺ 同時錄製和上傳視頻 ⚡️ 爲您的用戶提供閃電般的屏幕和攝像頭錄製 📺 用視頻信息豐富您的產品和應用程序 💻&nbsp; 演示：https://upstream.a.video/ 🎁 3個月計劃的50%：給我們發電子郵件：hello@api.video]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/progressive-upload-by-api-video</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/progressive-upload-by-api-video</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 08:31:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>⏺ Record and upload videos simultaneously ⚡️ Offer lightning-fast screen and camera recordings to your users 📺 Enrich your products and apps with video messaging 💻&amp;nbsp; Demo: https://upstream.a.video/ 🎁 50% on plans for 3 months: email us at hello@api.video</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Founders at work - 策劃的150多個YC創業公司創始人的故事集]]></title><description><![CDATA[傑西卡-利文斯頓的書《工作中的創始人》（2007年，32個故事）激勵了成千上萬的創始人開始創業。我找到了150多個創始人的故事來激勵新一波的創始人。我希望FoundersAtWork.io能夠爲1000多個新創始人節省50-100個小時。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/founders-at-work-9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/founders-at-work-9</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 22:47:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Jessica Livingston&apos;s book &quot;Founders at work&quot; (2007, 32 stories) inspired thousands of founders to start startup. I find 150+ founders stories to inspire new wave of founders. I hope, that FoundersAtWork.io saves 50-100 hours for 1000+ new founders.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Betts Connect - 招聘的未來是連接]]></title><description><![CDATA[通過利用十多年的招聘經驗，我們創建了一個平臺，縮短了招聘時間，節省了招聘費用。只需選擇你要招聘的角色，通過配額和交易規模等關鍵績效指標過濾候選人，並安排面試。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/betts-connect-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/betts-connect-2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 18:48:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>By leveraging over a decade of recruiting experience, we created a platform that reduces time to hire and saves money on recruiting fees. Simply choose the roles you’re hiring for, filter candidates by KPIs like quota and deal size, and schedule interviews.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[TryDraw - 通過即時反饋學習數字藝術]]></title><description><![CDATA[用我們的工具提高你的線條藝術和觀察能力，突出你的錯誤。等待老師來糾正你的錯誤的日子已經一去不復返了。在簡單的 "一步一步 "教程的指導下，你將按照自己的節奏學習。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/trydraw</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/trydraw</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 14:21:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Improve your line art and observational skills with our tool that highlights your mistakes. Gone are the days of waiting for a teacher to correct your mistakes. Get guided by simple STEP BY STEP tutorials that will teach you at your own pace.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PassThru - 一個基於電子郵件的票據存儲應用程序 🎟]]></title><description><![CDATA[PassThru允許你在一個地方安全地存儲和管理你的所有門票、優惠券和預訂。不管是哪家票務供應商，它都能與每個系統配合使用。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/passthru</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/passthru</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 13:13:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>PassThru allows you to store and manage all your tickets, vouchers and reservations safely in one place. Regardless of the ticket provider; it works with every system.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PM vs PM Challenge - 你是一個項目經理還是一個產品經理？]]></title><description><![CDATA[那個懷疑你的內心聲音--"我是PM嗎？不，我是一名PM！" 這正是一個結束。但是如果你不願意面對殘酷的現實檢查，請馬上離開。不要告訴我們我們沒有警告你。Jk會很有趣。或者會嗎？]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pm-vs-pm-challenge</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pm-vs-pm-challenge</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 10:31:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>That inner voice doubting you - “Am I a PM? No, I am a PM!” This is an end to exactly that. But if you aren’t okay facing harsh reality checks, leave rn. Don’t tell us we didn’t warn you. Jk will be fun. Or will it? :P</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rebox - 你不知道你需要的回報服務]]></title><description><![CDATA[易於使用的設計，能夠安排你的回報。我們重新設計了產品的退貨方式，所以你不必這樣做!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/rebox</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/rebox</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 10:31:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Easy to use design, Ability to schedule your returns. We reimagined how products should be returned, So you don&apos;t have to!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[100 Free Userpics - 爲設計項目創建的免費頭像]]></title><description><![CDATA[收集了一百個免費的用戶圖片，特別是爲你的設計項目。每個頭像都有圓形和方形兩種格式。按您的意願編輯圖片，使其符合您的設計觀點。完全矢量，與Figma兼容。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/100-free-userpics</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/100-free-userpics</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 10:09:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Collection of a hundred free userpics especially for your design projects. Each avatar is available in circle and square formats. Edit images as you wish to make them fit your view of design. Fully vector, compatible with Figma.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[HUENIT - 面向創客的AI相機和模塊化機械臂]]></title><description><![CDATA[該機械臂，它具有人工智能視覺、語音識別、3D打印、激光雕刻、吸盤抓取器和筆工具。它也可以通過塊狀編碼、python、Arduino C++或G代碼進行編程。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/huenit</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/huenit</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 10:09:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The robotic arm which has AI vision, voice recognition, 3D printing, laser engraving, a suction grabber, and a pen tool. It can aslo be programmed via block coding, python, Arduino C++, or G-code.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Valuer - 向你自己的AI發現引擎問好]]></title><description><![CDATA[梳理數十萬個全球數據點來尋找最具創新性的技術和公司聽起來是否很性感？我們並不這麼認爲。這就是爲什麼我們開發了一個人工智能驅動的平臺來爲你做繁重的工作。基本上，我們使創新採購變得簡單和個性化。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/valuer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/valuer</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 10:09:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Does combing through hundreds of thousands of global data points to find the most innovative technologies and companies sound sexy? We didn&apos;t think so. Which is why we have developed an AI-driven platform to do the heavy lifting for you. Basically, we make innovation sourcing easy and personal.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weekend Club 2.0 - 開拓者聯合辦公俱樂部打造盈利產品]]></title><description><![CDATA[由65位創業者組成的社區，共同啓動和發展盈利的互聯網企業。在我們的遠程和IRL聯合辦公活動中與創始人會面，與大師們一起保持責任感，從內部導師那裏學習，並通過100多個偉大的折扣節省開支。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/weekend-club-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/weekend-club-2-0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 10:09:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The community of 65+ bootstrapped founders launching &amp; growing profitable internet businesses together. Meet founders at our remote &amp; IRL co-working events, stay accountable with masterminds, learn from in-house mentors and save with 100+ great discounts.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GrowthPost - 從100多個活躍的新聞通訊中獲得高增長的隱性工作機會]]></title><description><![CDATA[GrowthPost幫助你從頂級企業家、投資者撰寫的利基通訊中發現100多個工作，這些人來自Sahil Bloom、Julian Shapiro、Greg Isenberg、Lenny等人。GrowthPost做所有繁瑣的工作，並每週向你發送新工作的更新。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/growthpost</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/growthpost</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 09:13:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>GrowthPost helps you discover 100+ jobs from niche newsletters written by top Entrepreneurs, Investors from the likes of Sahil Bloom, Julian Shapiro, Greg Isenberg, Lenny, and many more. GrowthPost does all tedious work &amp; sends you weekly updates of new jobs.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Moonship Personalized AI Discounts - 個性化的人工智能折扣，爲Shopify商店帶來最大收益]]></title><description><![CDATA[Moonship使Shopify商戶能夠爲對價格敏感的客戶提供個性化的人工智能折扣，這些客戶需要一個小小的推動力來購買。我們使用機器學習模型，使電子商戶的銷售額平均增加20%，最高可達80%。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/moonship-personalized-ai-discounts</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/moonship-personalized-ai-discounts</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 09:13:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Moonship enables Shopify merchants to offer personalized AI discounts to price sensitive customers who need a little nudge to buy. We use machine learning models to enable ecomm merchants to increase their sales by an average of 20% and as much as 80%.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nifty Generator - 生成你的NFT集合，無需代碼]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nifty Generator讓你生成具有不同特徵的NFT集合，併爲Solana或Ethereum提供完整的元數據--不需要編碼。只需將你的圖像層連接到我們的工具，我們就能處理好生成的問題。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nifty-generator</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nifty-generator</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 09:13:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Nifty Generator lets you generate NFT collections with different traits, complete with metadata for Solana or Ethereum—no coding needed. Just connect your image layers to our tool, and we’ll handle the generation!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Teamble - 在Slack & Teams上提供簡單、持續和可操作的反饋]]></title><description><![CDATA[通過https://teamble.com，給予並獲得👍簡單、🔁連續和🎯可操作的反饋。在https://slack.com/apps/AS8DW2X44-teamble 和 https://teams.microsoft.com/l/app/ee7907e3-f0b3-4e18-b882-baa83e87812f 上無縫連接。利用強大的工具、模板和提示，在你的團隊中建立一個持續的反饋文化。開始免費使用teamble。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/teamble</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/teamble</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 08:40:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Give and get 👍 simple, 🔁 continuous, and 🎯 actionable feedback with https://teamble.com. Seamlessly on https://slack.com/apps/AS8DW2X44-teamble and https://teams.microsoft.com/l/app/ee7907e3-f0b3-4e18-b882-baa83e87812f. Leverage powerful tools, templates, and nudges to build a continuous feedback culture in your team. Start using teamble for FREE.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lalo - 一個值得紀念的地方]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lalo是一個緬懷的平臺。我們給你提供工具來講述你所愛的人的故事。在一個安全、無廣告的地方保存你的記憶。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/lalo</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/lalo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 05:16:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Lalo is a platform for remembrance. We give you the tools to tell the story of those you love. Preserve your memories in a safe, ad-free place.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Convert Menu - 將紙質菜單轉換爲在線QR菜單]]></title><description><![CDATA[自動將紙質菜單轉換爲數字QR菜單。只要上傳你的（pdf）紙質菜單，剩下的就由我們來做。一份數字菜單應在32小時內準備好。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/convert-menu</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/convert-menu</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 22:47:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Automatically convert paper menus into a digital QR menu. Just upload your (pdf) paper menu and we do the rest. A digital menu should be ready within 32 hours.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PASSCARD - 簡單、免費、離線的卡片密碼保存器]]></title><description><![CDATA[PASSCARD是一個幫助你記住卡片密碼的應用程序。該應用程序將密碼離線安全地保存在你的設備上。該應用程序將永遠不會保存或收集任何信息。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/passcard-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/passcard-2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 22:47:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>PASSCARD is an app that helps you to remember card passwords. The app saves passwords on your device offline and securely. The app will never save or collect any information.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Showping - 與朋友展示和購物，購物建議社交網絡]]></title><description><![CDATA[Showping是你口袋裏的口碑力量。Showping是一個獨特的應用程序，你可以與朋友分享你的願望和購買列表。在這個地方，人們可以閱讀他們信任的人的評論，並通過屏幕共享一起進行購物。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/showping</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/showping</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 21:03:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Showping is the power of word of mouth in your pocket. Showping is a unique app where you can share your Wish and Bought list with friends. It&apos;s a place where people can read reviews from someone they trust and do shopping together through screen sharing.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Able: 28-Day Affirmation Plan - 個性化的每日積極肯定語]]></title><description><![CDATA[每日肯定有助於將你的心態轉變爲積極思考。獲得一個爲期28天的個性化計劃，通過口頭肯定你的夢想和抱負，將幫助你變得感激、有靈感、有內容，只是更快樂而已]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/able-28-day-affirmation-plan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/able-28-day-affirmation-plan</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 17:11:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Daily affirmations help shift your mindset to positive thinking. Get a personalized plan for 28 days that will help you become grateful, inspired, content, and just happier by verbally affirming your dreams and ambitions!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Snout - 電子郵件嗅探器和人與公司的社交網絡。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Snout從嗅探互聯網上的公共數據，努力尋找人們和公司的電子郵件和社交網絡。找到客戶、影響者、投資者、員工和更多。200+國家 ★ 57M+公司 ★ 800M+人 ★ 150M+電子郵件地址]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/snout</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/snout</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 14:31:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Snout works hard from sniffing public data on the internet to find emails and social networks of people and companies. Find customers, influencers, investors, employees and more. ★ 200+ Countries ★ 57M+ Companies ★ 800M+ people ★ 150M+ emails address</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Favelent - 創建一個你最喜歡的內容的畫廊]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們想把你最喜歡的內容水晶化，並讓你向世界展示它！這就是我們的目標。在你的聽衆要求推薦時，與他們分享你的簡介。收集電子郵件並添加您的社會鏈接 發現他人的最佳發現。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/favelent</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/favelent</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 14:23:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We want to crystalize your most-favourite content and let you represent it to the world! Share your Profile with your audience whenever they ask for recommendations. Collect E-Mails and add your social links Discover the best findings of others.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[InSite - 在你的Shopify商店中添加一個收集反饋的小工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[Insite是一個強大而簡單的工具，幫助您瞭解客戶對您的要求。在5分鐘內將一個定製的、優雅的反饋調查嵌入到您的網站。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/insite-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/insite-2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 13:31:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Insite is a powerful yet simple tool that helps you learn what your customers want from you. Embed a custom, elegant feedback survey into your website in under 5 minutes.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aguapro - 我們從頂級社區爲初創企業尋找人才!]]></title><description><![CDATA[在 "產品 "和 "增長 "領域，從獨家、獨特和頂級的社區僱用積極的人才。利用複雜的技術，將工作要求與社區價值相一致，並與合適的申請人相匹配。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/aguapro</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/aguapro</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 12:52:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Hire motivated talent from the exclusive, distinct &amp; top communities in ‘product’ and ‘growth’ domain. Using sophisticated techniques, job requirements are aligned to community values and match with the right applicant.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Health Hub OS (Notion Template) - 一個用來管理所有與健康有關的事物的操作系統!]]></title><description><![CDATA[❤️一個帶有+15個獨特模板和+10個跟蹤器的操作系統模板，幫助你在一個連接的樞紐中跟蹤與健康有關的一切。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/health-hub-os-notion-template</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/health-hub-os-notion-template</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 11:23:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>❤️ An Operating System Template with +15 unique templates &amp; +10 trackers to help you track everything health-related in one connected Hub.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Authorizer - 開源認證和授權解決方案]]></title><description><![CDATA[Authorizer是一個開源的認證和授權解決方案，適用於你的應用程序。帶上你的數據庫，對用戶信息有完全的控制。你可以自行託管授權器實例並連接到任何SQL數據庫。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/authorizer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/authorizer</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 10:40:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Authorizer is an open-source authentication and authorization solution for your applications. Bring your database and have complete control over the user information. You can self-host authorizer instances and connect to any SQL database.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[lllook - 可定製的表情符號線圖標集合]]></title><description><![CDATA[一組可定製的SVG表情符號線圖標。在瀏覽器中直接調整顏色、大小和筆畫寬度，然後使用SVG圖標爲你的設計添加一些有趣的小表情符號。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/lllook</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/lllook</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:16:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A collection of customizable SVG emoji line icons. Adjust the color, size and stroke width right in the browser, and then use the SVG icons to add some fun little expressive characters to your designs.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Porndora - 個性化的、由人工智能驅動的色情]]></title><description><![CDATA[Porndora是個性化的情色小說。我們使用人工智能來學習你喜歡的東西，併爲每個用戶建立一個個性化的快樂檔案。我們正在建立一個成人網站，爲每個人服務，無論其性別、性取向或癖好如何。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/porndora</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/porndora</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 20:36:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Porndora is personalized erotica. We use AI to learn what you like over time and build a personalized pleasure profile for every user. We’re building an adult site that works for everyone, regardless of gender, sexual orientation, or kink.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dash 6.0 - 即時離線訪問200多個API文檔集]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dash可以立即搜索200多個API的離線文檔集，100多個小抄等。Dash也是一個代碼片段管理器，支持使用縮寫的片段擴展。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/dash-6-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/dash-6-0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:19:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Dash instantly searches offline documentation sets for 200+ APIs, 100+ cheat sheets and more. Dash is also a code snippet manager and supports snippet expansion using abbreviations.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fisio - 最佳在線簡歷生成器]]></title><description><![CDATA[Fisio簡歷生成器允許你用一個直觀的工具快速、輕鬆地創建一個原創的簡歷。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fisio</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fisio</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:19:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Fisio resume builder allows you to create an original resule quickly and easily with an intuitive tool.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GTD Dashboard - 一體化的儀表板來完成事情]]></title><description><![CDATA[一個全面的Notion儀表盤，幫助你節省時間，完成更多工作。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/gtd-dashboard</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/gtd-dashboard</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:19:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A comprehensive Notion dashboard that helps you save time, and get more done.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[InstaaSnap - 保存Instagram的公共帖子和卷軸，開源節流]]></title><description><![CDATA[InstaaSnap是一個開源的Instagram帖子保存器API、WebApp、iOS和Andoid應用。我創建它是爲了保存Instagram上的一些重要信息。它是隱私友好的，沒有數據庫，沒有分析，沒有日誌，沒有cookies，加上開源的。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/instaasnap</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/instaasnap</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:19:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>InstaaSnap is a open-source Instagram post saver API, WebApp, iOS and Andoid app. I created it to save some important feeds from Instagram. It&apos;s Privacy-friendly, no database, no analytics, no logs, no cookies, plus open-source.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Passky - Passky是一個簡單、現代和開源的密碼管理器]]></title><description><![CDATA[Passky是一個簡單、現代、輕便、開源和安全的密碼管理器。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/passky-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/passky-2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:19:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Passky is a simple, modern, lightweight, open-source and secure password manager.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[W3Schools Spaces - 用W3Schools Spaces建立您自己的網站]]></title><description><![CDATA[W3Schools允許你創建自己的網站並與他人分享。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/w3schools-spaces</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/w3schools-spaces</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:19:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>W3Schools allows you to create your own website and share it with others.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Office Club Illustration pack - 觀念式的藝術指導和插圖]]></title><description><![CDATA[無論你是創建一個網站或移動應用程序，展示一個投資組合，發佈一個博客，還是一個電子商務商店 - Office Club的100幅插圖和設計的藝術指導幫助你創造最好的產品。現場：https://overflow.design/]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/office-club-illustration-pack</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/office-club-illustration-pack</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 10:45:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Whether you’re creating a website or mobile app, showcasing a portfolio, publishing a blog, or an e-commerce store — Office Club’s 100 illustrations and designed art directions help you create the best possible products. Live: https://overflow.design/</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ultimate Free Trial Card - 幫助你獲得免費試用的虛擬卡]]></title><description><![CDATA[使用Zerobalance虛擬卡進行所有的免費試用註冊，永遠不用擔心被收費或取消。探索我們的100多個不同類別的免費試用庫，無憂無慮地享受所有的好處。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ultimate-free-trial-card</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ultimate-free-trial-card</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 10:35:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Use Zerobalance virtual cards for all your Free-Trial Signups and never worry about getting charged or cancellations. Explore our library of 100+ free trials across different categories and enjoy all the benefits without a worry.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jobstack - 尋找工作。變得簡單。]]></title><description><![CDATA[構建你的求職過程。📈 帶有15個以上模板的個人簡歷生成器 😃 帶有3000個以上入圍資料的簡易網絡指南 ✍🏻 準備使用超過16個角色的個人CRM]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/jobstack</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/jobstack</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 09:32:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Structure your job search process: 📈 Personal Resume Builder with 15+ templates 😃 Easy Networking Guides with 3000+ shortlisted profiles ✍🏻 Ready to use Personal CRM for over 16 roles</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ExplodingCommunities - 發現增長最快的在線社區]]></title><description><![CDATA[ExplodingCommunites是一個擁有Reddit上增長最快的在線社區的數據庫，可以支撐你的下一個業務。它幫助你儘早發現趨勢性社區，發現隱藏的商業機會，並建立基於社區的產品。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/explodingcommunities</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/explodingcommunities</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 22:47:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>ExplodingCommunites is a database with the fastest-growing online communities on Reddit that can sustain your next business. It helps you discover trending communities early, uncover hidden business opportunities, and build community-based products.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenIn 3 - 自定義MacOS中的鏈接和文件打開方式]]></title><description><![CDATA[OpenIn幫助你管理Mac上的鏈接和文件的打開方式。對於每個鏈接，你可以從多個瀏覽器、郵件客戶端或應用程序中選擇文件，或根據文件或鏈接的打開位置，或根據位置或域進行配置。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/openin-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/openin-3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 22:47:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>OpenIn helps you manage how links and files open on your Mac. For every link, you can select from multiple browsers, mail clients or apps for files, or configure based on where the file or link is opened, or based on location or domain.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Notion Travel Template - 清楚地旅行。]]></title><description><![CDATA[🙅🏽♀️忘記電子表格、電子郵件、訂票網站和一打雜亂的硬盤或有限的雲存儲的文件。💻使用這個Notion旅行模板，把所有東西都放在一個地方，旅行時從雜亂無章到清晰明瞭。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/notion-travel-template</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/notion-travel-template</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 19:01:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>🙅🏽‍♀️ Forget spreadsheets, e-mails, booking sites and a dozen documents cluttering your hard drives or limited cloud storage. 💻 Use this Notion travel template to everything in one place and move from clutter to clarity when travelling.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[defly.ai - 以太坊費用優化器]]></title><description><![CDATA[你可能聽說過，甚至經歷過因爲交易失敗而損失以太坊交易費的痛苦。defly.ai使用實時區塊鏈數據和Spice.ai機器學習，進行最安全的AI驅動的估計，在使用Uniswap時挽救損失的費用。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/defly-ai</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/defly-ai</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 17:10:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>You may have heard of or even experienced the pain of losing your Ethereum transaction fee because your trade failed. defly.ai uses real-time blockchain data &amp; Spice.ai machine learning for the safest AI-powered estimates to save lost fees when using Uniswap.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Job Search Journey - 帶有幫助求職者的工具的數字市場]]></title><description><![CDATA[找工作不一定很困難。在世界第一個職業市場上找到由獲獎的簡歷作家和職業專家設計的模板和腳本。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/job-search-journey</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/job-search-journey</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 14:31:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Job searching doesn&apos;t have to be hard. Find templates and scripts designed by award-winning resume writers and career experts on the world&apos;s first career marketplace.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[High Signal - 每週與成功的創始人通話]]></title><description><![CDATA[High Signal是一個爲創始人創造收入的小型社區。我們每週都會在Zoom通話，以分享我們的進展，討論我們的目標，並在我們遇到困難時獲得幫助。我們也有一個Telegram羣組來分享建議。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/high-signal</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/high-signal</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 13:33:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>High Signal is a small community for founders making revenue. We meet for Zoom calls every week in order to share our progress, talk through our goals and get help when we get stuck. We also have a Telegram group for sharing advice.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[glyde - 最時尚、最酷、最快速的報稅方式]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們在手機上做任何事情，爲什麼不在稅務上做呢？有了Glyde，你可以預先將收入、扣除額、稅收抵免、銀行賬戶等信息填入你的ITR，從你的經紀人和投資平臺導入交易以及更多。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/glyde-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/glyde-3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 13:33:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>we do everything on our phones, so why not taxes too? with glyde, you can pre-fill your ITR with incomes, deductions, tax credits, bank accounts. import trades from your broker and investment platform &amp; much more. save, pay, file &amp; track taxes with a few taps.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lofly - 用LOFI節拍和大自然的聲音提高生產力]]></title><description><![CDATA[欣賞帶有自然聲音的Lofi節拍。從17種以上的自然聲音和17種以上的Lo-fi曲目中選擇。用Pomodoro提高你的工作效率並保持有序。享受與成員聊天的樂趣。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/lofly</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/lofly</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 12:27:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Enjoy lofi beats with nature sounds. Choose from 17+ nature sounds and 17+ lo-fi tracks. Increase your productivity and stay organized with Pomodoro. Enjoy chatting with members and have fun.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kizie for Twitter - 一個更乾淨、更好的方式來瀏覽Twitter]]></title><description><![CDATA[介紹一下Kizie，一個瀏覽Twitter的新方式 ✨ 更乾淨，更好，無廣告的主頁和簡介時間線 ⚡️ 專業功能，可以用twitter做更多事情（閱讀第一條評論的清單👇） 殨在網頁和PWA上工作 👉試試吧：https://kizie.co]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/kizie-for-twitter</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/kizie-for-twitter</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 11:49:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Introducing Kizie, a new way to browse Twitter 🐤 ✨ cleaner, better, ad-free home and profile timelines ⚡️ pro features to do more with twitter(read first comment for the list 👇) 📱 works on web and as PWA 👉 try it: https://kizie.co</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>