<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Product Hunt 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Product Hunt 热门App，网站和产品]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 02:24:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[OtpNinja - 輕鬆設置OTP API]]></title><description><![CDATA[OtpNinja是一個即插即用的Otp服務，適用於希望爲客戶添加2Auth層並通過短信發送驗證碼的應用程序和企業。該應用程序非常容易創建並通過短信發送代碼，並將驗證結果發回給應用程序。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/otpninja</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/otpninja</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 01:54:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>OtpNinja is a Plug and play Otp service for Apps And businesses who wish to add 2Auth layer and send code Verification By sms for their clients. The Api is super easy creates and send the code by SMS also send back to the app the Verification results.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WebBag - 易於學習的教育平臺]]></title><description><![CDATA[在我們產品的幫助下，你可以不再攜帶沉重的公文包。書籍、筆記本、日記和測試將只需一次點擊就能獲得。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/webbag</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/webbag</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 22:24:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With the help of our product, you can no longer carry a heavy briefcase. Books, notebooks, diaries and tests will be available in just one click</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GetMails - 讓每個人都能簡單地進行冷接觸]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們討厭冷門的外展，因爲大多數工具要麼太複雜，要麼需要很多其他工具並行才能使外展發揮作用。因此，我們決定爲營銷人員簡化冷推廣過程。歡迎加入GetMails大家庭❤️]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/getmails</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/getmails</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 17:30:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We hated cold outreach because most of the tools are either too complicated or they need a lot of other tools parallel to make the outreach work. So, we decided to simplify the cold outreach process for marketers. Welcome to GetMails Family ❤️</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Santa Hat Profile Pic Maker - 在你的個人照片上免費添加一頂聖誕節聖誕老人的帽子]]></title><description><![CDATA[通過在Twitter、Instagram、LinkedIn和Tiktok的社交媒體資料圖片上添加聖誕老人的帽子來慶祝2021年聖誕節。我們會自動刪除你的背景，並添加很酷的背景圖片和效果!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/santa-hat-profile-pic-maker</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/santa-hat-profile-pic-maker</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 14:46:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Celebrate 2021 Christmas by adding a Santa hat to your social media profile picture on Twitter, Instagram, LinkedIn, and Tiktok. We remove your background &amp; add cool background images &amp; effects automatically!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Paperback - 更簡單、更整潔的維基頁面的替代品]]></title><description><![CDATA[平裝書是一種比維基頁面更簡單、更整潔的選擇。與其把東西埋在深層次的結構中，它讓你用你的鏈接、文件和註釋創建簡明的列表。然後，人們可以真正找到他們需要的東西，而不是一直在問。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/paperback-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/paperback-3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 13:48:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Paperback is a simpler and tidier alternative to wiki pages. Instead of burying stuff in deep hierarchies, it lets you create concise lists with your links, files, and notes. Then, people can actually find what they need, instead of asking around all the time.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Incoggo - 免費的付費廣告屏蔽器--閱讀《紐約時報》、《華爾街日報》、《華盛頓郵報》等]]></title><description><![CDATA[- ⛔️Incoggo是一個免費的廣告屏蔽器，用於付費牆。適用於Mac，即將推出Windows版本! - 📚 自動免費解鎖新聞和文章，更方便地獲取新聞和信息! - 🗞️ 15+頂級酒館已解鎖。完整列表見go.incoggo.com/pubs]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/incoggo</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/incoggo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 09:16:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>- ⛔️ Incoggo is a free adblocker for paywalls. Available for Mac, coming soon for Windows! - 📚 Automatically unlock news and articles for free and get easier access to news and information! - 🗞️ 15+ top pubs unlocked. Full list at go.incoggo.com/pubs</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hypervault - 安全地管理並與你的團隊分享敏感數據]]></title><description><![CDATA[告別用平面文字 "安全筆記 "來存儲非密碼的東西。Hypervault爲企業提供解決方案，以安全地存儲、共享和組織多種類型的敏感數據，而不僅僅是密碼。對IT部門、開發人員、機構和初創企業來說是非常好的選擇!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hypervault</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hypervault</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:01:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Say goodbye to flat text “secure notes” to store anything that’s not a password. Hypervault offers the solution for businesses to securely store, share and organize many types of sensitive data, not just passwords. Great for IT, Devs, Agencies, and Startups!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[QRToon - 把你無聊的二維碼變成吸引人的藝術品]]></title><description><![CDATA[把你無聊的二維碼變成吸引人的藝術作品。不用擔心，它們的工作方式仍與您的原始代碼相同。只要提供一個二維碼和一張自拍，就可以準備好與大家分享它的卡通版本了!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/qrtoon-toonified-qr-maker</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/qrtoon-toonified-qr-maker</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 21:01:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Turn your boring QR codes into catchy artworks. No worries, they will still work the same way as your original codes. Just provide a QR code and a selfie and get ready to share its Toon version with everybody!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Havoc Shield - 一體化的網絡安全平臺。12個工具在一個儀表板上]]></title><description><![CDATA[一個爲小型企業打造的經濟實惠的一體化網絡安全平臺。通過一個儀表板中的十幾種工具，提供漏洞掃描、全球密碼管理器、防病毒/防惡意軟件威脅保護、策略管理等，讓人放心。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/havoc-shield</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/havoc-shield</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 18:49:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>An affordable, all-in-one cybersecurity platform built for small business. Get peace of mind through a dozen tools in one dashboard offering vulnerability scans, global password manager, antivirus/anti-malware threat protection, policy management and more.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SaaS Advent Calendar 2021 - 在降臨的每一天，解鎖獨家SaaS交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[每一天，都可以解鎖一些法國最好的SaaS公司的獨家優惠。有些你知道，有些你不知道；但大多數你會喜歡。快來加入聖誕老人的隊伍，享受一些樂趣吧！😀]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/saas-advent-calendar-2021-1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/saas-advent-calendar-2021-1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 15:01:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>For each day of advent, unlock exclusive deals on some of the best French SaaS companies. Some you&apos;ll know, some you won&apos;t; but most of them you&apos;ll love. Come join Santa&apos;s slede and have some fun 😀</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Greety - 免費創建獨特的、基於視頻的聖誕卡。]]></title><description><![CDATA[正在尋找一份特別的聖誕禮物嗎？只需填寫一個表格，附上一個Youtube視頻，就能得到一個基於視頻的賀卡鏈接，給你的朋友和家人一個驚喜。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/greety</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/greety</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 14:24:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Looking for a special gift for Christmas? Simply fill out a form, attach a Youtube video and get a link to a video-based greeting card to surprise your friends and family.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[250+ Trends for 2022 - 來自埃森哲、Gartner、Instagram、麥肯錫的70多個報告]]></title><description><![CDATA[2022年的250多個趨勢，來自70多個最近發佈的趨勢報告。 ft: 埃森哲、本尼迪克特-埃文斯、德勤、電通、福雷斯特、福布斯、Fjord、Gartner、Instagram、麥肯錫、Next Atlas、奧美、普華永道、Pinterest、Springwise、Sparks & Honey、Trendhunter、Unity，等等。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/250-trends-for-2022</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/250-trends-for-2022</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 13:46:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>250+ trends for 2022 from 70+ recently released trend reports. ft: Accenture, Benedict Evans, Deloitte, Dentsu, Forrester, Forbes, Fjord, Gartner, Instagram, McKinsey, Next Atlas, Ogilvy, PWC, Pinterest, Springwise, Sparks &amp; Honey, Trendhunter, Unity, &amp; more.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Project Shasta from Adobe - AI驅動的網絡音頻錄製和編輯]]></title><description><![CDATA[Project Shasta將人工智能驅動的音頻錄製和編輯帶入網絡，無需下載。現在，任何人都可以創建聽起來很專業的音頻，而不需要成爲專業人士。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/project-shasta-from-adobe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/project-shasta-from-adobe</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 11:47:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Project Shasta brings AI-powered audio recording and editing to the web, no download required. Now anyone can create audio that sounds professional, without needing to be a professional.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[eesel Extensions - 你所有的工作都在一個地方 - 現在也在火狐上了]]></title><description><![CDATA[eesel是對你的瀏覽器歷史的一個過濾器，只顯示與工作有關的網頁。它幾乎適用於任何工具。它在本地運行，所以你的工作永遠不會離開你的電腦。在我們在Chrome瀏覽器上推出幾個月後，我們現在也在Firefox上了!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/eesel-extensions</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/eesel-extensions</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 11:20:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>eesel is a filter on your browser history to just show pages relevant for work. It works with pretty much any tool. It runs locally, so your work never leaves your computer. A few months after our launch on Chrome, we’re now on Firefox too!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Podcast Cover Template - 用於播客的播客封面模板]]></title><description><![CDATA[購買後你將擁有這些東西😊 ▶ 101個播客封面 ▶ 101個Instagram帖子 ▶ 101件Youtube縮略圖 完全可編輯的播客封面設計 Figma - Adobe XD - Photoshop (Comig Soon)]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/podcast-cover-template</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/podcast-cover-template</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 10:16:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>You&apos;ll Have These When You Buy 😊 ▶ 101 Podcast Covers ▶ 101 Instagram Posts ▶ 101 Pieces Youtube Thumbnails Fully Editable Podcast Cover Designs Figma • Adobe XD • Photoshop (Comig Soon)</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Odyssey - 我們是一個學習型DAO，創造高質量的免費web3教育。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Odyssey是一個學習型DAO，其使命是讓下一個100萬人加入web3。 我們已經爲web3的入門、DeFi、DAO、NFT等編寫了高質量的ELI5指南。現在就開始學習👇]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/odyssey-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/odyssey-2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 10:01:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Odyssey is a learning DAO on a mission to onboard the next 1 million people to web3. We&apos;ve written quality ELI5 guides for intro to web3, DeFi, DAOs, NFTs, and more. Start learning now 👇</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Songtastic - 一個有趣的測試，測試你的音樂知識]]></title><description><![CDATA[Spotify Wrapped無處不在，展示了我們對歌曲的熱愛。但是，你對你最常聽的歌曲到底有多瞭解？帶上Songtastic轉一轉，瞭解一下你的分數吧!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/songtastic</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/songtastic</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 09:17:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Spotify Wrapped is everywhere showcasing our love for songs. But how well do you really know your most listened songs? Take Songtastic for a spin and get to know your score!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amon Wallet - 用Amon保護、管理和使用你的加密貨幣]]></title><description><![CDATA[Amon是由千禧一代創立的，他們致力於建立一個加密貨幣和法幣並存的世界。我們通過我們的Amon錢包、Amon Earn和即將推出的Amon卡，使加密貨幣服務變得簡單。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/amon-wallet</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/amon-wallet</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 09:01:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Amon was founded by millennials who strive for a world where crypto &amp; fiat co-exist. We make crypto services simple with our Amon Wallet, Amon Earn and the forthcoming Amon Card.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[HackerRank Interview - 點擊，採訪，就完成了]]></title><description><![CDATA[一體化的遠程技術採訪解決方案。同時編輯代碼，在虛擬白板上進行協作，並在你的瀏覽器中訪問一套面試問題的樣本。不需要下載。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hackerrank-interview</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hackerrank-interview</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 07:26:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>An all-in-one solution for remote technical interviewing. Simultaneously edit code, collaborate on virtual whiteboards, and access a sample set of interview questions all within your browser. No downloads required.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[heylogin - 無密碼登錄你的所有網絡賬戶]]></title><description><![CDATA[注重用戶體驗的登錄管理使heylogin變得簡單而方便。只要在你的智能手機上輕輕一掃，你就可以一鍵登錄到你的任何網絡賬戶。不再需要密碼了。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/heylogin</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/heylogin</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 20:28:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Login management with a focus on user experience makes heylogin simple and convenient. Just swipe on your Smartphone and you can log into any of your web accounts with just one click. No more passwords needed.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Web3 Army - 在加密貨幣、Web3和區塊鏈領域找工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[到2027年，全球GDP的10%（約9.7萬億美元）將在區塊鏈上。有一個全新的世界要建立，我們需要一支雄心勃勃的專業人員的軍隊來實現它。Web3Army幫助你找到跳入這個行業的最佳機會。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/web3-army</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/web3-army</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 18:52:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The 10% of global GDP (~$9.7 Trillion) will be on the blockchain by 2027. There&apos;s a whole new world to build and we need an army of ambitious professionals to make it. Web3Army helps you find the best opportunities to jump into the industry.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ngage - 爲您的混合會議提供現場演示、問答和投票。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在全年的會議和活動中，通過現場演示、現場投票、測驗、問答和文字雲，吸引聽衆。用易於使用的在線編輯器建立互動幻燈片。在你的演講中加入實時流媒體，並將互動遊戲化。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ngage-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ngage-2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 18:40:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Engage audiences for meetings &amp; events throughout the year with live presentations, live polls, quizzes, Q &amp; A, and word cloud. Build interactive slides with the easy-to-use online editor. Add live streaming to your presentations and gamify interaction.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[360+ OKR Examples Directory - 精心策劃的科技界每個角色的目標實例清單]]></title><description><![CDATA[對於領導者和IC來說，目標是一些最難想出的東西。這就是爲什麼我們擴大了我們的圖書館，包括360多個目標和OKR的例子，包括來自G2、GitLab和Privy的貢獻。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/360-okr-examples-directory</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/360-okr-examples-directory</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 15:33:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Goals are some of the hardest things for leaders and ICs to come up with. That’s why we’ve expanded our library to include over 360 goal and OKR examples, including contributions from G2, GitLab, and Privy.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Potential - 今天就開啓你的最佳生活]]></title><description><![CDATA[潛力幫助你重新獲得你的注意力和習慣--讓你控制你所做的事情，你的感覺，以及你成爲誰。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/potential</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/potential</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 14:01:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Potential helps you reclaim your attention and habits — giving you control over what you do, how you feel, and who you become.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fanalyze Voice - SIRI用於NFL橄欖球幻想和體育投注數據]]></title><description><![CDATA[你所有的NFL幻想或體育投注問題的SIRI。通過語音或文字輸入詢問有關NFL統計數據、球員和球隊信息、大/小球預測、賠率等問題。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fanalyze-voice</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fanalyze-voice</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 13:06:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The SIRI for all your NFL Fantasy or sports betting questions. Ask questions about NFL statistics, player and team info, over/under predictions, odds, and more through your voice or text input.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[nuka - 你將購買的最後一臺筆記本]]></title><description><![CDATA[嗨，這是nuka.me! BBC專題報道和3次reddot獎的永恆文具 可重複使用的筆記本和永無止境的鉛筆 它配備了一個應用程序，將手寫變成數字 10月開始發貨 目前已售罄 6500/6500 https://nuka.me/buy/，價格爲-30%，2月獲得一個]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nuka</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nuka</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 12:10:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Hi, it&apos;s nuka.me! BBC featured &amp; 3 times reddot awarded eternal stationery Reusable notebook &amp; never-ending pencil It comes with an app that turns handwriting into digital Shipping started Oct. Currently sold out 6500/6500 https://nuka.me/buy/ with -30%, get one in Feb</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Typewise Text Prediction API (Beta) - 在你的軟件中添加谷歌風格的智能撰寫]]></title><description><![CDATA[使用Typewise API（Beta）在幾分鐘內將先進的文本預測和自動更正AI添加到您的軟件或平臺： 🤖 下一個單詞和句子預測 🔤 自動更正（-75%的錯字） 🌎 語言檢測 😵 表情符號搜索 🔒 100%隱私，在🇨🇭製造]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/typewise-text-prediction-api-beta</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/typewise-text-prediction-api-beta</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 10:47:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Add advanced text prediction and autocorrect AI to your software or platform in minutes with Typewise API (Beta): 🤖 Next-word and sentence prediction 🔤 Autocorrection (-75% typos) 🌎 Language Detection 😵‍ Emoji Search 🔒 100% Privacy, made in 🇨🇭</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pioneer 3.0 - 創始人的家在第0天]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們將在先鋒計劃中增加一個新的選項。除了成爲先鋒的所有現有好處外，你的公司有2%的投資。我們還將增加一個爲期一個月的硅谷之旅，與其他創始人一起。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pioneer-3-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pioneer-3-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 10:17:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We’re adding a new option to the Pioneer offer: 2% of your company for a $20k investment, in addition to all the existing benefits of becoming a Pioneer. We&apos;re also adding a monthlong trip to Silicon Valley with fellow founders.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Virtual Event Chat Kit - 用於建立應用內虛擬活動聊天的UI工具包和示例應用程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[100多個精心設計的屏幕凝聚成映射出的流程，因此您和您的團隊可以跳入Figma，比以往任何時候都更快地創建您自己的定製活動聊天。示例應用程序顯示了Stream的聊天API，該API也可免費用於個人使用和小型項目，爲後端提供支持。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/virtual-event-chat-kit</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/virtual-event-chat-kit</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 10:00:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>100+ polished screens coalesce into mapped-out flows so you and your team can jump into Figma and create your own custom event chat faster than ever. The sample app shows Stream&apos;s chat API, also free for personal use and small projects, powering the backend.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2021 Looped - 關於2021年，你的日曆怎麼說？]]></title><description><![CDATA[好奇地想知道你是如何在工作中花費時間的？2021年的Looped對你的日曆年進行了彙總，併產生了獨特的見解，如在會議中花費的時間，會見的人數以及其他一些很酷的統計。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/2021-looped</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/2021-looped</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:48:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Curious to know how you spend your time at work? 2021 Looped rounds up your calendar year and generates unique insights like time spent in meetings, the number of people met along with some other cool stats.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Detail 2 - 簡單的電影式視頻]]></title><description><![CDATA[用你的Mac錄製和流傳高質量的視頻。通過場景、多鏡頭和自動取景，將你的 Mac 變成一個製作室。細節可與你的 iPhone、iPad、內置網絡攝像頭或任何其他攝像頭一起使用。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/detail-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/detail-2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:48:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Record and stream high-quality video with your Mac. Turn your Mac into a production studio with Scenes, multi-cam, and auto framing. Detail works with your iPhone, iPad, built-in webcam, or any other camera.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Multiversial - 科技和商業新聞變得更聰明的西班牙語日報]]></title><description><![CDATA[MultiVersial是一份每日通訊，以西班牙語提供最新的科技商業信息。語言仍然是獲取知識的一個障礙。一份有趣而簡單的通訊，讓你在5分鐘內掌握最新信息，瞭解科技戰略，實現專業成長。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/multiversial</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/multiversial</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:16:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>MultiVersial is a daily newsletter with the latest in tech business in Spanish. Languages are still a barrier to accessing knowledge. A fun and simple newsletter that allows you to stay up to date, understand tech strategy, and grow professionally in 5 mins</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Opal C1 - 第一個幫助你看起來更好的專業網絡攝像機。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們正在爲那些與他們的工作--他們的團隊、員工、客戶--的主要聯繫是通過視頻通話的人建立Opal。我們希望通過一個即插即用的系統，讓每個人都能輕鬆擁有專業的設置。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/opal-c1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/opal-c1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:16:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We’re building Opal for anyone who’s primary connection to their job – their team, their employees, their customers – is through video calls. We want to make it easy for everyone to have a professional setup, with a single plug and play system.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Face Swapper - 免費交換面孔，前所未有]]></title><description><![CDATA[忘記那些來自圖片庫的過度使用的面孔。忘掉有不適當許可證的照片。改變面孔或身體，在廣告、電子商務、社交媒體、教育、光鮮的雜誌等方面使用它們。卓越的質量。無與倫比的分辨率。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/face-swapper</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/face-swapper</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:01:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Forget about overused faces from stock photos. Forget about photos with an inappropriate license. Change faces or bodies and use them in ads, e-commerce, social media, education, glossy magazines, etc. Exceptional quality. Unrivaled resolution.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ripple - 掌控你的情緒，贏得一天，每一天]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ripple是一款情緒跟蹤應用程序，通過擺脫焦慮、抑鬱和毒性，幫助人們改善心理健康。只要在1到10的範圍內選擇你的滿意度和能量水平。Ripple將翻譯你的情緒，並將其轉化爲文字!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ripple-13</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ripple-13</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:01:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Ripple is a mood tracking app that helps people improve their mental health by getting rid of anxiety, depression, and toxicity. Just choose your satisfaction and energy level on a scale of 1 to 10. Ripple will translate your emotions and put them into words!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AutoCloud - 自動化的三維雲基礎設施圖和洞察力]]></title><description><![CDATA[對於在AWS、Azure和GCP上運行工作負載的人來說，AutoCloud可以自動繪製架構圖，進行合規性檢查和漂移檢測。使用3D環境或通過查詢GraphQL端點來探索洞察力。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/autocloud</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/autocloud</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 08:48:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>For anyone running workloads on AWS, Azure, and GCP, AutoCloud automates architecture diagrams, compliance checks, and drift detection. Explore insights using a 3D environment or by querying a GraphQL endpoint.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Magic Sidebar by BlackMagic.so - 爲Twitter提供強大的增強體驗]]></title><description><![CDATA[Magic Sidebar是Twitter的最佳瀏覽器擴展。今天就使用它，解開你從不知道的見解，與你的受衆更好地溝通，並建立強大的1：1關係。也可使用iOS和Android的移動應用程序!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/magic-sidebar-by-blackmagic-so</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/magic-sidebar-by-blackmagic-so</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 08:36:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Magic Sidebar is the best browser extension for Twitter. Use it today and unlock insights you never knew about, communicate better with your audience, and build strong 1:1 relationships. Mobile apps for iOS and Android are also available!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Creativity Booster by Alpe Audio - 爲你的教學和內容尋找故事和例子]]></title><description><![CDATA[不再有寫作障礙。不要一直糾結於如何打開你的課程、文章或視頻。自動生成偉大的開場鉤子、故事和相關的例子，涉及你想教的或想寫的任何東西!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/creativity-booster-by-alpe-audio</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/creativity-booster-by-alpe-audio</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 23:28:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>No more writers block. Don&apos;t stay stuck wondering how to open your lesson, article or video. Automatically generate great opening hooks, stories and relevant examples about anything you want to teach or write about!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Christmas Design Assets by Iconfinder - 免費的節日圖標、插圖和動畫]]></title><description><![CDATA[用這些節日的好東西灑在你的季節性內容上。小精靈們來了，他們帶來了充滿設計資產的聖誕贈品，非常適合你的節日通訊、簡報和社交媒體帖子。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/christmas-design-assets-by-iconfinder</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/christmas-design-assets-by-iconfinder</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 16:02:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Sprinkle up your seasonal content with these festive goodies. Here come the elves with a Christmas freebie full of design assets that are perfect for your holiday newsletters, presentations &amp; social media posts.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[HiHo - 具有無限線程的異步視頻討論區]]></title><description><![CDATA[HiHo是一個面對面的社交應用程序，用於認識有趣的人並進行精彩的視頻對話。通過異步回覆和無限線程，每個人都可以在任何時間參與。該應用程序既提供公共論壇，也提供私人DMs。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hiho</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/hiho</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 16:02:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>HiHo is a face-forward social app for meeting interesting people and having great video conversations. With asynchronous replies and infinite threading, everyone can participate at any time. The app offers both public forums as well as private DMs.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CommerceBooster - 一個用於電子商務的開源B2B UI模板]]></title><description><![CDATA[CommerceBooster是第一個開源的B2B電子商務的UI模板。它可以在Figma社區免費使用，並針對commercetools和Vue Storefront進行了優化。它實際上爲任何開始B2B電子商務項目的人節省了幾個月的工作。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/commercebooster</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/commercebooster</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 15:52:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>CommerceBooster is the first open-source, UI template for B2B eCommerce. It’s available for free on the Figma Community and optimized for commercetools and Vue Storefront. It literally saves months of work for anyone starting B2B eCommerce projects.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Carrot - 你的所有購物，像魔術一樣組織起來]]></title><description><![CDATA[無法跟蹤你想買的東西？認識一下Carrot，這個擴展可以在你購物時自動收集你的購物車。你可以通過點擊回到產品上，創建可分享和可贈送的收藏，獲得降價提醒，而且完全免費！這就是Carrot。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/carrot-4400273f-0d5e-4a81-a978-0f2477a39ad6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/carrot-4400273f-0d5e-4a81-a978-0f2477a39ad6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 13:14:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Can’t keep track of the stuff you want to buy? Meet Carrot, the extension that automatically collects your carts as you shop. You can get back to products with a click, create shareable and gift-able collections, get price drop alerts, and it&apos;s totally free!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pilot - 遠程團隊的薪資、福利和合規性]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pilot爲擁有遠程團隊的美國公司提供薪資、福利和合規性。輕鬆地在160多個國家的員工和240多個國家的承包商入職和付款。爲Product Hunt用戶提供特殊價格： pilot.co/producthunt]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pilot-8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pilot-8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 12:55:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Pilot provides payroll, benefits, and compliance for US-based companies with remote teams. Easily onboard and pay employees in 160+ countries and contractors in 240+ countries. Offering special pricing for Product Hunt users: pilot.co/producthunt</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Battle of Mars - 一個玩家與玩家之間的NFT遊戲]]></title><description><![CDATA[火星之戰是一個PVP的NFT遊戲，你可以挑戰對方，把對手的火星人帶走。1. 鑄造一個火星人（有10,000個獨特的火星人） 2. 加入一個加密派別 3. 挑戰朋友並奪走他們的火星人]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-battle-of-mars</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-battle-of-mars</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 10:16:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The Battle of Mars is a PVP NFT game where you can challenge each other and take your opponent&apos;s Martian away. 1. Mint a Martian (10,000 unique martians available) 2. Join a crypto faction 3. Challenge a friend and take their Martian away</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pretty Progress - 在你的iPhone主屏幕上有漂亮的倒計時小工具]]></title><description><![CDATA[漂亮的進度允許你在你的iPhone主屏幕上添加漂亮的個性化的倒計時和進度條部件。在你每天使用的設備上跟蹤並提醒自己重要的事情。清晰而方便。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pretty-progress</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/pretty-progress</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 10:16:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Pretty Progress allows you to add beautiful &amp; personalized Countdown &amp; Progress Bar widgets on your iPhone&apos;s Home Screen. Track and remind yourself about the important things on the device you use every day. Clear and convenient.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Adobe Creative Cloud Express - 快速、輕鬆地製作社交圖形和更多]]></title><description><![CDATA[Creative Cloud Express（以前的Adobe Spark）使您可以輕鬆地開始使用數以千計的精美模板，以及用於社交媒體內容、標誌和更多的資產。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/adobe-creative-cloud-express</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/adobe-creative-cloud-express</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 10:01:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Creative Cloud Express (formerly Adobe Spark) makes it easy to get started with thousands of beautiful templates, plus assets for social media content, logos, and more.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Albert - 在Slack上爲你的團隊提高網絡安全意識]]></title><description><![CDATA[艾伯特通過Slack向你的團隊傳授網絡安全基礎知識。這些課程很短，爲每個員工動態定製，具有互動性，並且全年發送。這就是爲什麼你的團隊會喜歡它。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/albert-5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/albert-5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 09:48:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Albert teaches cybersecurity basics to your team over Slack. The courses are short, dynamically customized for each employee, interactive, and sent all year long. That&apos;s why your team will love it.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tella for Chrome - 在Chrome瀏覽器的任何地方都能錄製精彩的視頻]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tella for Chrome，屏幕和相機記錄器，讓你的工作看起來很棒。在Chrome瀏覽器的任何地方錄製完全可定製的、可立即分享的視頻。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tella-for-chrome</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tella-for-chrome</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 09:31:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Tella for Chrome, the screen and camera recorder that makes your work look great. Record fully customisable, instantly shareable videos from anywhere in Chrome.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Around 3.0 - 爲你的下一個快樂時光提供帶有音樂和遊戲的視頻通話]]></title><description><![CDATA[Around獨特的視頻通話旨在幫助混合遠程團隊一起創造、協作和慶祝。現在還配有音樂和遊戲，以促進團隊的團結和聯繫。在你的下一個快樂時光或聯合辦公會議上試試吧。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/around-3-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/around-3-0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:47:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Around&apos;s radically unique video calls are designed to help hybrid-remote teams create, collaborate and celebrate together. Now comes with music and games for team bonding and connection. Try it for your next happy hour or co-working session.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Smart VC Search by Unicorn Nest - 爲你的創業公司提供免費的獨特的相關風險投資商名單]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們建立了一個算法，分析38000個風險投資基金的歷史數據，爲初創企業推薦相關的投資者（種子期、A輪、B輪和C輪）。填寫調查問卷 ➡️獲得一份VC名單（包括決策者） ➡️立即開始投資者推廣 🚀]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/smart-vc-search-by-unicorn-nest</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/smart-vc-search-by-unicorn-nest</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:47:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We&apos;ve built an algorithm that analyses historical data of 38,000 VC funds and suggests relevant investors for startups (seed, round A, B and C). Fill in the questionnaire ➡️ Get a list of VCs (incl. decision makers) ➡️ Start investor outreach immediately 🚀</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>