<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Product Hunt 热门]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览 Product Hunt 热门App，网站和产品]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 17:42:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Snoozz - 緩衝標籤和窗口，以便以後使用]]></title><description><![CDATA["Snoozz "標籤和窗口現在就會自動重新打開 - 暫停個別標籤、選定的標籤或整個窗口 - 暫停一次或重複間隔（每週或每月） - 極其輕量級和開放源代碼 閱讀更多信息，請訪問https://snoozz.me]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/snoozz</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/snoozz</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 17:19:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&quot;Snoozz&quot; tabs and windows now and they will reopen automatically later - Snooze individual tabs, selected tabs, or full windows - Snooze once or at repeated intervals (weekly or monthly) - Extremely lightweight and open source Read more on the https://snoozz.me</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gwaber - 聯繫到1,000,000多名遠程工作者，申請遠程工作。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gwaber是一個簡單的平臺，在一個地方連接遠程求職者和遠程公司。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/gwaber</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/gwaber</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 16:59:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Gwaber is an easy platform that connect between remote job seekers and remote companies in one place.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[UKO - 免費的Figma儀表盤和設計系統]]></title><description><![CDATA[Uko是一個免費的Figma儀表盤和設計系統捆綁包，包含大量的組件和頁面。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/uko</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/uko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 14:01:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Uko is a Free Figma Dashboards &amp; Design System Bundle with lots of Components and pages</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NeuralCam 5 - 4800萬像素的iPhone照片，夜間模式，HDR和微距模式]]></title><description><![CDATA[NeuralCam 5是iPhone上最先進的計算攝影相機應用程序，可用於拍攝夜間和白天的照片。通過人工智能驅動的4800萬像素超級分辨率、微距模式和NeuralHDR捕捉更好的照片。更多詳情請見：https://neural.cam/news/ https://neural.cam/news/nightmode5/]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/neuralcam-5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/neuralcam-5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 13:29:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>NeuralCam 5 is the most advanced Computational Photography Camera App for the iPhone for both Night and Day photos. Capture better photos with AI powered 48MP Super-resolution, Macro-Mode and NeuralHDR. More details here: https://neural.cam/news/ https://neural.cam/news/nightmode5/</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sleek - 愉快地完成任務]]></title><description><![CDATA[發現一種新的令人愉快的方式來創建和管理你的待辦事項。爲任務和提醒引入了一個新的彩色等級系統。Sleek是完全可定製的! 你可以改變主題和字體。設置到期日和提醒，添加註釋、鏈接和更多]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sleek-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/sleek-3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 13:29:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Discover a new delightful way to create and manage your to-do&apos;s. Introducing a new colorful Rank system for tasks and reminders. Sleek is completely customizable! You can change themes and fonts. Set due dates and reminders, add notes, links and more!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YouNote - 無縫記下YouTube視頻]]></title><description><![CDATA[YouNote是一個極其簡單的網絡應用程序，允許用戶觀看YouTube視頻並在旁邊以RichText格式做筆記。目前處於測試階段。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/younote</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/younote</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 13:29:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>YouNote is an extremely simple web application that allows users to watch a YouTube video and take notes next to it in RichText format. Currently in Beta.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Quire Nested Kanban Board - 讓無限嵌套的任務列表遇到看板]]></title><description><![CDATA[Quire是一個現代協作應用程序，旨在幫助有遠見的團隊實現大的想法。以嵌套任務列表視圖而聞名，現在引入了嵌套看板視圖。在Inc和Huffington Post上被評爲最佳項目管理軟件之一。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/quire-nested-kanban-board</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/quire-nested-kanban-board</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 11:46:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Quire is a modern collaborative app made to help visionary teams with big ideas. Well-known for Nested Task List View, now introducing Nested Kanban Board View. Featured as one of the best project management software on Inc and Huffington Post.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Outdone - 人工智能驅動的禮物推薦]]></title><description><![CDATA[特殊場合是有壓力的。Outdone的Ai-powered禮品推薦器讓你少了一件事的煩惱。目前，Outdone的引擎推薦服裝品牌，但我們計劃擴大到其他禮品類別，並很快將用戶引向特定的產品!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/outdone</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/outdone</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 11:24:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Special occasions are stressful. Outdone&apos;s Ai-powered gift recommender gives you one less thing to worry about. For now, Outdone&apos;s engine recommends apparel brands, but we plan to expand into other gift categories and drive users to specific products soon!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Runbooks by Airplane - 將腳本、SQL等轉化爲內部工作流程]]></title><description><![CDATA[Airplane Runbooks可以輕鬆地將少量的代碼變成複雜的內部工作流程。模擬入職流程、管理操作、類似於cron的時間表等等，並與你的團隊分享。它就像Zapier，但適用於觸及prod數據的第一方操作。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/runbooks-by-airplane</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/runbooks-by-airplane</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 09:01:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Airplane Runbooks make it easy to turn small amounts of code into complex internal workflows. Model onboarding flows, admin operations, cron-like schedules and more and share with your team. It&apos;s like Zapier but for first-party operations that touch prod data.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SuperDMs - 只需2次點擊，就能向所有的Twitter回覆發送批量DMs]]></title><description><![CDATA[SuperDMs通過向你的推特迴應者批量發送DM，幫助你增加你的關注。你可以使用SuperDMs來發送你的。- 贈品 - 通訊 - 獨特的優惠 - 特別策劃的內容 SuperDMs是所有活躍的Twitter用戶的理想選擇。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/superdms</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/superdms</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 08:37:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>SuperDMs helps you grow your following by sending bulk DMs to your tweet responders. You can use SuperDMs to send your: - Giveaways - Newsletters - Offers that are unique - Specially-curated content SuperDMs is ideal for all active Twitter users.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BiFi X - 輕鬆的閃電貸款。獲得槓桿收益的耕作和交易。]]></title><description><![CDATA[BiFi X是一項DeFi服務，使你能夠在一次交易中使用閃電式貸款的收益耕作和保證金交易頭寸獲得最大的槓桿。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bifi-x</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bifi-x</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 08:18:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>BiFi X is a DeFi service that enables you to get maximum leverage in a single transaction using flash loans on yield farming and margin trading positions.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Okel - 與合適的陌生人分享膳食並不奇怪]]></title><description><![CDATA[Okel是一個社交平臺，通過分享當地餐館的飯菜將用戶聯繫起來。與約會軟件的功能類似，Okel根據共同的興趣、最喜歡的美食和可用的時間來匹配用戶。等待名單 👉 https://www.joinokel.com/]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/okel</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/okel</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 08:18:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Okel is a social platform that connects users over sharing meals at local restaurants. Similar to how dating apps function, Okel matches users based on shared interests, favorite cuisines, and times of availability. Waitlist 👉 https://www.joinokel.com/</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reward Hunt - 每週通過對喜歡的產品進行評論獲得100美元的獎金]]></title><description><![CDATA[在Capterra、G2、Trustpilot等網站上有75.000美元的活躍評論獎勵計劃。通過對你最喜歡的產品進行評論或發現新的產品來獲得報酬! 獎勵計劃的產品搜索]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/reward-hunt</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/reward-hunt</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 22:00:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>$75.000 active review reward programs on Capterra, G2, Trustpilot etc. Get paid by making review about your favorite products or discovering new ones! Product Hunt for Reward Programs</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fantasy Startup - 財務複雜性是新的投資標準]]></title><description><![CDATA[通過這種真實的模擬，你將--在幾周內體驗10年的投資；--掌握股權的非流動性；--建立耐心、紀律和毅力；--發現如何保護你的淨資產；以及--成爲財務上的老手。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fantasy-startup</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fantasy-startup</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 15:19:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With this real-to-life simulation, you will - Experience 10 yrs of investing in a few weeks; - Grasp the illiquid nature of equity; - Build patience, discipline &amp; perseverance; - Discover how to protect your net worth; and - Become Financially Sophisticated</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wicked Launchers - 13個帶有HTML、Tailwind CSS的啓動器和即將推出的模板]]></title><description><![CDATA[Wicked Launchers是一個用Tailwind CSS製作的13個英雄的集合，準備好獲得註冊，將它連接到你的數據庫，使用你的副本，你就可以開始了]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/wicked-launchers</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/wicked-launchers</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 14:17:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Wicked Launchers is a collection of 13 heros made with Tailwind CSS ready to get Sign Ups, connect it to your data base, use your copy and you are ready to go!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Biport Wallet - 你的去中心化的多幣種錢包]]></title><description><![CDATA[用Biport多鏈錢包開始你的區塊鏈之旅，適用於比特幣、以太坊、BSC以及其他。Biport允許你在一個地方管理散落在不同區塊鏈上的加密貨幣，而不需要切換區塊鏈網絡。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/biport-wallet</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/biport-wallet</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 13:32:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Start your blockchain journey with Biport Multichain Wallet for Bitcoin, Ethereum, BSC, and beyond. Biport allows you to manage cryptocurrencies scattered across different blockchains all in one place without switching blockchain networks.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ZUQ.AI for Facebook Messenger - 創建你自己的人工智能客戶支持代理，不需要代碼]]></title><description><![CDATA[Zuq學習您的常見問題，並立即爲您的客戶提供重複性問題的相關答案。Zuq就像一個完美的客戶支持人工智能代理，它將晝夜不停地工作，總是很有禮貌，只會變得更聰明，而且永遠不會退出。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zuq-ai-for-facebook-messenger</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/zuq-ai-for-facebook-messenger</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 12:44:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Zuq learns your FAQ and instantly provides your customers with relevant answers to repetitive questions. Zuq is like a perfect customer support AI agent that will work around the clock, always be polite, only get smarter, and will never quit.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Emojination - 使用表情符號創建有趣的引人入勝的圖形 😎]]></title><description><![CDATA[一個結合了表情符號和現代美學的簡單設計工具。在幾秒鐘內創建有趣的引人入勝的視覺效果。壯大你的社交媒體，表達你的公司文化，脫穎而出，最重要的是要有樂趣!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/emojination-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/emojination-3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 11:26:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A simple design tool combining emojis and modern aesthetics. Create fun engaging visuals in seconds. Grow your social media, express your company culture, standout and most importantly have fun!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Podcast Audiogram Creator by Milk Video - 帶有社會剪輯的標題和標誌的視頻字幕生成器]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是一個將播客快速轉化爲社會聽覺的工具。它不需要註冊，而且是免費的! 它是如何工作的。* 上傳一個播客 *添加標題和設置顏色 *剪輯一個關鍵時刻 *下載和分享 如果你有一個播客，我們希望得到你的反饋!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/podcast-audiogram-creator-by-milk-video</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/podcast-audiogram-creator-by-milk-video</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 11:26:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>This is a tool to quickly turn podcasts into social audiograms. There is no sign up and it&apos;s free! How it works: * Upload a podcast * Add titles and set colors * Clip a key moment * Download and share If you have a podcast, we would love your feedback!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Co.Lab Learning - 與他人一起，在小組中現場學習]]></title><description><![CDATA[一種新的多人在線學習方法。通過Co.Lab的混合直播、無講師的課程，觀看視頻、開展活動、分享觀點並交朋友。通過在親密的小團體中相互學習和交流，更深入地學習。#LearnTogether]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/co-lab-learning</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/co-lab-learning</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 11:01:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>A new multiplayer-method of learning online. Watch videos, do activities, share perspectives and make friends via Co.Lab’s hybrid-live, instructor-less courses. Go deeper by learning with and from one another in small intimate groups. #LearnTogether</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MRR Meter Generator - 爲你的Twitter和Instagram簡歷提供ASCII進度條]]></title><description><![CDATA[生成很酷的進度條，展示你的MRR朝着你的夢想目標的進展。🤑非常適合獨立黑客和創業者在公開場合建立他們的開放式創業公司。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mrr-meter-generator</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/mrr-meter-generator</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 10:40:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Generate cool progress bars to showcase your MRR progress toward your dream goals. 🤑 Perfect for indie hackers &amp; entrepreneurs who build in public their open startups.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Ultimate Google Sheet Toolkit - 99個資源來提高你的電子表格遊戲]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們把一個精心策劃的模板、視頻和教程列表放在一起，可以幫助你建立你的分析專業知識。瀏覽這個目錄，爲你的任務找到合適的工具。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-ultimate-google-sheet-toolkit</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-ultimate-google-sheet-toolkit</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 10:40:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>We put together a curated list of templates, videos, and tutorials that can help you build your analytics expertise. Browse through this directory to find the right tools for your task.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fundraising Market Map - 所有可用於籌款的工具的視覺概述]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲你的初創企業獲得資金是很難的，但有數百家公司在幫助你進行籌款工作。這張地圖是對籌款生態系統中每一個參與者的直觀概述。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fundraising-market-map</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fundraising-market-map</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 10:24:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Getting funding for your startup is hard, but there are hundreds of companies helping you with your fundraising efforts. This map is a visual overview of every player in the fundraising ecosystem.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Headroom 2.0 - 通過實時AI視頻會議進行免提會議]]></title><description><![CDATA[淨空實現了自然的視頻通話。我們的人工智能可以識別手勢，提供實時記錄和摘要，並允許你在重播、記錄和筆記中進行搜索。專注於人，讓Headroom將工作自動化。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/headroom-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/headroom-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 10:24:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Headroom enables natural video calls. Our AI recognizes gestures, provides real-time transcripts and summaries, and allows you to search across replays, transcripts and notes. ​​Focus on people and let Headroom automate away the work.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AcquireFlow - 英國和歐洲的SaaS、電子商務初創企業收購市場]]></title><description><![CDATA[AcquireFlow是英國和歐洲的免費私人收購市場，供數字初創企業的買家和賣家使用。我們專注於SaaS、電子商務和亞馬遜FBA等關鍵領域。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/acquireflow</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/acquireflow</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 10:03:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>AcquireFlow is the UK &amp; Europe&apos;s free private acquisition marketplace for buyers and sellers of digital startups. We focus on the key areas of SaaS, e-commerce and Amazon FBA.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Status Page by Spike.sh - 爲你的網站、應用程序或商店提供漂亮的狀態頁面]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲您的網站、應用程序和商店創建漂亮的品牌狀態頁。🚀 快速設置 - 在2分鐘內創建您的品牌狀態頁。分享有關事故和計劃維修的實時更新。🎁 12月免費提供無限的狀態頁!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/status-page-by-spike-sh</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/status-page-by-spike-sh</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 09:46:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Create beautiful and branded Status Pages for your website, app and store. 🚀 Fast setup - create your branded status page in 2 minutes. Share real time updates about incidents and planned maintenances. 🎁 Unlimited Status Pages for free in December!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chatwoot 2.0 - 開源的自我託管的客戶參與套件]]></title><description><![CDATA[Chatwoot是一個開源的、自我託管的客戶參與套件。通過Chatwoot，你可以查看和管理你的客戶數據，與他們溝通，無論他們使用哪種媒介，並根據他們的資料重新與他們接觸。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/chatwoot-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/chatwoot-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 09:33:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Chatwoot is an open-source, self-hosted customer engagement suite. With Chatwoot, you can view and manage your customer data, communicate with them irrespective of which medium they use, and re-engage them based on their profile.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ycode - 無代碼網絡應用程序生成器，設計與功能完美結合]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ycode是一個可視化的開發平臺，使創作者能夠在無需僱傭開發人員的情況下建立自定義的網絡項目。Ycode的使命是使視覺開發與手工編碼一樣強大，只是更快、更容易獲得。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ycode-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/ycode-3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 09:33:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Ycode is a visual development platform that enables creators to build custom web projects without having to hire developers. Ycode&apos;s mission is to make visual development as powerful as coding by hand—just faster and more accessible.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nanonets Table Extractor - 從任何文件中提取超強的表格]]></title><description><![CDATA[使用Nanonets的無代碼表格提取器，可以節省從各種文檔中提取表格數據的時間、精力和資源。自動捕捉任何 "類似表格 "的結構，提取整個表格或只提取特定單元格/行/列的數據。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nanonets-table-extractor</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/nanonets-table-extractor</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 09:01:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Save time, effort &amp; resources&amp;nbsp;spent on extracting tabular data from all kinds of documents with Nanonets’ no-code table extractor. Automatically capture any “table-like” structure, extract entire tables or just pull data from specific cells/rows/columns.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Quarkly 2.0 - 在React上創建網站和網絡應用的無代碼平臺]]></title><description><![CDATA[你是否一直在尋找一個無需代碼的快速上市的React構建器，並在需要時進行深入控制？你是否對快速創建一個在圖形用戶界面和代碼輸入之間保持良好平衡的用戶界面感興趣？告訴你一個好消息--現在你可以使用Quarkly了。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/quarkly-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/quarkly-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 09:01:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Have you been searching for a no-code fast-to-market builder in React with in-depth controls when needed? Are you interested in quickly creating a UI with a good balance between GUI and code input? Good news for you — now you can use Quarkly.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WeWeb 2.0 - 唯一一個與後端無關的無代碼前端構建器]]></title><description><![CDATA[WeWeb是建立生產就緒的網絡應用程序的最快方式： - 連接多個數據源（如Airtable、REST APIs、XANO、PostgreSQL） - 可視化設計你的前端或添加自定義組件（vue.js / react） - 建立無代碼工作流或添加自定義JS]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/weweb-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/weweb-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 09:01:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>WeWeb is the fastest way to build production-ready web apps: - connect multiple data sources (e.g. Airtable, REST APIs, XANO, PostgreSQL) - visually design your frontend or add custom components (vue.js / react) - build no-code workflows or add custom JS</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stytch - 現代應用的用戶基礎設施]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stytch是一個全堆棧認證和授權平臺，其API使其能夠簡單地無縫地加入、認證和吸引用戶。通過無密碼，提高安全性和用戶體驗。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/stytch</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/stytch</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 08:49:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Stytch is a full stack authentication and authorization platform, whose APIs make it simple to seamlessly onboard, authenticate and engage users. Improve security and user experience by going passwordless.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bookstash - 在3分鐘內獲得頂級書籍的精髓]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bookstash是一個免費的圖書館，收錄了頂級非小說類書籍的精選摘要。我們爲你挑選一本書，並給你所有的關鍵想法，你可以保存你的最愛，以便以後跟蹤你的閱讀進度。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bookstash</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/bookstash</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 08:18:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Bookstash is a free library of curated summaries from top nonfiction books. We pick a book for you and give you all the key ideas and you get to save your favorites for later &amp; track your reading progress.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Universal UI Kit (Web) v1.0 - 用於在Figma中創建網站的強大的Web UI組件]]></title><description><![CDATA[強大的 Web UI 套件，用於在 Figma 中創建登陸頁面、網站和儀表板。使用我們的 UI 套件可節省數百個小時。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/universal-ui-kit-web-v1-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/universal-ui-kit-web-v1-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 08:18:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Powerful Web UI kit for creating landing pages, websites and dashboards in Figma. Save hundreds of hours with our UI Kit.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wannadocs - 知識庫管理系統]]></title><description><![CDATA[爲你的客戶創建公共產品文檔，或爲你的團隊創建內部知識庫，所有這些都在同一個令人敬畏的用戶界面中🖖。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/wannadocs</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/wannadocs</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 08:18:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Create public product docs for your customers or internal knowledge base for your team, all within the same awesome UI 🖖</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Founders' Book 2.0 - 世界上最大的創始人工具和資源庫]]></title><description><![CDATA[創始人和創始團隊在建立和擴大他們的想法方面的知識差距是真實的、昂貴的和耗時的。這種差距傷害了我們的想法、信心和雄心壯志! 因此，《創始人之書》支持他們的風險建設過程。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/founders-book-2-0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/founders-book-2-0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 07:48:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>The knowledge gap in founders and founding teams to build on and scale their ideas is real, expensive and time-consuming. This gap hurt our ideas, confidence and ambition! Hence Founders’ Book to support their venture building process.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[OKR for Jira - 用OKRs使你的日常工作與公司戰略保持一致]]></title><description><![CDATA[在Jira中管理你的OKRs的最佳方式。通過OKRs使你的日常工作與公司戰略保持一致。通過在Jira中跟蹤你的OKRs，關注真正重要的事情。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/okr-for-jira-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/okr-for-jira-2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 03:01:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Best way to manage your OKRs in Jira. Align your daily work to the company strategy with OKRs. Focus on what really matters by tracking your OKRs in Jira.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Clubs Poker - 讓你的下一次公司活動成爲在線撲克之夜]]></title><description><![CDATA[拋棄虛擬的歡樂時光，用Clubs Poker的新產品-->"For Companies "來舉辦一個撲克之夜 💚 只需將鏈接發送給你的同事，就可以開始遊戲 💚 在桌子和牌上添加你公司的標誌 💚 專門的活動主持（可選）]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/clubs-poker-for-companies</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/clubs-poker-for-companies</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 16:33:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Ditch the virtual happy hours and host a poker night instead with Clubs Poker&apos;s new product --&gt; &quot;For Companies&quot; 💚 Just send a link to your colleagues and start playing 💚 Add your company logo to the table and card decks 💚 Dedicated event host (optional)</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AltCoffee - 給人們提供一種用加密貨幣表示感謝的方式]]></title><description><![CDATA[這基本上是一個加密版本的請我喝咖啡。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/altcoffee</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/altcoffee</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 15:16:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>It&apos;s basically a crypto version of buy me a coffee.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Cold Start Problem - 一本關於如何啓動和擴大網絡效應的書]]></title><description><![CDATA[根據對Twitch、Tinder、Uber、Airbnb、Pinterest等公司創始團隊的100次採訪，陳志剛探討了科技界最成功的公司是如何利用網絡效應解決可怕的 "冷啓動問題 "來啓動和擴展的。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-cold-start-problem</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-cold-start-problem</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 14:33:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Based on 100s of interviews with founding teams at Twitch, Tinder, Uber, Airbnb, Pinterest, and many more, Andrew Chen explores how tech’s most successful companies solved the dreaded &quot;cold start problem” using network effects to launch and scale.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Link in Bio - 帶視頻的生物體內鏈接工具，內置無代碼]]></title><description><![CDATA[一個頁面上有你所有的視頻鏈接。要求一個獨特的URL並在你的簡歷中分享。添加你的鏈接，選擇你的主題，你就可以開始了。所有這些都是在沒有代碼的情況下建立的。Webflow + Bubble在4周內完成。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/link-in-bio-1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/link-in-bio-1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 14:06:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>One page for all your links with a video. Claim a unique URL and share in your bio. Add your links, pick your theme and you&apos;re good to go. All built in no-code: Webflow + Bubble in 4 weeks.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Matrix Playground - 矩陣內部的一瞥]]></title><description><![CDATA[在Spline，我們喜歡Matrix，所以我們建立了一個有趣的輔助項目，供大家玩耍。你可以上傳你的3D模型，使用網絡攝像頭看到自己在Matrix代碼中的樣子，並改變粒子的參數。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/matrix-playground</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/matrix-playground</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 13:35:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>At Spline, we love the Matrix so we built a fun side project for everyone to play around! You can upload your 3d models, see yourself inside Matrix code using the webcam, and change the parameters of the particles.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Patchstack - 給你的WordPress堆棧打補丁]]></title><description><![CDATA[監控您所有的WordPress網站，以防止我們的道德黑客社區發現安全漏洞。免費添加多達99個網站!]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/patchstack</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/patchstack</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 12:54:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Monitor all your WordPress sites for security vulnerabilities found by our community of ethical hackers. Add up to 99 websites for free!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gentler - 通過了解你的活動水平來支持長期的健康狀況]]></title><description><![CDATA[瞭解你的活動水平並讓它們指導你的活動生活，可以降低疲勞、倦怠、受傷的機率。Gentler監測你的健身進展，並提示你放慢、加強或休息。它是個性化的，適合所有健身水平。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/gentler</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/gentler</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 11:48:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Knowing your activity levels and having them guide your active life lowers the chances of fatigue, burnout, injury. Gentler monitors your fitness progress and nudges you to slow down, step up, or rest. It is personalized, appropriate for all fitness levels.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The State of Customer Onboarding 2022 - 有史以來第一次關於客戶入職空間的調查]]></title><description><![CDATA[100多位客戶入職專業人士分享了他們預見的2022年的挑戰、目標和趨勢。點擊 "獲取"，下載您的《客戶入職狀況》報告副本。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-state-of-customer-onboarding-2022</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/the-state-of-customer-onboarding-2022</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 11:03:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>100+ customer onboarding professionals share the challenges, goals, and trends they foresee in 2022. Click ‘Get it’ to download your copy of The State of Customer Onboarding report.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CloudTalk for Mobile - 用於擴大銷售和支持團隊規模的呼叫軟件]]></title><description><![CDATA[CloudTalk Go允許銷售、支持和運營團隊在辦公室外使用WiFi或移動網絡保持聯繫並專業地處理客戶來電。可在iOS應用商店和Android Play商店購買。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/cloudtalk-for-mobile</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/cloudtalk-for-mobile</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 10:46:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>CloudTalk Go allows Sales, Support &amp; Operation teams to stay connected and professionally handle customer calls outside of the office using WiFi or mobile networks. Available on the iOS App Store and the Android Play Store.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenScout by Landscape - 爲多家風險投資公司物色人才，推薦人可獲得高達5萬美元的獎金]]></title><description><![CDATA[通過OpenScout，投資者可以從精心挑選的星探那裏獲得各種交易信息。風險投資偵察員可以與整個投資者市場分享交易，並獲得成功的費用（5千至5萬美金！）。申請加入我們的邀請測試版，成爲星探或投資者。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/openscout-by-landscape</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/openscout-by-landscape</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 10:46:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>With OpenScout, investors can access diverse dealflow from handpicked scouts. Venture scouts can share deals with an entire marketplace of investors, and get paid a success fee ($5k-50k!). Apply to join as a scout or as an investor for our invite-only beta!</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fathom - 再也不用在Zoom電話中做筆記了]]></title><description><![CDATA[Fathom在你的Zoom通話中只需點擊一個按鈕就能記錄、轉錄和取代筆記，因此你可以簡單地專注於手頭的對話。通過電子郵件、Slack或發送到CRM的自動生成的摘要，輕鬆地與你的團隊分享通話要點。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fathom-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/fathom-2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 10:32:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Fathom records, transcribes, and replaces note taking with a click of a button on your Zoom calls, so you can simply focus on the conversation at hand. Easily share call highlights with your team via email, Slack, or auto-generated summaries sent to your CRM.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tailwind CSS Cheat Sheet - 在一個頁面上來自Tailwind CSS的每一個類名]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一個頁面上訪問和搜索Tailwind CSS的每一個實用類，並加速你的開發過程。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tailwind-css-cheat-sheet</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/tailwind-css-cheat-sheet</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 10:32:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>Get access and search for every utility class from Tailwind CSS on a single page and accelerate your development process.</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Screeb - 針對SaaS、安卓和iOS應用的免費應用內NPS調查]]></title><description><![CDATA[應用內NPS調查具有非侵入性、突破性的受訪者體驗、強大的目標定位能力和預建報告。可用於SaaS、安卓和iOS應用程序，免費提供，對用戶數量或回覆數量沒有任何限制。]]></description><link>https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/screeb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ph.buzzing.cc/ph/screeb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 09:38:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>In-app NPS surveys with a non-intrusive, breakthrough respondent experience, powerful targeting capabilities and pre-built reports. Available for SaaS, Android and iOS apps, for free without any limitation on your number of users or the number of responses.</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>